<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mac on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/mac/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mac on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/mac/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s decided</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/05/05/its-decided/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/05/05/its-decided/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s decided, my next machine will be an Apple computer. Most likely I will end up buying a Mac Mini, although an iMac is also being considered. Now, who wants a (still under warranty) DELL XPS 630i? It is a Q6600 (quad), with 4GB RAM, 500GB HD, and NVIDIA 9800GT. Comes with Windows 7 Ultimate. Nice machine!
Note: Someone contacted me, but the email went to spam, and got deleted. Try again please, I have whitelisted the contact form address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do you want to try it?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/20/do-you-want-to-try-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/20/do-you-want-to-try-it/</guid>
      <description>A demo of Office 2004 for Mac is available for Mac users to try. From Microsoft MacTopia Office 2004 page:
 &amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;There&amp;rsquo;s time for fun and time to focus. When you&amp;rsquo;re ready to get down to business, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Office 2004 for Mac provides the intuitive, intelligent tools you need to transform your ideas and opportunities into action&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
 No, thank you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got a Mac, once again</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/11/13/got-a-mac-once-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/11/13/got-a-mac-once-again/</guid>
      <description>My first knowledge about Mac&amp;rsquo;s came sorrounded by a mist of legend, legend that has lived until today: Mac&amp;rsquo;s are wonderful, powerful, friendly machines, that boot with a graphic interface and which mouse has only one big button. Ok, that was what I thought 15 years ago or so, but you get the idea.
Eight months ago I bought a dual 1.42 Ghz PowerMac G4, with 2GB RAM, 128 VRAM, 120GB HD, SuperDrive, Bluetooth&amp;hellip; beautiful machine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>