<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>family on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/categories/family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in family on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 20:22:10 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/categories/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Friend</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2019/02/11/my-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 20:22:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2019/02/11/my-friend/</guid>
      <description>Friends are not easy to come by. They are made, just like good wine, after many years of ageing. At a certain point, which is hard to pinpoint, they cease to be just friends to become family. Just like a family member would, and should, they give you the best advise, uncompromisingly, unabashedly, unreservedly. They praise your virtues and take pride on them, but are quick to call out the stupid things you are bound to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandfather has left us</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/01/13/grandfather-has-left-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 14:40:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/01/13/grandfather-has-left-us/</guid>
      <description>Grandfather died today.
Kim was very close to him because she lived with her grandparents since she was young, until we got married. Back in Vietnam, when she was in elementary school, grandpa took her and her siblings to school, and picked them up in his bicycle every day. He was more than a grandfather to her. He was, throughout her life, a father figure.
Grandpa was a soft spoken man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mi Vieja</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/12/03/mi-vieja/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/12/03/mi-vieja/</guid>
      <description>She created me, all my flaws and gifts unintended. She nurtured and guided me through life the best she could, suffering for my mistakes &amp;mdash;but always hopeful&amp;mdash; and rejoicing on my victories. Always supportive she gave herself to me (and my siblings), selflessly.
After a lifetime mission, her time around here has expired. We knew it would come, but never fully prepared for it. And so we wept, sadness seeping through us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mi viejo</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/11/26/mi-viejo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/11/26/mi-viejo/</guid>
      <description>A steady, yet gentle, rain was falling over Miami on the night of November 24th, 2010. Some say rain are tears from the sky. I was crying as well. On November 24th my father died.
Those who have lost an infinitely dear one will understand how I feel. Not only did I lose the best father a son could have, I lost a lifetime friend, a restless protector, a confidant. The many memories that I have of him continue to bring tears.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>