<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Iphone on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/iphone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Iphone on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/iphone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple on Encryption</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/21/apple-on-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/21/apple-on-encryption/</guid>
      <description>Apple mobile devices&amp;mdash;iPhones, iPads, iPods&amp;mdash;are used everywhere. The US smartphone subscriber market share highest percentage is dominated by them. As an American company, they are bound to comply with U.S. laws and regulations. So, when the U.S. Justice Department requested that Apple grants access to a locked iPhone, Apple brought the case to court.
 Apple Inc told a U.S. judge that accessing data stored on a locked iPhone would be &amp;ldquo;impossible&amp;rdquo; with devices using its latest operating system, but the company has the &amp;ldquo;technical ability&amp;rdquo; to help law enforcement unlock older phones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the removal of Garbage Apps</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/15/about-the-removal-of-garbage-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/15/about-the-removal-of-garbage-apps/</guid>
      <description>Tim Cook answered a few questions for BuzzFeed, while they talked about things iPhone, iPad Pro, and many other Apple&amp;ndash;related things. This part got close to me, as I am sure it might be to anyone who likes iPhones. Why can&amp;rsquo;t we remove certain apps?
 Why are there apps on the iOS that I can’t delete even though I never use them? Why does Apple insist that I keep Tips and Stocks”on my iPhone when I’d like nothing more than to delete them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Unthinkable</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/06/25/the-unthinkable/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/06/25/the-unthinkable/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I did the unthinkable. Something I have never done &amp;mdash; nor will I do again &amp;mdash; before. I went very early (03:15) to stand at the Millenia all, to be one of the first (or so I thought) to buy the iPhone 4.
I don&amp;rsquo;t want to write long about something I am more than half way ashamed of. Suffice it to say that I got an iPhone 4 after standing in line for 14 hours (17:15).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The wheels of justice</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/26/the-wheels-of-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/26/the-wheels-of-justice/</guid>
      <description>I thought twice before coming here and write two or three sentences. But sometimes two or three sentences is all you have. I had to do it: Apple Inc., you rock!
If you want to be a &amp;ldquo;journalist&amp;rdquo;, act as one. As Powazek wrote in a tweet, &amp;ldquo;Real journalists don&amp;rsquo;t buy stolen property.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selling iPhone</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/10/13/selling-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/10/13/selling-iphone/</guid>
      <description>In an effort to start saving money towards an Android based device (would love HTC Hero), I am selling my 2G 16GB iPhone. As the eBay listing reads, it is a very well kept, 2G 16GB iPhone, unlocked and jailbroken. No scratches, no blemishes. Bid starts at $1, no reserve. Yes, $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone is near, Leopard not so</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/12/iphone-is-near-leopard-not-so/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/12/iphone-is-near-leopard-not-so/</guid>
      <description>For many Apple fans (me included) that were anxiously waiting for both products, this is a good and slight bad news. Good news, iPhone is on track and it will be delivered as promised. Slight bad news, we will have to wait a bit longer for the Big Cat to come out.
 Apple - Hot News &amp;ndash; iPhone has already passed several of its required certification tests and is on schedule to ship in late June as planned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wired News: Apple&#39;s iPhone is Calling</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/11/15/wired-news-apples-iphone-is-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/11/15/wired-news-apples-iphone-is-calling/</guid>
      <description>Wired News: Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone is Calling
 The most likely scenario, as Jupiter analyst Ian Fogg has pointed out, is that the iPhone will be a stand-alone device that will accept a standard SIM card. You&amp;rsquo;ll pop the SIM card out of your current cell phone and plug it into the iPhone. It&amp;rsquo;ll be just like buying an unlocked handset from Asia, except you&amp;rsquo;ll buy it at an Apple store instead of on Craigslist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>