<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dad on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/dad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dad on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/dad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday, Viejo!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/02/27/happy-birthday-viejo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/02/27/happy-birthday-viejo/</guid>
      <description>Not a day goes by without me thinking of my Dad. Today he would have being 92 years old.
I still remember him on his 90th birthday, doing push ups using only three fingers on each hand. I will forever remember the endless stories he used to tell, and his constant smile. He was the best father a son can ask for, an example for many. It hurts so very much not to have him around anymore&amp;hellip;!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mi viejo</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/11/26/mi-viejo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/11/26/mi-viejo/</guid>
      <description>A steady, yet gentle, rain was falling over Miami on the night of November 24th, 2010. Some say rain are tears from the sky. I was crying as well. On November 24th my father died.
Those who have lost an infinitely dear one will understand how I feel. Not only did I lose the best father a son could have, I lost a lifetime friend, a restless protector, a confidant. The many memories that I have of him continue to bring tears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mention two</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/07/06/mention-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/07/06/mention-two/</guid>
      <description>My parents are visiting. They got here July 3rd and on July 4th dad was telling me they needed to leave the coming Friday. My old people are really something, but that is not what I wanted to post about.
My father talks, continuously, a lot. He will start with a simple answer to a question I asked and go on into various topics and anecdotes that seem not to have an end.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>