<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>china on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/china/</link>
    <description>Recent content in china on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/china/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Two Child Policy</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/29/chinas-two-child-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/29/chinas-two-child-policy/</guid>
      <description>This one is worth documenting, as it doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen every day. As a matter of fact, it hasn&amp;rsquo;t happened for over three decades.
 &amp;ldquo;It is the latest twist in the most ambitious and ruthless social-engineering program ever undertaken by a modern state: Beijing announced Thursday that the Chinese Communist Party will officially abandon its one-child policy. Yet it has no plans to relinquish authority over its subjects’ birth patterns; rather, Beijing has simply changed the ration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China earthquake help</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/15/china-earthquake-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/15/china-earthquake-help/</guid>
      <description>Cities completely wipe out, thousands dead, thousands missing, thousands without anything left. China needs our help, and every little thing would help. Ten dollars might not be much for you, but when many donate we can make a difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics for sports</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/10/olympics-for-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/10/olympics-for-sports/</guid>
      <description>Olympics Games relate to sport. The Olympic Games is where the World most accomplished athletes and teams compete for medals, for the win. Making the Olympics Games a political chess board goes against what Olympic Games are all about. And it is a nasty thing to do.
We&amp;mdash;as in the U.S.A.&amp;mdash;are not being fair with China. Our government and our politicians (including Presidential aspirants) are all playing politics with the Olympics for their own political advantage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese products are cheap</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/09/chinese-products-are-cheap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/09/chinese-products-are-cheap/</guid>
      <description>Not anymore.
 The era of cheap Chinese consumer goods may finally be ending, thanks to irrepressible inflation. Now when the Chinese present their lists, some American importers are conceding higher prices, meaning that American shoppers, for the first time in years, are starting to pick up the tab for rising costs in China. Some Chinese factories are now asking their American customers for price increases of as much as 20 percent to 30 percent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Made in China</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/30/made-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/30/made-in-china/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t have a particular problem with China. I admire its very old culture, its people resourcefulness and their resilience, among other things. But when I see everything I buy here in the U.S. made in China, I feel uncomfortable. It tells me something is wrong with the way we are doing business.
It isn&amp;rsquo;t the &amp;ldquo;Made in China&amp;rdquo; the thing that bugs me. It&amp;rsquo;s the everything &amp;ldquo;Made in China&amp;rdquo; that does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mid-Autumn Festival, Mooncake!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2002/09/17/mid-autumn-festival-mooncake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2002 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2002/09/17/mid-autumn-festival-mooncake/</guid>
      <description>It is mooncake holiday again! Taken From Travel in Taiwan Festivals, the following &amp;ldquo;Legends of the Moon&amp;rdquo;:
 Hhou Yi was a great archer and architect, who shot down nine extra suns that had suddenly appeared in the sky and thus kept the earth from being scorched. He also built a palace of jade for the goddess of the western heaven. For this, he was rewarded with a pill containing the elixir of immortality, but with strings attached &amp;ndash;he must fast and pray for a year before taking it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>