<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>amazon on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/amazon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in amazon on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/amazon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Cloud Drive Feedback</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/11/12/amazon-cloud-drive-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/11/12/amazon-cloud-drive-feedback/</guid>
      <description>This is not merely a technical problem, but I did not have the choice for multiple selections. Anytime I use the word &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; down below, I mean Amazon.
First the good. I love you, I have used AWS S3 for a long time, no complains. I do much of my online purchases on you, although I am not a fervent shopper. I rent my movies on Amazon Video. I am signed up for Flex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On AWS S3</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2012/01/28/on-aws-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2012/01/28/on-aws-s3/</guid>
      <description>I have moved from Linode (which I will be canceling soon) to Namecheap DNS management (I have all my domains on Namecheap) and Amazon S3. Transition went well, and painless. It should save me some money.
Nothing wrong with Linode, which I recommend to anyone looking to having their own Virtual Server. Their service rock, and their price is hard to beat. I used their services for a year and totally loved it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Route 53, wish I could have used you</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/02/24/almost-at-route53-and-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/02/24/almost-at-route53-and-s3/</guid>
      <description>Ever since Amazon announced it&amp;rsquo;s Route 53 service I have been dreaming on using it, but since I dislike to have services too spread out (got Google Apps and Linode now), I held up. Two days ago or so, Amazon announced new features that make hosting static websites&amp;mdash;such as this one&amp;mdash;on AWS S3 buckets possible. This was it, just what I have been waiting for!
Promptly I set off to migrate one of my domains over Route 53.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>