<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bits and Rambles on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bits and Rambles on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 13:15:56 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nín hǎo!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/about/</guid>
      <description>Ego Hi there, welcome! You are now browsing my personal blog. In here I write about whatever happens to interest me from time to time. I am a father and a husband living in Orlando, FL, U.S.A.
I have worked for the Florida Educational System as a system administrator (sysadmin) since June of 1996 or whereabouts, but nothing on this site is affiliated with, sponsored, or endorsed by them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using GPG and Openssl to Encrypt</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2019/07/30/using-gpg-and-openssl-to-encrypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 13:15:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2019/07/30/using-gpg-and-openssl-to-encrypt/</guid>
      <description>I have used gpg to encrypt my private files, specially those that I upload to the clouds, for a long time. I used to encrypt to self, using my own key, then later moved to symmetric encryption only. The command is easy:
To encrypt:
gpg --cipher-algo aes256 --symmetric file.txt Adding the option --armor to the above will produce an ASCII armoured encrypted file.
To decrypt:
gpg --output file.txt --decrypt file.txt.{gpg,asc} Use asc ending to decrypt, if encrypted with the --armor option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There Is Always a First Time</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2019/07/29/there-is-always-a-first-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 17:04:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2019/07/29/there-is-always-a-first-time/</guid>
      <description>For eleven years I have used iPhones exclusively. More than half of that time, I have used them without any cover. My rationale? It is a beautifully crafted device, why to hide its beauty behind a cover? I never had an issue with it, until today. I am coming here to mark the first time my iPhone screen has ever shattered. I didn&amp;rsquo;t drop it, but placed it in a way that, after a few vibrations, made it fall to the floor—a tiled floor, nonetheless, the &amp;ldquo;evil&amp;rdquo; kind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Closing LinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2019/07/29/closing-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 11:48:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2019/07/29/closing-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Not long ago—not even a year now—I re-created a LinkedIn account, mostly following an invitation to join from one of my friends. I did it against my will, because for whatever reason I have hated LinkedIn even since before it was acquired by Microsoft. Yet, I joined, filled very little information, set privacy settings to fully closed—or so I thought—and moved on.
Soon after I started receiving UCE from medical, or pharmaceutical related companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Close My Account, Robinhood</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2019/07/12/close-my-account-robinhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 18:23:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2019/07/12/close-my-account-robinhood/</guid>
      <description>On 23 April, 2019 I sent an email to Robinhood, using their online help tool, because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a phone number to call on their website.
 Couldn&amp;rsquo;t find […] a proper choice under &amp;ldquo;support issue,&amp;rdquo; so picked something that is close to what I want, but not quite. I would like to close, and delete my account (not just deactivate). Thanks!
 The reply promptly arrived the same day, stating, along other things:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Sorry I Was Late</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2019/04/25/i-am-sorry-i-was-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 18:38:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2019/04/25/i-am-sorry-i-was-late/</guid>
      <description>I can explain why I was so late, I swear.
I woke up this morning after a brilliant two hours of sleep and went to milk the cow. She did not really have much, so the cereal kinda blew. Anyways, as I turned on my red 1993 Chevy Malibu I realised the garage was not opening. Great, the power was down! I went upstairs with a broom and woke up the hamster, which must have fallen asleep on the job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Friend</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2019/02/11/my-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 20:22:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2019/02/11/my-friend/</guid>
      <description>Friends are not easy to come by. They are made, just like good wine, after many years of ageing. At a certain point, which is hard to pinpoint, they cease to be just friends to become family. Just like a family member would, and should, they give you the best advise, uncompromisingly, unabashedly, unreservedly. They praise your virtues and take pride on them, but are quick to call out the stupid things you are bound to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Happiness?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/08/24/what-is-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:54:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/08/24/what-is-happiness/</guid>
      <description>After questioning myself on the meaning of life &amp;mdash; something I still do, by the way &amp;mdash; I long settled that, regardless of what it might be, living a happy life and aiming to be happy is what life is all about. Happiness, though, isn&amp;rsquo;t a fixed thing. Just like the many avatars of gods, their many incarnations, happiness comes from many sources, and is often found in subtle contexts throughout life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Someone Is in Trouble When...</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/25/someone-is-in-trouble-when.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 18:02:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/25/someone-is-in-trouble-when.../</guid>
      <description>You know a company is in trouble when they have to take a full page advertisement on several major newspapers in the U.S., and the U.K., with an apology from their chief. Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Mark Zuckerberg did just that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplicity</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/22/simplicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:34:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/22/simplicity/</guid>
      <description>That is a screenshot of my macOS desktop. It could be simpler, but as it is it does what I need, and want. When I need to use an app, I simply hit command (⌘) space and start typing the app name to launch it. That is, I use Spotlight.
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great that iOS could be customized like that too? Preferably it would be a setting, that would allow to turn off the visibility of all, or any app on the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Meltdown</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/another-meltdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 21:19:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/another-meltdown/</guid>
      <description>Someone is having another meltdown.
 The Mueller probe should never have been started in that there was no collusion and there was no crime. It was based on fraudulent activities and a Fake Dossier paid for by Crooked Hillary and the DNC, and improperly used in FISA COURT for surveillance of my campaign. WITCH HUNT!
 😂
Now, there is a background for his latest fit.
Yesterday, 16 March, Jeff Sessions fired Andrew McCabe, the FBI deputy director.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flowers Will Follow</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/flowers-will-follow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 18:17:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/flowers-will-follow/</guid>
      <description>To the untrained, this image will have little meaning. Who could imagine that those &amp;ldquo;ugly sticks,&amp;rdquo; as the child called them, will soon bloom into hundreds of beautiful yellow flowers? Yet, as it has happened each year, flowers will follow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching for The Car</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/searching-for-the-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 17:15:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/searching-for-the-car/</guid>
      <description>A year ago, Kent got his learner&amp;rsquo;s permit. With the help of John, and a little from me, he practiced driving for over 250 hours. A year later — more or less — on 9 March, he got his driver&amp;rsquo;s license, passing the practical test with a 96, out of 100 points, score. And so the asking for a car began.
What car should we get for a 17 year old?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adrian Lamo Has Died</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/16/adrian-lamo-has-died/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:53:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/16/adrian-lamo-has-died/</guid>
      <description>Adrian Lamo, mostly known as the hacker who broke into several major companies computer networks, and indirectly reported Chelsea Manning, has died — cause unknown thus far. The news was posted on Hacker News, of course, and I found one the comments — true or not — left there interesting.
 I had a car, while my friend did not, and Adrian had traveled via transit, so I spent the day with them hopping around town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Goes After Trump Org</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/15/mueller-goes-after-trump-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 19:50:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/15/mueller-goes-after-trump-org/</guid>
      <description>I have disliked other presidents in the past, for actions taken while they were in the office that I — and many others — considered stupid, crazy, or just plain wrong. My dislike for the current president eclipses any of my previous. I voted for Hillary, and wrongly predicted that she would win the presidency.
Today news, although perhaps inconsequential, brings joy to an otherwise political nightmare.
 The special counsel, Robert S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Market for a Camera</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/04/on-the-market-for-a-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 21:12:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/04/on-the-market-for-a-camera/</guid>
      <description>We have gone through quite a few cameras. The very first one we recall was a Canon EOS D30, with an amazing 3.2 megapixel &amp;mdash; sarcasm aside, it took amazing photos. After that we had had many Sony Cyber-shots, a Canon Powershot A640, a couple of Canon Powershot Gs, and another bigger Canon, the EOS 6D. In between we have used the camera that comes with the iPhones, starting with the iPhone 2G.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Impermanence of Things</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/01/21/about-the-impermanence-of-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 11:13:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/01/21/about-the-impermanence-of-things/</guid>
      <description>Thinking about the impermanence of things is a reoccurring theme for me. It usually happens if I get mad at something I don&amp;rsquo;t like, which used to be quite often no long ago. I still notice situations that are less than desirable for my point of view, but I no longer get mad every single time. I am trying my very best not to get upset for anything, or with anyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandfather has left us</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/01/13/grandfather-has-left-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 14:40:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/01/13/grandfather-has-left-us/</guid>
      <description>Grandfather died today.
Kim was very close to him because she lived with her grandparents since she was young, until we got married. Back in Vietnam, when she was in elementary school, grandpa took her and her siblings to school, and picked them up in his bicycle every day. He was more than a grandfather to her. He was, throughout her life, a father figure.
Grandpa was a soft spoken man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unalloyed irony</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/12/08/unalloyed-irony/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 13:14:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/12/08/unalloyed-irony/</guid>
      <description>Soon to be ex-Senator Al Franken announced, on an emotional speech, his resignation yesterday. He is leaving the Senate after been accused of sexual misconduct.
 &amp;ldquo;I, of all people, am aware that there is some irony in the fact that I am leaving while a man who has bragged on tape about his history of sexual assault sits in the Oval Office, and a man who has repeatedly preyed on young girls campaigns for the Senate with the full support of his party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On AT&amp;T fibre</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/10/08/att-fibre/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 12:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/10/08/att-fibre/</guid>
      <description>Had to chat with an AT&amp;amp;T employee, as a result of an order I placed yesterday. This is the feedback I left (with minor spelling corrections), after concluding the chat:
 The chat experience was excellent (chat agent, Marry). AT&amp;amp;T experience thus far, not quite so.
I had an AT&amp;amp;T sales agent visit me yesterday. I signed up for Internet 1Gbps (Internet 1000 on AT&amp;amp;T lingo), and phone service (transferring my current number).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A downright moron</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/10/05/a-downright-moron/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 05:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/10/05/a-downright-moron/</guid>
      <description>Henry Louis Mencken wrote an article on the Baltimore Sun, on 26 July, 1920, that amongst other things read:
 As democracy is perfected, the office represents, more and more closely, the inner soul of the people. We move toward a lofty ideal. On some great and glorious day the plain folks of the land will reach their heart&amp;rsquo;s desire at last, and the White House will be adorned by a downright moron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Uber Affair</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/06/06/the-uber-affair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 11:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/06/06/the-uber-affair/</guid>
      <description>Using Uber for the first time, in France, was a delightful experience. We were able to summon a relatively cheap minivan within minutes, the drivers were nice, nothing found to complain. Then, once back home, I decided that I might want to occasionally drive for Uber, for fun. That is when the real affair started.
To begin with, the rider photo I had on my profile no longer met their requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comey Sacking</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/05/11/comey-sacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 16:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/05/11/comey-sacking/</guid>
      <description>This is, at least for me, completely surreal. It is not only that Trump sacked the FBI director &amp;mdash; who arguably helped him getting elected President &amp;mdash; while he was conducting an investigation on Trump&amp;rsquo;s presidential campaign, but the way he wrote the sacking letter (I emphasised):
 Dear Director Comey:
I have received the attached letters from the Attorney General and Deputy Attorney General of the United States recommending your dismissal as the Director of the Federal Bureau of Investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A few technical changes</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/03/05/a-few-technical-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 19:28:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/03/05/a-few-technical-changes/</guid>
      <description>A few things have happened on my current server setup. The biggest one was my move from FreeBSD to Ubuntu. I do not have complains about FreeBSD &amp;mdash; how could I? &amp;mdash; but I wanted to play with more recent stuff, and it was becoming very hard to do under BSD. I also wanted a refresh, since I had been running that VPS for a while and it was starting to feel &amp;ldquo;dirty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Intelligent Person</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/27/an-intelligent-person/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 19:59:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/27/an-intelligent-person/</guid>
      <description>From Twitter:
 The most amazing thing about the Trump presidency is that it’s made GWB look like a reasonably intelligent person.
&amp;mdash; Derek Powazek (@fraying) February 27, 2017
 And from The New York Times:
 Former President George W. Bush said Monday &amp;ldquo;we all need answers&amp;rdquo; on the extent of contact between President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s team and the Russian government, and didn&amp;rsquo;t rule out the idea that a special prosecutor could be necessary to lead an investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Silence of the Hacks</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/18/the-silence-of-the-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 21:32:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/18/the-silence-of-the-hacks/</guid>
      <description>There is a reason why I subscribed to the digital edition of The New York Times. Its journalists are superb; it is a paper I trust, and have found to be veridical after cross referencing the news they post with other major, equally trusted, news sources.
From yesterday&amp;rsquo;s edition (some emphasis mine):
 The story so far: A foreign dictator intervened on behalf of a U.S. presidential candidate — and that candidate won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incapable of Serving</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/14/incapable-of-serving/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 05:49:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/14/incapable-of-serving/</guid>
      <description>From the opinion pages of The New York Times yesterday, 13 of February, 2017, also appearing in print today. Some emphasis mine.
 Mr. Trump’s speech and actions demonstrate an inability to tolerate views different from his own, leading to rage reactions. His words and behavior suggest a profound inability to empathize. Individuals with these traits distort reality to suit their psychological state, attacking facts and those who convey them (journalists, scientists).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning the plate</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/12/cleaning-the-plate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 11:04:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/12/cleaning-the-plate/</guid>
      <description>My wife has always told me, &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t eat everything in your plate, leave something!&amp;rdquo; It is her believe, and her culture&amp;rsquo;s, that only poor people eats everything, and that if I do so, it will show I am dying of hunger, and thus, poor. If it were so, what&amp;rsquo;s wrong with being poor? Why will I leave food on the plate, food that I really like, to pretend what I am not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake Email Clients</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/11/fake-email-clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 21:06:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/11/fake-email-clients/</guid>
      <description>For a few (years?) now, there has been an increase of so called email clients that are not so. I am talking about the &amp;ldquo;value added email clients&amp;rdquo; that require a third party server/service to work. Within that category there is Nylas, Polymail, and Sparkmail, to mention a few. Although they bring an array of features not normally found on an email client, they are worthless if the third party company server(s) goes down, or have problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard to Believe</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/09/hard-to-believe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 14:30:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/09/hard-to-believe/</guid>
      <description>If you hear or read this somewhere else &amp;mdash; whether on social media, or via your clueless uncle Olaf &amp;mdash; you will find it hard, if not impossible, to believe. Now, finding it on Reuters is a different story.
 In his first call as president with Russian leader Vladimir Putin, Donald Trump denounced a treaty that caps U.S. and Russian deployment of nuclear warheads as a bad deal for the United States, according to two U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unpresidential</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/01/12/unpresidential/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 20:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/01/12/unpresidential/</guid>
      <description>Not presidential at all.
 “President-elect Donald J. Trump’s aides often cite his appearances at professional wrestling matches as an inspiration for his outsize political speaking style, and his buoyantly belligerent news conference in New York on Wednesday proved he has no plans to betray his brawler’s roots in the service of seeming more presidential.”
&amp;mdash; New York Times
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warming up to Emoji</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/01/08/warming-up-to-emoji/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 19:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/01/08/warming-up-to-emoji/</guid>
      <description>No long ago I wrote that I loathed Emoji. My main grumble was their usage abuse, and, especially, the overuse of &amp;ldquo;smilies.&amp;rdquo;
Since Apple&amp;rsquo;s iOS 10, I have been warming up to them, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t until I came across Mu-An that they really started to captivate me. She uses them, sparingly, but with such taste! A few of her repositories exclusively deal with Emoji as well. Thus, this post is to correct myself: I don&amp;rsquo;t loathe Emoji.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I was wrong</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/11/09/i-was-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/11/09/i-was-wrong/</guid>
      <description>Back in October 5th, 2015, I wrote a prediction, which I saved in a file for which I posted a hash. I predicted that Hillary Clinton would win the United States presidential elections. Sadly, I was wrong.
I really do not have much else to say. I am sorry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What have you taught me?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/10/29/what-have-you-taught-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/10/29/what-have-you-taught-me/</guid>
      <description>His father was only giving him a small advise, worried for him. Parents worry too much, sometimes. It was not taken well.
“You suffocate me, don’t worry so much about me! Enough advise, what have you taught me, until now?” He asks. Perhaps no much, the father thinks in retrospect. Brushing the teeth, maybe? Lacing the shoes? How to clean the arse? How to respect others, and do good? To be happy, love, study hard, work hard?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders keeps fighting</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/06/09/bernie-sanders-keeps-fighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/06/09/bernie-sanders-keeps-fighting/</guid>
      <description>Bernie Sanders has had a good run. Yet numbers are pilled against him, and he should know it. After all he said he was &amp;ldquo;pretty good in arithmetic.&amp;rdquo; Hillary has beaten him, and the right and honorable thing for him to do is to call it quits.
 “If, on November 8th of this year, Hillary Clinton is elected President, we will have only begun to fight,” Sanders told a packed rally in San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Violin Lessons</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/04/29/violin-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/04/29/violin-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Just as they started, randomly, on a whim, as a child desire to learn to play the violin, the lessons that Kent has been taking for almost two years came to an end two weeks ago. It was hard to tell Julie &amp;mdash; his teacher &amp;mdash; that he was not to continue, but it was what he wanted.
Kent never intended to play violin professionally, it was no more than an artistic hobby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Dangerous Precedent</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/02/17/a-dangerous-precedent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/02/17/a-dangerous-precedent/</guid>
      <description>The United States government demanded that Apple weakens the security on iOS. Tim Cook, Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, replied.
 Rather than asking for legislative action through Congress, the FBI is proposing an unprecedented use of the All Writs Act of 1789 to justify an expansion of its authority.
The government would have us remove security features and add new capabilities to the operating system, allowing a passcode to be input electronically. This would make it easier to unlock an iPhone by “brute force,” trying thousands or millions of combinations with the speed of a modern computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Alone</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/12/17/home-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/12/17/home-alone/</guid>
      <description>Just like I did on July 18, 2014, this one is mostly for keeping a record of a first time activity or occasion. This time it was Kent&amp;rsquo;s first home alone day. He is almost 15 years old, and for the first time he spent eight hours home alone, while Kim and I were at work.
Happy &amp;ldquo;graduation&amp;rdquo; step, Kent!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Cloud Drive Feedback</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/11/12/amazon-cloud-drive-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/11/12/amazon-cloud-drive-feedback/</guid>
      <description>This is not merely a technical problem, but I did not have the choice for multiple selections. Anytime I use the word &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; down below, I mean Amazon.
First the good. I love you, I have used AWS S3 for a long time, no complains. I do much of my online purchases on you, although I am not a fervent shopper. I rent my movies on Amazon Video. I am signed up for Flex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Parenting killing Marriage</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/11/08/american-parenting-killing-marriage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/11/08/american-parenting-killing-marriage/</guid>
      <description>This article sounds very true, although I would not go as far as generalizing it for all Americans.
 Mothers must devote themselves to their children above anyone or anything else, but many wives would be offended if their husbands said, “You’re pretty great, but my love for you will never hold a candle to the love I have for John Junior.”
Mothers are also holy in a way that fathers are not expected to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumping Dollars Left and Right</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/11/02/dumping-dollars-left-and-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/11/02/dumping-dollars-left-and-right/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;DOD charged the American taxpayer $43 million for what is likely the world&amp;rsquo;s most expensive gas station.&amp;rdquo;
That&amp;rsquo;s what Special Inspector General John F. Sopko found when he looked at the construction of a natural gas station in Sheberghan, Afghanistan.
According to the report, at most that station should have cost about $500,000. But in this case, the Department of Defense&amp;rsquo;s Task Force for Stability and Business Operations awarded Central Asian Engineering a contract to build the station for a little under $3 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard and Daylight Savings Time</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/11/01/standard-and-daylight-savings-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/11/01/standard-and-daylight-savings-time/</guid>
      <description>Standard Time. When I was a child, an old lady I loved as my own grandmother used to tell me this time was &amp;ldquo;God&amp;rsquo;s time,&amp;rdquo; and that she never changed clocks when everyone else switched to &amp;ldquo;Daylight Savings Time.&amp;rdquo; I wish I could do the same, unfortunately I am not old enough not to care.
I am part of the growing group that believes DST (or time changing of any kind) is worthless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Two Child Policy</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/29/chinas-two-child-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/29/chinas-two-child-policy/</guid>
      <description>This one is worth documenting, as it doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen every day. As a matter of fact, it hasn&amp;rsquo;t happened for over three decades.
 &amp;ldquo;It is the latest twist in the most ambitious and ruthless social-engineering program ever undertaken by a modern state: Beijing announced Thursday that the Chinese Communist Party will officially abandon its one-child policy. Yet it has no plans to relinquish authority over its subjects’ birth patterns; rather, Beijing has simply changed the ration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Red Bus</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/22/big-red-bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/22/big-red-bus/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Hi guys, don&amp;rsquo;t forget to donate today!&amp;rdquo; says the lady with the oneblood.org t-shirt. The Big Red Bus parks on campus often, sometimes they seem to be here every day. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ll give you a t-shirt and a cookie!&amp;rdquo; She says. That&amp;rsquo;s the price of your donation, but is it?
A typical pint of blood costs $130-150, and sometimes even more. A lucrative business, don&amp;rsquo;t you agree? Yet, oneblood.org is non-profit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple on Encryption</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/21/apple-on-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/21/apple-on-encryption/</guid>
      <description>Apple mobile devices&amp;mdash;iPhones, iPads, iPods&amp;mdash;are used everywhere. The US smartphone subscriber market share highest percentage is dominated by them. As an American company, they are bound to comply with U.S. laws and regulations. So, when the U.S. Justice Department requested that Apple grants access to a locked iPhone, Apple brought the case to court.
 Apple Inc told a U.S. judge that accessing data stored on a locked iPhone would be &amp;ldquo;impossible&amp;rdquo; with devices using its latest operating system, but the company has the &amp;ldquo;technical ability&amp;rdquo; to help law enforcement unlock older phones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking and using the Phone</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/21/walking-and-using-the-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/21/walking-and-using-the-phone/</guid>
      <description>Walking around with your head stuck on the phone is like playing the chicken game. The fully aware pedestrian walking in your opposite direction&amp;mdash;and on the same path&amp;mdash;is forced to play the game. Not as dangerous as driving but still very annoying. When you walk, please pay attention, look where you are walking, and leave the phone in your pocket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neighbors</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/20/neighbors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/20/neighbors/</guid>
      <description>Our neighbors are moving. The ones on the left, that is. They have been our neighbors for fifteen years, and lived here for seventeen, since the community was built. Quiet neighbors, the best kind. Now we roll the dice, and hope for the best, for whoever comes next.
The house on the right has had three owners; we have known them all. The first were the previous owners of our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reminders</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/19/reminders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/19/reminders/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;What did you have for lunch?,&amp;rdquo; the father asks while driving home. &amp;ldquo;Same as usual,&amp;rdquo; he replies. &amp;ldquo;And that is?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I just eat random sandwiches of what comes to whim.&amp;rdquo; The father processes that for a bit. &amp;ldquo;I see.&amp;rdquo; Later, at home, &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s there for homework today?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;No much,&amp;rdquo; he says. &amp;ldquo;Brush your teeth,&amp;rdquo; he is reminded. Later, in the evening. &amp;ldquo;Take a shower.&amp;rdquo; A few times.
Just before the father goes to sleep, and sees his bedroom lights on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP Classes</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/16/ap-classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/16/ap-classes/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday (15 October) Kent told me he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to take AP (Advanced Placement) classes next year. He also told me he might not want to be a neurological surgeon after all, and that he really doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what he will want to be, professionally. We talked more, but the rest of it has no place in here.
Amongst the many feelings I am experiencing, regret is one of them. If only my parents were alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backing up and Restoring GPG Keys</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/13/backing-up-and-restoring-gpg-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/13/backing-up-and-restoring-gpg-keys/</guid>
      <description>If you use GPG to occasionally encrypt and/or sign your email, or to encrypt your files before placing them on the cloud, you will understand how important it is to have a backup of your GPG keys. Similarly important will be to know how to restore them as well.
Backing up your keys and configuration files To back your private, and public keys, as well as your trust database, you will do1:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Office Slave Manual</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/11/good-office-slave-manual/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/11/good-office-slave-manual/</guid>
      <description>Yegor Bugayenko has a few tips&amp;mdash;a short manual, per se&amp;mdash;to help us be good office slaves.
 Don&amp;rsquo;t Nag. No matter what is happening, you should never criticize your direct manager. The boss is always right. Everything else may be wrong — the situation, colleagues, suppliers, computers, the CEO, investors, the market, or the weather, but not the boss you directly report to. The word of this person is the law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enticement</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/10/enticement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/10/enticement/</guid>
      <description>Someone decided to entice us to fill out a survey, by sending us a &amp;ldquo;lucky&amp;rdquo; two dollars bill with it. Normally we do not fill out any type of surveys, unless proper remuneration is provided. Two dollars isn&amp;rsquo;t really worth the effort, and normally would not be accepted as a fee. Yet, since there is no way to send it back with assurances it will reach the original sender, we have a small dilemma on hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Martian</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/10/the-martian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/10/the-martian/</guid>
      <description>We just came from seeing the movie &amp;ldquo;The Martian.&amp;rdquo; Minus the obvious, very predictable, Hollywood scenes, the movie was quite alright. It made me wish I could live to see the first few missions to the Red Planet. Being the selfless guy that I am, thought, I would be willing to settle if my child gets to see them instead.
While on the topic of movies, and theaters, it is amazing how expensive it is to see a movie these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russians and Syria</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/08/russians-and-syria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/08/russians-and-syria/</guid>
      <description>We bomb. From the air, from the ground, from afar, from ships. And so do the Russians now. We target what we believe are terrorists, sometimes we miss. Russians are doing the same now.
We removed Saddam, and the Taliban, just to mention two, and that created&amp;mdash;or increased&amp;mdash;a mess that continues until today. The Russian&amp;rsquo;s tactic is different, they are targeting both, the terrorists fighting against the &amp;ldquo;official&amp;rdquo; regime, and those which we are targeting as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of no Use</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/of-no-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/of-no-use/</guid>
      <description>A farmer got so old that he couldn&amp;rsquo;t work the fields anymore. So he would spend the day just sitting on the porch. His son, still working the farm, would look up from time to time and see his father sitting there.
&amp;ldquo;He&amp;rsquo;s of no use any more,&amp;rdquo; the son thought to himself, &amp;ldquo;he doesn&amp;rsquo;t do anything!&amp;ldquo;
One day the son got so frustrated by this, that he built a wood coffin, dragged it over to the porch, and told his father to get in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/prediction/</guid>
      <description>Next year we will have our Presidential Elections. Everyone knows that, of course, because the politicians have been campaining for almost a year now.
Below is the name of a file with my winner&amp;rsquo;s prediction on the United States 2016 Presidential Elections written on it. It is a hash algorithm of a file containing a sentence with my prediction. I will refer to this post the day after elections, as the results are known.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space for the Dead</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/space-for-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/space-for-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>I read an article today on The Guardian, which showed up on the eight page of Hacker’s News. It talks about the lack of space for the dead, in the world of the living.
 &amp;ldquo;Some 55 million people are reckoned to pass away each year (about 0.8% of the planet’s total population – equivalent to 100% of England’s). Yet urban planners and developers focus overwhelmingly on accommodating and making money from the living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tempus Fugit</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/tempus-fugit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/tempus-fugit/</guid>
      <description>Time seems to be passing by too fast. Way too fast.
A week starts and then it is over when I blink. Same applies to weekends. It used to be that time seemed to pass quick only when engaged in something. Lately it is the same, whether I am busy or not. I am afraid I will blink again, and I will be gone.
Amongst the many things we can’t control, time is the one that hurts the most, especially as we grow older.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On a Rock</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/01/on-a-rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/01/on-a-rock/</guid>
      <description>From our last vacation&amp;mdash;which occurred four months ago&amp;mdash;to Colorado. This one was taken somewhere around Pikes Peak. Kent was daring, and Kim was afraid. I took the photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disappointing</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/30/disappointing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/30/disappointing/</guid>
      <description>Pope Francis &amp;ldquo;thanked her for her courage&amp;rdquo; and told her to &amp;ldquo;stay strong&amp;rdquo;, Mr. Stavers said.
&amp;mdash; BBC News
 If this truly happened, it is disappointing. A person as charismatic as Pope Francis, who has been so politically careful, should have known better. She is a government employee, fulfilling an official task. She must abide the law, or simply leave her job, if she can&amp;rsquo;t perform as expected. What would we do if our troops, due to their religious beliefs, decide to put down their weapons?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presidential Elections 2016</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/27/presidential-elections-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/27/presidential-elections-2016/</guid>
      <description>Back in 2011 was the last time I wrote about Presidential Elections (2012). I can&amp;rsquo;t believe we are about to get into them again. In 2012 I knew exactly who to vote for, but in 2016, with the selection we have thus far, I really have no idea about who is the most viable&amp;mdash;if there is one. Certainly not this one:
 Question: &amp;ldquo;How will you bring back the American Dream?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/26/saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/26/saturday/</guid>
      <description>Respect others, seek peace, do not be irascible. Give, help, construct; never the opposite. Turn lemons into lemonade. Hard things to do, most of the time, even more so all the time. We are so recalcitrant by nature!
Yet, our existence would be idyllic if we could manage to, at least, try to do all of the above often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glowforge</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/24/glowforge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/24/glowforge/</guid>
      <description> We all need this. Watch the video and tell me if you do not feel amazed. It is pricey, but oh the fun one could have with one of those!
 Glowforge is a wireless 3D laser printer that fits on your desktop, works with your favorite design programs, and stores your designs &amp;amp; data on a cloud.
&amp;mdash; What is Glowforge?
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selling Out</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/24/selling-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/24/selling-out/</guid>
      <description>It seems iOS 9 ad blocker, Crystal, will allow some ads to go through for a fee. From an article on the Wall Street Journal:
 Mr. Murphy said he has taken Eyeo up on its offer, and plans to implement an option within his app whereby “acceptable” ads will be displayed to users. The feature will be switched on by default, Mr. Murphy said, and he will receive a flat monthly fee from Eyeo in return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumnal Equinox</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/23/autumnal-equinox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/23/autumnal-equinox/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the beginning of one of my two favorite seasons, Autumn&amp;mdash;or Fall, as it is commonly called in the United States. Living in Florida makes the season a very, very mild one, with temperatures still quite high (it will be 90&amp;deg;F today), yet it brings the solid certainty that summer is being left behind.
Join me on celebrating the Autumnal Equinox today, at 04:21 US Eastern time, which is 08:21 UTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Francis</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/22/protecting-francis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/22/protecting-francis/</guid>
      <description>The Pope has recently been to Cuba, and today he will be arriving to the United States. Like any other dignitary, the Pope needs protection from both, bad people, and adoring crowds. Yet, doing so is not easy feat.
 “The crowds throw things,” Mr. Clancy, who took over as the head of the Secret Service last October, said in an interview. “They throw flags, dolls and, obviously, babies towards him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shogi</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/20/shogi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/20/shogi/</guid>
      <description>Kent&amp;rsquo;s latest hobby is to play Shogi. That makes me an obligatory player and fan as well since, just like chess, Shogi requires two players. We bought a cheap board from Amazon, but he has already stated that a better quality board and pieces is what he would want for Christmas (yes, he is already planning for it).
The game isn&amp;rsquo;t difficult to play, but I am having an excruciating hard time remembering each piece — labeled with kanji characters — and how they move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/19/microsoft-studio-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/19/microsoft-studio-code/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft launched its free (non open source), cross-platform, code editor early this year (April, 2015), at its Build Developer Conference.
I have been tempted to try it, as I read its file comparison is very nice, its intelliSense, and it&amp;rsquo;s based on the same platform as Atom, which I happen to love. Today was the day, but as you can see, it is a non-signed OS X application. Microsoft is big enough, and rich enough to afford signing their OS X applications, but they chose not to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Loathe Emoji</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/18/i-loathe-emoji/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/18/i-loathe-emoji/</guid>
      <description>I despise Emoji and emoticons, specially graphical emoji, or people who continuously abuse them, and interject them in every single sentence they type, sometimes even more than once. I thought that I hated &amp;ldquo;LOL,&amp;rdquo; which I do, but I would rather see LOL &amp;mdash; when justified, not the moronic &amp;ldquo;LOL&amp;rdquo; without reason you see often &amp;mdash; than see the utter idiotic smiles, winks, etc., continuously, all the time. &amp;ldquo;I am an elitist asshole, but here, have an Emoji!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Living to 200 Years Old</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/16/secrets-of-living-to-200-years-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/16/secrets-of-living-to-200-years-old/</guid>
      <description>This article refers to aging as not being an inevitable fact of life. It goes to describe the marvelous capabilities that some animals have to live, seemingly, forever. Yet, do we really want to? With all the problems we are having with over population, do we want to pursue the holy grail, and extend life to last hundreds?
We have already &amp;ldquo;extended&amp;rdquo; our lives considerably, taking into account that in 1950 the world average on life expectancy was 48 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the removal of Garbage Apps</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/15/about-the-removal-of-garbage-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/15/about-the-removal-of-garbage-apps/</guid>
      <description>Tim Cook answered a few questions for BuzzFeed, while they talked about things iPhone, iPad Pro, and many other Apple&amp;ndash;related things. This part got close to me, as I am sure it might be to anyone who likes iPhones. Why can&amp;rsquo;t we remove certain apps?
 Why are there apps on the iOS that I can’t delete even though I never use them? Why does Apple insist that I keep Tips and Stocks”on my iPhone when I’d like nothing more than to delete them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never-ending Homework</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/14/neverending-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/14/neverending-homework/</guid>
      <description>Ever since Kent started the 9th grade he has been having to do an unusual amount, and I mean really unusual, of homework. I might be getting too old, but I do not recall having to do that much, so early into high school. It is really messing up his sleeping schedule, and&amp;ndash;kind of&amp;ndash;mine.
Going to sleep really late each day, and waking up when sun still sleeps is wearing me out too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huckabee offers his Support</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/02/huckabee-offers-his-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/02/huckabee-offers-his-support/</guid>
      <description>Mike Huckabee, a christian pastor turned politician has offered his support to the Court clerk in Kentucky who, against Supreme Court order, refuses to issue gay marriage licenses.
 &amp;ldquo;I spoke with Kim Davis this morning to offer my prayers and support. I let her know how proud I am of her for not abandoning her religious convictions and standing strong for religious liberty. She is showing more courage and humility than just about any federal office holder in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jekyll and Git</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/08/29/jekyll-and-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 14:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/08/29/jekyll-and-git/</guid>
      <description>I have been using Jekyll for a while now, but all this time I have been generating it on the server, That is, I had had a directory on the server holding the Jekyll files, in which I would run jekyll build to generate the website. Not too streamlined.
Before hosting this weblog on Vultr, I had it on GitHub, and their Pages would do the publishing for me, right after a commit, which was great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Atom</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/08/29/using-atom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/08/29/using-atom/</guid>
      <description>I have used many editors in the past, either under Windows or OS X. Too many, I have really lost the count. The last one I used was Sublime Text. Great editor, cross platform too, but pricey. Each time I would get the nag, I would feel guilty for not buying me a licensed copy.
I tried Atom when it first came out. It was buggy and slow, really, really slow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me, but you, but me</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/28/me-but-you-but-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/28/me-but-you-but-me/</guid>
      <description>On May 28, 2010, Mark Pilgrim wrote the entry below on his weblog. He has since long been gone, but I am keeping this entry, named &amp;ldquo;Me, but you, but me,&amp;rdquo; which I liked very much. I really wish he would come back.
I’ve been active online for 9 years now. With one exception, nothing I’ve done online has brought me closer to making 25-year friends. Life online rewards breadth, not depth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail.app on iOS</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/16/gmail-app-on-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/16/gmail-app-on-ios/</guid>
      <description>I like Google and its services. Like is too little, I love them! Their mobile applications on the other hand &amp;mdash; specifically those running under iOS &amp;mdash; are horrible. The UIX is confusing and it does not follows Apple UIX design. Their choice of font is of poor taste and, again, does not match the rest of the OS. They lack of functionality and/or their functionality is limited by poor choices and, what is seems to be, a lack of common sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The very last of Something</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/14/the-very-last-of-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/14/the-very-last-of-something/</guid>
      <description>There hasn&amp;rsquo;t been an article like this for a while, that fills me with such feeling of sadness, and emptiness. For as long as I can remember, a cartoon I saw as a child started my attraction for rhinoceros. Such lovely animals!
And now, the one pictured above (CB2/ZOB/Brent Stirton/National Geographic) is the last of his kind. Who do we have to thank for that? Us. On a comment to the article, a poster under a &amp;ldquo;Gordo Granudo&amp;rdquo; pseudonym writes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Beat a Polygraph Test</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/03/how-to-beat-a-polygraph-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/03/how-to-beat-a-polygraph-test/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;He used to advise trainees to clench their anus but has since concluded that terrifying mental imagery works better.&amp;rdquo;
 When you get a control question, which is more general, envision the scariest thing you can in order to trigger physiological distress; the polygraph&amp;rsquo;s tubes around your chest measure breathing, the arm cuff monitors heart rate and electrodes attached to you fingertips detect perspiration. What is your greatest fear? Falling? Drowning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iCloud mess</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/02/icloud-mess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/02/icloud-mess/</guid>
      <description>Having lost many photos of certain sentimental value a few years ago has made me paranoid. Ever since I lost my child&amp;rsquo;s first four years of photographic memory I have kept copies of our family photos and videos in two different places. I keep a copy of photos and videos in our Synology NAS at home, which backup photos to Amazon S3 and videos to Glacier.
When Apple announced their iCloud plans, and the ability to keep my entire photo library on the cloud, I was one of the first to sign up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding little to talk about</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/03/30/little-to-talk-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/03/30/little-to-talk-about/</guid>
      <description>The main problem with Jekyll is that is out of the way. Unlike other weblog engines, which are managed via the web, I come to the shell to type and process this. Perhaps I need to research a better workflow?
 I am finding little to talk about lately, and that is keeping things here rather quiet. It is not only that I do not have much to write, but that when the desire arrives it gets lost in translation, mostly because of the way I have decided to handle this little space of mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy 2015!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/12/31/happy-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/12/31/happy-2015/</guid>
      <description>Here we go again. Not complaining, as there is nothing to complain about. Just another year. It seems 2014 flew by quite fast, will you agree? Nevertheless, happy 2015 everyone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iCloud Drive on standby</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/11/13/icloud-drive-on-standby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/11/13/icloud-drive-on-standby/</guid>
      <description>When Apple announced the iCloud Drive integration in Yosemite, I got really excited. As I was already part of the &amp;ldquo;Apple ecosystem&amp;rdquo; (iPhone, iPad, iMac), the iCloud Drive availability in all, specially on the desktop, seemed like the culmination of all my dreams: a Cloud to rule them all. I ordered the 200 GB for $4 a month right away.
As it turns out with products in infancy, the iCloud Drive is no yet mature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where are you from?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/07/30/where-are-you-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/07/30/where-are-you-from/</guid>
      <description>In the States, looking different and/or having an accent will get you asked &amp;ldquo;Where are you from?&amp;rdquo; It doesn&amp;rsquo;t fail, it happens all the time.
Why are we so concerned about knowing someone&amp;rsquo;s country of origin? What difference does it make? If anything, it might be a knowledge we do not want to have. Knowing from where someone is from might spark stereotypical comments and behaviors that would jeopardize an otherwise perfect encounter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Braces</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/07/18/on-braces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/07/18/on-braces/</guid>
      <description>This is mainly for our records. Today Kent got his braces on, and thus it begins a few months of uncomfortable chewing, special diet, fastidious brushing and everything else that comes with braces.
Now I must go to sell some blood, and place one of my kidneys for sale on the black market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft and Global Cybercrime</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/07/01/microsoft-and-global-cybercrime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/07/01/microsoft-and-global-cybercrime/</guid>
      <description>From The Official Microsoft Blog:
 On June 19, Microsoft filed for an ex parte temporary restraining order (TRO) from the U.S. District Court for Nevada against No-IP. On June 26, the court granted our request and made Microsoft the DNS authority for the company’s 23 free No-IP domains, allowing us to identify and route all known bad traffic to the Microsoft sinkhole and classify the identified threats.
 Microsoft granted rights to take control of another business&amp;rsquo; DNS, to &amp;ldquo;identify and route&amp;rdquo; bad traffic?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moved to a Droplet</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/06/29/moved-to-a-droplet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/06/29/moved-to-a-droplet/</guid>
      <description>Having wished for a while to run this little site on SSL &amp;mdash;as well as having the freedom to do more things&amp;mdash; which GitHub does not allow, I have finally decided to move to a virtual server of my own. At $5 a month per droplet, DigitalOcean was the provider of choice.
DigitalOcean droplets web interface is very clean, simple, responsive and functional. Spawning the server took 54 seconds, and configuring nginx took 15 minutes, SSL included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Backup</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/06/28/cloud-backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/06/28/cloud-backup/</guid>
      <description>I have a NAS at home, a Synology DS411J, which we use for backups, and to keep our family photos and videos. It works great, no complains here, but I am looking to keep an outside backup. A backup in the cloud, to be precise.
The choices are:
 Amazon Drive Amazon AWS S3 Google Drive Apple iCloud DropBox Microsoft OneDrive Any other?  I used to have Arqbackup, but it became unreliable, and I never liked the way it stored the files on AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four-Way Stop</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/02/19/four-way-stop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/02/19/four-way-stop/</guid>
      <description>Drivers in Orlando do not seem to know what to do when they reach a four way stop. It really makes me wonder how were they able to obtain a drivers license without that knowledge, as it is part of Drivers Handbook (search for &amp;ldquo;Stop Signs&amp;rdquo; on that page), the test, and occasionally encountered while driving.
For the record, and in case you live in Orlando, and do not know what to do on a four-way stop (also known as all-way stop), these are the basics:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Winter Morning Small Talk</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/cold-winter-morning-small-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/cold-winter-morning-small-talk/</guid>
      <description>We have 36 Fahrenheit degrees this morning (2.2&amp;deg; Celsius). That is mighty cold for almost-always warm, sunny Florida. I stressed it to my child yesternight: he must wear warm clothes the next day. Reluctantly he said &amp;ldquo;OK&amp;rdquo;.
Then comes this morning, and the iMessages exchange look like this:
  Child :  &amp;ldquo;Mama is trying to make me wear an incredibly uncomfortable shirt and is yelling like a siren.&amp;rdquo;   Me :  &amp;ldquo;Why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specialization is for Insects</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/specialization-is-for-insects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/specialization-is-for-insects/</guid>
      <description>From Robert Heinlein&amp;rsquo;s science fiction book, Time Enough for Love:
 &amp;ldquo;A human being should be able to change a diaper, plan an invasion, butcher a hog, conn a ship, design a building, write a sonnet, balance accounts, build a wall, set a bone, comfort the dying, take orders, give orders, cooperate, act alone, solve equations, analyze a new problem, pitch manure, program a computer, cook a tasty meal, fight efficiently, die gallantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sands of Time</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/04/the-sands-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/04/the-sands-of-time/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It is said that some lives are linked across time connected by an ancient calling that echoes through the ages. Destiny.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;mdash; Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time
 I do not believe on such thing as destiny, but the line above from the movie is certainly touching. The movie itself is quite nice. Last night we watched it for the fourth time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy MMXIV everyone!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/01/happy-mmxiv-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/01/happy-mmxiv-everyone/</guid>
      <description>Now that we have gone around the Sun one more time, we simply start doing it again. We don&amp;rsquo;t fool ourselves, it is not by choice. And with this new elliptical orbit we walk into age, which will lead, ultimately, to our demise. It is a simple concept.
Leaving the obvious behind, what&amp;rsquo;s left is to enjoy what we have. To try being nice to others, to the best of our abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is All around Us</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/29/it-is-all-around-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/29/it-is-all-around-us/</guid>
      <description>Love. It really is.
 &amp;ldquo;Whenever I get gloomy with the state of the world, I think about the arrivals gate at Heathrow Airport. General opinion&amp;rsquo;s starting to make out that we live in a world of hatred and greed, but I don&amp;rsquo;t see that. It seems to me that love is everywhere. Often it&amp;rsquo;s not particularly dignified or newsworthy, but it&amp;rsquo;s always there &amp;mdash; fathers and sons, mothers and daughters, husbands and wives, boyfriends, girlfriends, old friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joy of Reading Hemingway</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/27/the-joy-of-reading-hemingway/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/27/the-joy-of-reading-hemingway/</guid>
      <description>Recently, Kent had the misfortune of picking &amp;ldquo;A Moveable Feast&amp;rdquo;, by Ernest Hemingway, for a school assignment. I know I am not the right person1 to judge anyone&amp;rsquo;s writing style, I am simply recollecting the comments Kent has made while reading the book.
So far, other than finding the book boring &amp;mdash; mind it, he is barely 13 &amp;mdash; he is puzzled at the use of French terms that he wonders how would the &amp;ldquo;everyday&amp;rdquo; American reader comprehend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/it-is-christmas-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/it-is-christmas-day/</guid>
      <description>One of the many things to look forward to each year is, of course, the end of year holidays. Christmas, Festivus, or whatever you call it, the end of December is always a special time. My only complain, and that might be yours too, is that it comes and goes so fast! Kent has finished opening his presents, and somehow it feels &amp;ldquo;it is all over.&amp;rdquo; But we waited the whole year for this!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies to Watch during Christmas</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/movies-to-watch-during-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/movies-to-watch-during-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Christmas is not the same without watching certain movies. The ones that are always a must for me are &amp;ldquo;National Lampoon&amp;rsquo;s European Vacation&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;National Lampoon&amp;rsquo;s Christmas Vacation&amp;rdquo;. As I type this I am getting ready to watch them both. Those are the ones to laugh to tears and have fun. The other favorite one &amp;ndash;please don&amp;rsquo;t hate me&amp;ndash; is &amp;ldquo;The Sound of Music.&amp;rdquo; There is something about it that just does it for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Mobile and the iPad</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/24/tmobile-and-the-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/24/tmobile-and-the-ipad/</guid>
      <description>I am not sure about the other mobile telephony providers, but this morning I went to T-Mobile with the intention of buying an iPad mini. They had only the dark colour in stock, and on 32GB capacity &amp;ndash; I was wanting a 16GB. The transaction was almost finished, when I was asked for a telephone number. After stating that I just wanted the iPad, no connection, I was told they could only sell it, if it was with a mobile data plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas Tree Small Story</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/23/a-christmas-tree-small-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/23/a-christmas-tree-small-story/</guid>
      <description>Last year we had a plastic Christmas tree. Wife was not happy. This year she wanted a real one, so this morning the child and I went on the quest of getting it. Most families in the States will get a Christmas tree right after Thanksgiving, but I am used to get it the day before Christmas. Of course, if I wait for that day there will be none left. So it is today, or never1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Lorre Productions, 373</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/23/the-prophet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/23/the-prophet/</guid>
      <description>At the end of each episode of &amp;ldquo;The Big Bang Theory&amp;rdquo; there is always something witty printed, that passes by so fast you can not read it. Today I saw, and remembered, &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; the prophet did not answer right away &amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo; I looked it up, and this came up.
The Prophet  A young woman stepped forward from the throng and asked, &amp;ldquo;0&amp;rsquo; great prophet, tell us how we might find love that is unconditional, unwavering and unending.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>