<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>guardian on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/guardian/</link>
    <description>Recent content in guardian on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/guardian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Space for the Dead</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/space-for-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/space-for-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>I read an article today on The Guardian, which showed up on the eight page of Hacker’s News. It talks about the lack of space for the dead, in the world of the living.
 &amp;ldquo;Some 55 million people are reckoned to pass away each year (about 0.8% of the planet’s total population – equivalent to 100% of England’s). Yet urban planners and developers focus overwhelmingly on accommodating and making money from the living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The very last of Something</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/14/the-very-last-of-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/14/the-very-last-of-something/</guid>
      <description>There hasn&amp;rsquo;t been an article like this for a while, that fills me with such feeling of sadness, and emptiness. For as long as I can remember, a cartoon I saw as a child started my attraction for rhinoceros. Such lovely animals!
And now, the one pictured above (CB2/ZOB/Brent Stirton/National Geographic) is the last of his kind. Who do we have to thank for that? Us. On a comment to the article, a poster under a &amp;ldquo;Gordo Granudo&amp;rdquo; pseudonym writes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where are you from?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/07/30/where-are-you-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/07/30/where-are-you-from/</guid>
      <description>In the States, looking different and/or having an accent will get you asked &amp;ldquo;Where are you from?&amp;rdquo; It doesn&amp;rsquo;t fail, it happens all the time.
Why are we so concerned about knowing someone&amp;rsquo;s country of origin? What difference does it make? If anything, it might be a knowledge we do not want to have. Knowing from where someone is from might spark stereotypical comments and behaviors that would jeopardize an otherwise perfect encounter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>