<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>serverbeach on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/serverbeach/</link>
    <description>Recent content in serverbeach on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/serverbeach/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Host hunting</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/11/24/host-hunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/11/24/host-hunting/</guid>
      <description>I had had all my websites &amp;mdash;this one, and many other test ones, etc&amp;mdash;, plus my self-managed DNS on ServerBeach(now part of Peer1) for a very long time. They all reside on a dedicated server, which has, sadly, reached it&amp;rsquo;s end of life (EOL).
Although I can keep it as it is, doing so represents a liability problem, as I will be out of luck, should it decide to fail. The problem is, ServerBeach isn&amp;rsquo;t offering anything right now similar to the server I have, for the amount of money I pay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoDaddy and MediaTemple</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/07/godaddy-and-mediatemple/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/07/godaddy-and-mediatemple/</guid>
      <description>Not long ago I was looking for a new collocation provider. I was with ServerBeach, as I am right now, but the friend I was teaming up with to share the expenses wanted to move from Linux to a Windows server, and I have nothing to do with one &amp;ndash;Windows server, that is. Since I couldn&amp;rsquo;t afford to pay the fees on my own, I was off to find a new provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short and sweet</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/06/17/short-and-sweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/06/17/short-and-sweet/</guid>
      <description>Just a quick post, short and sweet, while my wife and kid still sleep and I patiently wait for the ServerBeach people to fix the mess on my server (the other server). Can you believe that I lost connection last night, went to sleep and this morning I found that my IP goes to a Windows 2003 server? Boy, talk about some big time screw up!
I have 15 (fifteen, that is) invitations for Gmailthat I am giving out for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing servers</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/25/changing-servers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/25/changing-servers/</guid>
      <description>As if weren&amp;rsquo;t enough my move to WordPress and my internal debacle on what to do with the site design, now I am getting ready to move all domains and files &amp;ndash;physically&amp;ndash; to another hosting company, on a real colocated server (not VSanymore).
The virtual server I have used until now (and that I still use now, for the time being) served me well, but it is getting old (RH 8.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>