<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/categories/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/categories/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Beat a Polygraph Test</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/03/how-to-beat-a-polygraph-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/03/how-to-beat-a-polygraph-test/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;He used to advise trainees to clench their anus but has since concluded that terrifying mental imagery works better.&amp;rdquo;
 When you get a control question, which is more general, envision the scariest thing you can in order to trigger physiological distress; the polygraph&amp;rsquo;s tubes around your chest measure breathing, the arm cuff monitors heart rate and electrodes attached to you fingertips detect perspiration. What is your greatest fear? Falling? Drowning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insignificant</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/27/insignificant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/27/insignificant/</guid>
      <description>Do you see the pale dot on the dark image above? You don&amp;rsquo;t see it? Look carefully, it is there! That pale dot could be us, Earth; but you pick: Solar System, Milky Way, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. We are that insignificant because of the vastness of the universe we live in. And vastness is an understatement. After all, the universe is infinite.
We might try to explain what is at our noses, but that &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rdquo; will always be too insignificant to mean anything more than what is immediate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t talk to aliens</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/28/dont-talk-to-aliens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/28/dont-talk-to-aliens/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;We only have to look at ourselves to see how intelligent life might develop into something we wouldn’t want to meet. I imagine they might exist in massive ships, having used up all the resources from their home planet. Such advanced aliens would perhaps become nomads, looking to conquer and colonise whatever planets they can reach.&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;If aliens ever visit us, I think the outcome would be much as when Christopher Columbus first landed in America, which didn’t turn out very well for the Native Americans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veteran of Charley</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/08/15/veteran-of-charlie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/08/15/veteran-of-charlie/</guid>
      <description>Mother Nature, just as humans, changes her mind. That is the case of hurricane Charley. All forecasts read that Tampa, FL would be the one beaten by him but Mother Nature, with it&amp;rsquo;s natural (no pun intended) ambivalence made a twist and brought it directly near Fort Myers, and then to us in Orlando, FL.
Needless is to say we had winds. We had winds all right. Actually, we got everything: homes, commercial buildings, trees&amp;hellip; all destroyed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>