<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 19:28:16 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A few technical changes</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/03/05/a-few-technical-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 19:28:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/03/05/a-few-technical-changes/</guid>
      <description>A few things have happened on my current server setup. The biggest one was my move from FreeBSD to Ubuntu. I do not have complains about FreeBSD &amp;mdash; how could I? &amp;mdash; but I wanted to play with more recent stuff, and it was becoming very hard to do under BSD. I also wanted a refresh, since I had been running that VPS for a while and it was starting to feel &amp;ldquo;dirty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IP migration</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/09/09/ip-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/09/09/ip-migration/</guid>
      <description>I have a deadline to meet. I must migrate all my servers, and clients to a private IP space. Servers must be done &amp;mdash; if at all possible &amp;mdash; by September 30th. Clients by October 30th. That is, this year. Problem is, I have never done anything close to it, and there are so many things that need to be done at once, I don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start.
I have a Linux DNS/DHCP to change (Internet facing one).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linuxers for Obama</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/21/linuxers-for-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/21/linuxers-for-obama/</guid>
      <description>Linuxers for Obama &amp;ndash; LinuxersForObama is a campaign for all Free and Open Source Software advocates to contribute to the Obama campaign. Sorry for the shorthand &amp;ldquo;LinuxForObama&amp;rdquo;, I know it should have been &amp;ldquo;FLOSSGNUX11BSDApacheMySQLForObama&amp;rdquo;, but I went for short and simple.
Hopefully team LinuxForObama can do some nice fund raising for Obama and we can settle once and for all the argument about which operating system is the best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora Core Test 3</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/04/25/fedora-core-test-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/04/25/fedora-core-test-3/</guid>
      <description>I have installed Fedora Core Test 2 on my new XPS (dual boot), ran up2date, gotten Test 3 and I must say it is one sweet, nice coming along distribution. Hardened with SELinux, running kernel 2.6.3 and with a nice set of packages available, Fedora will certainly stand out.
I am really contemplating getting one of those mighty cheap Dell servers, get Fedora (once it is released) installed and collocate. I might do that, seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>