<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bbc on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/bbc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bbc on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2006 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/bbc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nazi crimes archives set to open</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/05/16/nazi-crimes-archives-set-to-open-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/05/16/nazi-crimes-archives-set-to-open-2/</guid>
      <description>BBC News: Nazi crimes archives to set open.
 The 47 million files hold Nazi records of forced labourers, concentration camp victims and political prisoners. They have been used to help people trace their relatives, but were kept closed to protect victims&amp;rsquo; privacy. Many people felt the files should be opened to historical researchers to ensure the details of the Holocaust (Nazis genocide) are not forgotten.
 Yes, we must not forget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC goes WoW again!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/10/20/bbc-goes-wow-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/10/20/bbc-goes-wow-again/</guid>
      <description>Although this new &amp;ldquo;interview&amp;rdquo; involves only Horde players, the latest BBC article about WoW is awesome and it gives some very sutil but good insides of the game.
 I&amp;rsquo;ts popularity can be primarily attributed to its accessibility. The game is easy, plain and simple.
It&amp;rsquo;s more forgiving than most other online role-playing games on the market, and does not take as much dedicated playing or &amp;ldquo;grinding&amp;rdquo; to reach the top level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC and WoW</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/09/30/bbc-and-wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/09/30/bbc-and-wow/</guid>
      <description>From one article on today&amp;rsquo;s BBC Online news:
 Occasionally gryphons and hippogriffs swept majestically overhead taking their riders to elsewhere in Azeroth or, as it is also known, the World of Warcraft (WoW).
At the edge of the computer screen chatter constantly scrolled past as other WoW players sought members forguilds, buyers for magical items, help with quests or engaged in idle banter.
 Go and read: A Walk in the World of Warcraft.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>