<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>linode on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/linode/</link>
    <description>Recent content in linode on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/linode/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>On AWS S3</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2012/01/28/on-aws-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2012/01/28/on-aws-s3/</guid>
      <description>I have moved from Linode (which I will be canceling soon) to Namecheap DNS management (I have all my domains on Namecheap) and Amazon S3. Transition went well, and painless. It should save me some money.
Nothing wrong with Linode, which I recommend to anyone looking to having their own Virtual Server. Their service rock, and their price is hard to beat. I used their services for a year and totally loved it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Many changes coming soon</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/04/01/many-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/04/01/many-changes/</guid>
      <description>Just very recently I wrote about me moving to Jekyll from WordPress:
 After much thought, and tinkering, I decided to ditch my six year old or so WordPress and start blogging like a hacker with the awesome Jekyll.
 I also wrote —fairly recently— about living on a Linode:
 Moved to Linode. Love it, highly recommend it. They reward customers that bring referrals, but notice my links do not have any referral code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living on a Linode</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/14/living-on-a-linode/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/14/living-on-a-linode/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR.
Moved to Linode. Love it, highly recommend it. They reward customers that bring referrals, but notice my links do not have any referral code. That much I like their product.
All my domains have resided on a ServerBeach dedicated server for over six years now. I have tried to find something else before (cheaper, price wise), but I always stayed on ServerBeach, as they have always been reliable, with fast connections.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>