<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hillary on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/hillary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hillary on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/hillary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I was wrong</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/11/09/i-was-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/11/09/i-was-wrong/</guid>
      <description>Back in October 5th, 2015, I wrote a prediction, which I saved in a file for which I posted a hash. I predicted that Hillary Clinton would win the United States presidential elections. Sadly, I was wrong.
I really do not have much else to say. I am sorry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders keeps fighting</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/06/09/bernie-sanders-keeps-fighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/06/09/bernie-sanders-keeps-fighting/</guid>
      <description>Bernie Sanders has had a good run. Yet numbers are pilled against him, and he should know it. After all he said he was &amp;ldquo;pretty good in arithmetic.&amp;rdquo; Hillary has beaten him, and the right and honorable thing for him to do is to call it quits.
 “If, on November 8th of this year, Hillary Clinton is elected President, we will have only begun to fight,” Sanders told a packed rally in San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/prediction/</guid>
      <description>Next year we will have our Presidential Elections. Everyone knows that, of course, because the politicians have been campaining for almost a year now.
Below is the name of a file with my winner&amp;rsquo;s prediction on the United States 2016 Presidential Elections written on it. It is a hash algorithm of a file containing a sentence with my prediction. I will refer to this post the day after elections, as the results are known.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From today&#39;s Barack&#39;s email</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/07/from-todays-baracks-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/07/from-todays-baracks-email/</guid>
      <description>News broke this morning that Senator Clinton made three separate loans to her campaign in the past 30 days &amp;mdash;including one as recently as Monday.
These loans total more than $6.4 million, which combined with her previous personal loans, add up to at least $11.4 million she&amp;rsquo;s loaned her campaign since February.
A spokesman said she may continue to &amp;ldquo;loan the campaign additional money out of her jointly-held assets&amp;rdquo; &amp;mdash;which include more than $100 million in income since her husband left the White House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary speaks like Bush</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/06/hillary-speaks-like-bush/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/06/hillary-speaks-like-bush/</guid>
      <description>Obama accuses Clinton of using the language of Bush on Iran
 In the sharpest attack, Obama said that Clinton&amp;rsquo;s threat to &amp;ldquo;totally obliterate&amp;rdquo; Iran should it attempt a nuclear attack on Israel was inappropriate. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s not the language we need right now. It&amp;rsquo;s language that&amp;rsquo;s reflective of George Bush,&amp;rdquo; he said.
Obama said it was time to get away from a foreign policy of &amp;ldquo;bluster and sabre-rattling and tough talk&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinton wins in Pennsylvania, projected</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/22/clinton-wins-pennsylvania/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/22/clinton-wins-pennsylvania/</guid>
      <description>Clinton wins in Pennsylvania &amp;ndash; NBC News projected Tuesday night that Sen. Hillary Rodham Clinton had won Pennsylvania&amp;rsquo;s presidential primary, a victory that analysts said she had to have if she were to remain a credible candidate for the Democratic nomination.
 I find it incredible how she has been able to get as many votes as she has. But after seeing McCain take over the Republican&amp;rsquo;s vote I should have expected anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vicepresident? No, thank you</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/11/vicepresident-no-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/11/vicepresident-no-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Obama spurns double ticket hints
 &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know how somebody who is in second place is offering the vice presidency to somebody who is in first place,&amp;rdquo; he told a rally in Columbus, Mississippi.
&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t want anybody here thinking that somehow &amp;lsquo;well, you know, maybe I can get both.&amp;rsquo; Don&amp;rsquo;t think that way. You have to make a choice in this election.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not running for vice president. I am running for president of the United States of America,&amp;rdquo; he added.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That 3:00AM call</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/07/that-300am-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/07/that-300am-call/</guid>
      <description>Comment posted on Larry David: On the Red Phone
 &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s 3AM and your children are sleeping. But the phone is ringing. It&amp;rsquo;s your mortgage lender, calling to let you know that you are 180 days late on your payment for that crazy mortgage you agreed to. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, because your phone was disconnected a long time ago. But no worries, Hillary Clinton is working late, at some desk somewhere, doing a Sudoku puzzle maybe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I just hope...</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/04/i-just-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/04/i-just-hope/</guid>
      <description>I just hope she doesn&amp;rsquo;t win. I am talking about politics, if you are following the news, you know who I am talking about. Hard not to follow politics these days, but you never know.
Yes, I hope she looses.
Update: She didn&amp;rsquo;t loose. She won three states. Obama still leads on delegates. There is still hope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What counts as an issue...</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/02/01/what-counts-as-an-issue-in-the-clinton-obama-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/02/01/what-counts-as-an-issue-in-the-clinton-obama-race/</guid>
      <description>George Lakoff: What Counts as an &amp;ldquo;Issue&amp;rdquo; In the Clinton-Obama Race?
 There is a reason that Obama recently spoke of Reagan. Reagan understood that you win elections by drawing support from independents and the opposite side. He understood what unified the country so that he could lead it according to his vision. His vision was a radical conservative one, a vision devastating for the country and contradicted by his economic policies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>