<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>att on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/att/</link>
    <description>Recent content in att on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 12:42:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/att/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>On AT&amp;T fibre</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/10/08/att-fibre/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 12:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/10/08/att-fibre/</guid>
      <description>Had to chat with an AT&amp;amp;T employee, as a result of an order I placed yesterday. This is the feedback I left (with minor spelling corrections), after concluding the chat:
 The chat experience was excellent (chat agent, Marry). AT&amp;amp;T experience thus far, not quite so.
I had an AT&amp;amp;T sales agent visit me yesterday. I signed up for Internet 1Gbps (Internet 1000 on AT&amp;amp;T lingo), and phone service (transferring my current number).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video quality while on 3G</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/05/01/video-quality-while-on-3g/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/05/01/video-quality-while-on-3g/</guid>
      <description>The same day I got the iPad 3G, I noticed a very contrasting video quality while using Wi-Fi and while using 3G. Videos watched on Youtube would have HD quality (Wi-Fi); same videos, while on 3G, would show horribly. Yet, videos on Apple, while on 3G or Wi-Fi, would show perfectly. All that whether using the app or the web browser, tested both.
Is it Youtube serving a very low quality video to 3G users?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate cell phones!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2002/10/29/as-gee-will-say-i-hate-cell-phones/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2002 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2002/10/29/as-gee-will-say-i-hate-cell-phones/</guid>
      <description>I had had BellSouth Mobility, Cingular Wireless and, now, AT&amp;amp;T. Each and everyone of them rendered a really bad service. In street talk, they have sucked. Now I am at a dilemma: two years contract with AT&amp;amp;T, $150 to break it. On the other hand, I can not receive neither initiate calls from inside my house, neither at work. Most of the times the reception/transmission is really bad, regardless where I am at.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>