<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>parents on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/parents/</link>
    <description>Recent content in parents on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/parents/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mi Vieja</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/12/03/mi-vieja/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/12/03/mi-vieja/</guid>
      <description>She created me, all my flaws and gifts unintended. She nurtured and guided me through life the best she could, suffering for my mistakes &amp;mdash;but always hopeful&amp;mdash; and rejoicing on my victories. Always supportive she gave herself to me (and my siblings), selflessly.
After a lifetime mission, her time around here has expired. We knew it would come, but never fully prepared for it. And so we wept, sadness seeping through us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday, Viejo!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/02/27/happy-birthday-viejo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/02/27/happy-birthday-viejo/</guid>
      <description>Not a day goes by without me thinking of my Dad. Today he would have being 92 years old.
I still remember him on his 90th birthday, doing push ups using only three fingers on each hand. I will forever remember the endless stories he used to tell, and his constant smile. He was the best father a son can ask for, an example for many. It hurts so very much not to have him around anymore&amp;hellip;!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mi viejo</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/11/26/mi-viejo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/11/26/mi-viejo/</guid>
      <description>A steady, yet gentle, rain was falling over Miami on the night of November 24th, 2010. Some say rain are tears from the sky. I was crying as well. On November 24th my father died.
Those who have lost an infinitely dear one will understand how I feel. Not only did I lose the best father a son could have, I lost a lifetime friend, a restless protector, a confidant. The many memories that I have of him continue to bring tears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parents at home</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2002/12/22/parents-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2002 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2002/12/22/parents-at-home/</guid>
      <description>We have my parents visiting for Christmas and New Year. Kent Martin is already showing his happiness and he remembered my dad. I am glad it is not too cold &amp;mdash; at least for now &amp;mdash; so my parents time is more enjoyable (meaning they will be able to go out with us and such). I have miss them a lot and I am really happy to have them with us for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>