<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gmail on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/gmail/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gmail on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/gmail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail.app on iOS</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/16/gmail-app-on-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/16/gmail-app-on-ios/</guid>
      <description>I like Google and its services. Like is too little, I love them! Their mobile applications on the other hand &amp;mdash; specifically those running under iOS &amp;mdash; are horrible. The UIX is confusing and it does not follows Apple UIX design. Their choice of font is of poor taste and, again, does not match the rest of the OS. They lack of functionality and/or their functionality is limited by poor choices and, what is seems to be, a lack of common sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail for Domains</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/05/12/gmail-for-domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/05/12/gmail-for-domains/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I received my invitation to move my Collantes.US domain over Google, to handle all mail by using the Gmail interface. That is Google new beta testing of hosted email for corporations or midsize companies. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a midsize company, but have a big family, so I qualified. Collantes.US, of course, is way too valuable for beta testing, but I have several more domains I can use, so I decided to resubmit my request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moved!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/06/22/moved/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/06/22/moved/</guid>
      <description>I have just moved Collantes.US to the new server. DNS is still running on the old one, but you should be seeing the new pages served on the new server Apache. If you see a note at the top asking not to enter a comment, please do so &amp;ndash; that is, do not enter a comment. That server is the old one and it will disappear sooner rather than later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short and sweet</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/06/17/short-and-sweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/06/17/short-and-sweet/</guid>
      <description>Just a quick post, short and sweet, while my wife and kid still sleep and I patiently wait for the ServerBeach people to fix the mess on my server (the other server). Can you believe that I lost connection last night, went to sleep and this morning I found that my IP goes to a Windows 2003 server? Boy, talk about some big time screw up!
I have 15 (fifteen, that is) invitations for Gmail that I am giving out for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail invitations for sale</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/08/gmail-invitations-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/08/gmail-invitations-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>It was just a matter of time until this happened: Google webmail invitations are being sold like crazy on eBay. Some people are even buying one invitation knowing that eventually Google will give two (it has been happening on every new account), so they can resell more. Amazing!
This site looks like crap under Mozilla on Linux, which bothers me a lot. I think I will move things around here soon to accommodate what it might become my desktop OS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail is not for everyone</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/04/22/gmail-is-not-for-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/04/22/gmail-is-not-for-everyone/</guid>
      <description>I have used Gmail now a little bit. Sometimes I am a lucky guy; I have experienced good luck several times: when I met Kim, when my child was born, when I first flew over the Atlantic. This time my luck came in the form of a Gmail account. Thanks to those who graciously offered me the chance to see with my own eyes what many other mortals have ambition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Hype</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/04/17/gmail-hype/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/04/17/gmail-hype/</guid>
      <description>Everybody is talking about Google&amp;rsquo;s upcoming Gmail. Since I wasn&amp;rsquo;t choosen to beta test, I can not offer any excellent insider view, but I can write about what I think of the whole thing. The reason of this post is to keep a record, for the posterity, about my point of view on this whole thing.
So, let&amp;rsquo;s get to the point. I think Gmail will be awesome, if it opens at all for the general public (&amp;ldquo;We think it&amp;rsquo;s an absolute invasion of privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>