<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>religion on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/categories/religion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in religion on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/categories/religion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Disappointing</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/30/disappointing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/30/disappointing/</guid>
      <description>Pope Francis &amp;ldquo;thanked her for her courage&amp;rdquo; and told her to &amp;ldquo;stay strong&amp;rdquo;, Mr. Stavers said.
&amp;mdash; BBC News
 If this truly happened, it is disappointing. A person as charismatic as Pope Francis, who has been so politically careful, should have known better. She is a government employee, fulfilling an official task. She must abide the law, or simply leave her job, if she can&amp;rsquo;t perform as expected. What would we do if our troops, due to their religious beliefs, decide to put down their weapons?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Francis</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/22/protecting-francis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/22/protecting-francis/</guid>
      <description>The Pope has recently been to Cuba, and today he will be arriving to the United States. Like any other dignitary, the Pope needs protection from both, bad people, and adoring crowds. Yet, doing so is not easy feat.
 “The crowds throw things,” Mr. Clancy, who took over as the head of the Secret Service last October, said in an interview. “They throw flags, dolls and, obviously, babies towards him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huckabee offers his Support</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/02/huckabee-offers-his-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/02/huckabee-offers-his-support/</guid>
      <description>Mike Huckabee, a christian pastor turned politician has offered his support to the Court clerk in Kentucky who, against Supreme Court order, refuses to issue gay marriage licenses.
 &amp;ldquo;I spoke with Kim Davis this morning to offer my prayers and support. I let her know how proud I am of her for not abandoning her religious convictions and standing strong for religious liberty. She is showing more courage and humility than just about any federal office holder in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ricky Gervais - Why I&#39;m an Atheist</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/03/10/ricky-gervais-why-im-an-atheist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/03/10/ricky-gervais-why-im-an-atheist/</guid>
      <description>This is an article written by Ricky Gervais, for The Wall Street Journal back in 2010.
Reproduced entirely here, as SpeakEasy seems not to be keep articles around long enough. If WSJ does not like what I have done, let me know and I will remove it, or adapt it to a compromise. Please do not sue me.
Some emphasis mine.
Ricky Gervais: Why I&amp;rsquo;m an Atheist Why don&amp;rsquo;t you believe in God?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Einstein on religion</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/15/einstein-on-religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/15/einstein-on-religion/</guid>
      <description>Einstein: Letter to Eric Gutkind &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; The word God is for me nothing more than the expression and product of human weaknesses, the Bible a collection of honourable, but still primitive legends which are nevertheless pretty childish. No interpretation no matter how subtle can for me change this. These subtilized interpretations are highly manifold according to their nature and have almost nothing to do with the original text. For me the Jewish religion like all other religions is an incarnation of the most childish superstitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John McCain on religion</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/07/john-mccain-on-religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/07/john-mccain-on-religion/</guid>
      <description>John McCain on religion.
 &amp;ldquo;I just have to say in all candor that since this nation was founded primarily on Christian principles&amp;hellip;personally, I prefer someone who I know who has a solid grounding in my faith&amp;hellip;I think the number one issue people should make [in the] selection of the President of the United States is, &amp;lsquo;Will this person carry on in the Judeo Christian principled tradition that has made this nation the greatest experiment in the history of mankind?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In God we trust</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/02/in-god-we-trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/02/in-god-we-trust/</guid>
      <description>It is interesting to find out, at times when some minority wants to have removed &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;under God&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; from the Pledge of Allegiance, about this &amp;mdash;it refers to the Great Seal of the United States of America motto:
 The federal courts have held that the motto symbolizes the historical role of religion in our society, Lynch, 465 U.S. at 676, formalizes our medium of exchange, see O&amp;rsquo;Hair v. Blumenthal, 462 F.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>