<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>google on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/google/</link>
    <description>Recent content in google on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/google/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumnal Equinox</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/23/autumnal-equinox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/23/autumnal-equinox/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the beginning of one of my two favorite seasons, Autumn&amp;mdash;or Fall, as it is commonly called in the United States. Living in Florida makes the season a very, very mild one, with temperatures still quite high (it will be 90°F today), yet it brings the solid certainty that summer is being left behind.
Join me on celebrating the Autumnal Equinox today, at 04:21 US Eastern time, which is 08:21 UTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail.app on iOS</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/16/gmail-app-on-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/16/gmail-app-on-ios/</guid>
      <description>I like Google and its services. Like is too little, I love them! Their mobile applications on the other hand &amp;mdash; specifically those running under iOS &amp;mdash; are horrible. The UIX is confusing and it does not follows Apple UIX design. Their choice of font is of poor taste and, again, does not match the rest of the OS. They lack of functionality and/or their functionality is limited by poor choices and, what is seems to be, a lack of common sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Google Checkout</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/11/01/use-google-checkout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/11/01/use-google-checkout/</guid>
      <description>I was going to write a longer note on Paypal and eBay, but after some time to cool down I do not think it is worth it. Instead I am going to recommend, wholeheartedly, the use of Google Checkout for all your payments and shopping needs. Really, once again Google did not let me down and transformed an otherwise nightmare into a pleasant auctioning/shopping dream.
If you must use eBay, find a way to use Google Checkout with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gOS is coming our way</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/07/08/gos-is-coming-our-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/07/08/gos-is-coming-our-way/</guid>
      <description>Yes, it is coming!
 We hear a lot from our users and their message is clear &amp;ndash; computers need to get better. People want to get to their email instantly, without wasting time waiting for their computers to boot and browsers to start up. They want their computers to always run as fast as when they first bought them. They want their data to be accessible to them wherever they are and not have to worry about losing their computer or forgetting to back up files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! and the future of the Internet</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/02/04/yahoo-and-the-future-of-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/02/04/yahoo-and-the-future-of-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>Official Google Blog: Yahoo! and the future of the Internet
 Could the acquisition of Yahoo! allow Microsoft &amp;ndash; despite its legacy of serious legal and regulatory offenses &amp;ndash; to extend unfair practices from browsers and operating systems to the Internet? In addition, Microsoft plus Yahoo! equals an overwhelming share of instant messaging and web email accounts. And between them, the two companies operate the two most heavily trafficked portals on the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two visions?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/03/20/two-visions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/03/20/two-visions/</guid>
      <description>Mark posted yesterday that he will be working for Google, since out of the &amp;ldquo;two visions&amp;rdquo; of the web, he says, Google is the right one. I am not web savvy nor I really care much about it, but I am sure there is more than two visions on the web, there is not right and wrong, but many, many, many shades in between. But the way I see it, the bottom line in my mind: he is going to work for someone who will pay him very well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail for Domains</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/05/12/gmail-for-domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/05/12/gmail-for-domains/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I received my invitation to move my Collantes.US domain over Google, to handle all mail by using the Gmail interface. That is Google new beta testing of hosted email for corporations or midsize companies. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a midsize company, but have a big family, so I qualified. Collantes.US, of course, is way too valuable for beta testing, but I have several more domains I can use, so I decided to resubmit my request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adsense presence</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/01/25/adsense-presence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/01/25/adsense-presence/</guid>
      <description>I few of you might have realized that I, finally, got approved on Goggle&amp;rsquo;s Adsense program. Two years ago I applied, with the hopes of becoming rich. I was very naïve and I was denied participation. Recently I applied again. I did it mainly for two reasons: I love Google. I can not deny I am in love with it. Everything that Google has offered so far is of my liking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail invitations</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/08/25/gmail-invitations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/08/25/gmail-invitations/</guid>
      <description>I have 6 Gmail invitations that I will give out to anyone who writes a sincere comment about the use it will give to such account, if given. I have been using Gmail for a while now and I can assure you it is a great service, addictive indeed. It is not all about the 1GB of space that Google gives with it, but the excellent features and blazing speed. You can read more about Gmail on the Gmail Support Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s Doodles</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/08/22/googles-doodles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/08/22/googles-doodles/</guid>
      <description>Google is well known for altering its homepage logos to commemorate a special event or Holidays. They have done it since 1999 &amp;mdash;at least, that is the earliest documented year.
This year Olympic Games are not an exception. Google Doodle VIII celebrates the 2004 Olympic Games in Athens. Below is a local cache of them (I will keep adding them until the Olympics are over). I hope I will not get into trouble for doing so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail invitations for sale</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/08/gmail-invitations-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/08/gmail-invitations-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>It was just a matter of time until this happened: Google webmail invitations are being sold like crazy on eBay. Some people are even buying one invitation knowing that eventually Google will give two (it has been happening on every new account), so they can resell more. Amazing!
This site looks like crap under Mozilla on Linux, which bothers me a lot. I think I will move things around here soon to accommodate what it might become my desktop OS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail is not for everyone</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/04/22/gmail-is-not-for-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/04/22/gmail-is-not-for-everyone/</guid>
      <description>I have used Gmail now a little bit. Sometimes I am a lucky guy; I have experienced good luck several times: when I met Kim, when my child was born, when I first flew over the Atlantic. This time my luck came in the form of a Gmail account. Thanks to those who graciously offered me the chance to see with my own eyes what many other mortals have ambition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Hype</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/04/17/gmail-hype/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/04/17/gmail-hype/</guid>
      <description>Everybody is talking about Google&amp;rsquo;s upcoming Gmail. Since I wasn&amp;rsquo;t choosen to beta test, I can not offer any excellent insider view, but I can write about what I think of the whole thing. The reason of this post is to keep a record, for the posterity, about my point of view on this whole thing.
So, let&amp;rsquo;s get to the point. I think Gmail will be awesome, if it opens at all for the general public (&amp;ldquo;We think it&amp;rsquo;s an absolute invasion of privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money for your hobby?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/09/15/money-for-your-hobby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/09/15/money-for-your-hobby/</guid>
      <description>I have seeing an increasing amount of weblogs that are, either running Google AdSense to make money or asking for donations. Does that works? I mean, does Google AdSense can be enough for someone to actually make a living out if it? And, on a related token, would the amount of &amp;ldquo;donations&amp;rdquo; add up enough to pay the rent? I am curious.
On politics. I am a republican although I am not sure if I will vote like so on the next Presidential elections.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>