<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bush on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/bush/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bush on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 19:59:15 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/bush/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An Intelligent Person</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/27/an-intelligent-person/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 19:59:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/27/an-intelligent-person/</guid>
      <description>From Twitter:
 The most amazing thing about the Trump presidency is that it’s made GWB look like a reasonably intelligent person.
&amp;mdash; Derek Powazek (@fraying) February 27, 2017
 And from The New York Times:
 Former President George W. Bush said Monday &amp;ldquo;we all need answers&amp;rdquo; on the extent of contact between President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s team and the Russian government, and didn&amp;rsquo;t rule out the idea that a special prosecutor could be necessary to lead an investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The truth is useless</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/01/14/the-truth-is-useless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/01/14/the-truth-is-useless/</guid>
      <description>On Digg, someone submitted, Jeb Bush, the truth is useless, to which a reader commented:
Digg - Jeb Bush: &amp;lsquo;The truth is useless&amp;rsquo;
 [&amp;hellip;] This is not just the Bushes, though. This is human nature. This sort of thing develops when you elevate yourself to stratospheric heights and start to believe your own hype. It happens to Hollywood actors, musicians, moguls, models, magicians, shop managers, morticians, bankers, soldiers, physicians&amp;hellip; Even the guy temporarily assigned to run the night shift cleaning crew while the regular dick is out on sick leave starts to walk more proudly thinking he best be listened to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You are a prisoner, keep quiet!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/27/you-are-a-prisoner-keep-quiet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/27/you-are-a-prisoner-keep-quiet/</guid>
      <description>U.S. Seeks Silence on CIA Prisons
 The Bush administration has told a federal judge that terrorism suspects held in secret CIA prisons should not be allowed to reveal details of the &amp;ldquo;alternative interrogation methods&amp;rdquo; that their captors used to get them to talk.
The government says in new court filings that those interrogation methods are now among the nation&amp;rsquo;s most sensitive national security secrets and that their release &amp;ndash; even to the detainees&amp;rsquo; own attorneys &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;could reasonably be expected to cause extremely grave damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chosen by God?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/12/chosen-by-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/12/chosen-by-god/</guid>
      <description>I have heard in several occasions, and read quite a few times, that President George W. Bush believes he was chosen (appointed) by God to be our President. God, supposedly, wants nothing but well being for us all, right? Then I would like to know what Mr. Bush is doing to end the killing, abuse and hunger (among other things) from places like Central, South America and Caribbean, Africa and great parts of Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iraq, are we going to war?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/01/18/iraq-are-we-going-to-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2003 18:14:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/01/18/iraq-are-we-going-to-war/</guid>
      <description>If you have been following the news you already know about the Iraq situation. You might still be asking yourself why are we building up such a massive military power in the area, that is, Middle East. Right, you are not questioning that, since you know the answer: we are going to war. What you might be thinking is whether or not we should be there, should we care. All valid questions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>