<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>brighthouse on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/brighthouse/</link>
    <description>Recent content in brighthouse on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/brighthouse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bright House saga</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/05/02/bright-house-saga/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/05/02/bright-house-saga/</guid>
      <description>In two occasions I have written about Bright House service, or the lack of. Ever since my last entry, many issues aroused, but I never came here to document them.
What where those issues? They vary, and cover a wide range. So many Bright House technicians has passed by my house, I lost count. The proverbial &amp;ldquo;how many technicians do Bright House needs&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; comes to mind. Issues:
 Black out screens, with &amp;ldquo;Please wait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bright House Follow Up</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/10/09/bright-house-follow-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/10/09/bright-house-follow-up/</guid>
      <description>You will remember my previous Bright House post. The same day I wrote that, I got a call from a Bright House customer service representative. Since there is no need to know names, let&amp;rsquo;s call her Christine. I like that name.
Christine told me Bright House was aware I had publicly written about my displeasure with their services, and that her job was to make sure I was completely satisfied. Fair enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avoid Bright House if You Can</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/10/05/avoid-brighthouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/10/05/avoid-brighthouse/</guid>
      <description>I live in Central Florida. In my area, if I want cable TV and Internet, I have no choice but to use Bright House services. The competition is satellite TV/Internet and/or DSL (for Internet). Why am I recommending to avoid Bright House, if you can? It is simple: their service is far from being of a good quality and/or reliable. I will elaborate a little.
On cable TV, you get black screens (no video or audio), or &amp;ldquo;Please wait&amp;rdquo; screens, constantly and randomly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>