<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jobs on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jobs on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Fry on Steve Jobs</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/10/26/steve-jobs-by-stephen-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/10/26/steve-jobs-by-stephen-fry/</guid>
      <description>Stephen Fry is an English actor, screenwriter, author, playwright, journalist, poet, comedian, television presenter, film director and a director of Norwich City Football Club. He is also an awesome human being.
 As always there are those who reveal their asininity (as they did throughout his career) with ascriptions like &amp;ldquo;salesman&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;showman&amp;rdquo; or the giveaway blunder &amp;ldquo;triumph of style over substance&amp;rdquo;. The use of that last phrase, &amp;ldquo;style over substance&amp;rdquo; has always been, as Oscar Wilde observed, a marvellous and instant indicator of a fool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve P. Jobs, 1955 - 2011</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/10/05/steve-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/10/05/steve-jobs/</guid>
      <description>A great man has passed away. While mourning, we celebrate all he brought to us&amp;hellip; his many accomplishments. He will not be forgotten.
February 24, 1955 &amp;ndash; October 5, 2011</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C.E.O. no longer, good bye Steve!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/08/24/ceo-no-longer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/08/24/ceo-no-longer/</guid>
      <description>Steve Jobs &amp;ldquo;resigns&amp;rdquo; as Apple&amp;rsquo;s C.E.O.
 &amp;ldquo;I have always said if there ever came a day when I could no longer meet my duties and expectations as Apple’s C.E.O., I would be the first to let you know,&amp;rdquo; Mr. Jobs wrote. &amp;ldquo;Unfortunately, that day has come.&amp;rdquo;
 The world needs more Steve Jobs. He will be missed. Get better Steve!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find what you love</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/04/11/find-what-you-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/04/11/find-what-you-love/</guid>
      <description>Steve Jobs commencement address at Stanford University, in 2005:
 Remembering that I’ll be dead soon is the most important tool I’ve ever encountered to help me make the big choices in life. Because almost everything — all external expectations, all pride, all fear of embarrassment or failure — these things just fall away in the face of death, leaving only what is truly important. Remembering that you are going to die is the best way I know to avoid the trap of thinking you have something to lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Flash</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/29/thoughts-on-flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/29/thoughts-on-flash/</guid>
      <description>Steve Jobs shared with us this month his thoughts on Flash:
 &amp;ldquo;Flash was created during the PC era &amp;mdash;for PCs and mice. Flash is a successful business for Adobe, and we can understand why they want to push it beyond PCs. But the mobile era is about low power devices, touch interfaces and open web standards &amp;mdash;all areas where Flash falls short.
The avalanche of media outlets offering their content for Apple’s mobile devices demonstrates that Flash is no longer necessary to watch video or consume any kind of web content.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>