<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archives on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/archives/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archives on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/archives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Me, but you, but me</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/28/me-but-you-but-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/28/me-but-you-but-me/</guid>
      <description>On May 28, 2010, Mark Pilgrim wrote the entry below on his weblog. He has since long been gone, but I am keeping this entry, named &amp;ldquo;Me, but you, but me,&amp;rdquo; which I liked very much. I really wish he would come back.
I’ve been active online for 9 years now. With one exception, nothing I’ve done online has brought me closer to making 25-year friends. Life online rewards breadth, not depth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Social</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/08/03/non-social/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/08/03/non-social/</guid>
      <description>Almost over two years ago I left Facebook. A few months ago I left LinkedIn and Twitter. Two weeks ago I left Google+. I also left Groupon (I don&amp;rsquo;t even know why I ever sign up for that junk!). Next is to leave here. I guess this is my way to pursuit happiness.
As Mark weblog is gone1 &amp;mdash;perhaps step 9 was, &amp;ldquo;Get rid of the weblog&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash; I enumerate what he wrote:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you have a weblog, read</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/06/09/if-you-have-a-weblog-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/06/09/if-you-have-a-weblog-read/</guid>
      <description>Recently, one of the weblogs I used to read often closed it&amp;rsquo;s doors. It was kind of sad to see it happen, but I am sure sooner or later it&amp;rsquo;s doors will open for something, even yet, more interesting. It is (or was?) Joaquin Bernal &amp;ldquo;bitacora&amp;rdquo;, a weblog in spanish.
I decided to poorly translate his last post, which I found quite informative and interesting. I say poorly translate, first because english is not my mother tongue, and second, because with every translation you loose a lot of meaning that can be only understood completely on the language the text was written.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>