<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kim on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/kim/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kim on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 11:04:35 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/kim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning the plate</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/12/cleaning-the-plate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 11:04:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/12/cleaning-the-plate/</guid>
      <description>My wife has always told me, &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t eat everything in your plate, leave something!&amp;rdquo; It is her believe, and her culture&amp;rsquo;s, that only poor people eats everything, and that if I do so, it will show I am dying of hunger, and thus, poor. If it were so, what&amp;rsquo;s wrong with being poor? Why will I leave food on the plate, food that I really like, to pretend what I am not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Winter Morning Small Talk</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/cold-winter-morning-small-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/cold-winter-morning-small-talk/</guid>
      <description>We have 36 Fahrenheit degrees this morning (2.2° Celsius). That is mighty cold for almost-always warm, sunny Florida. I stressed it to my child yesternight: he must wear warm clothes the next day. Reluctantly he said &amp;ldquo;OK&amp;rdquo;.
Then comes this morning, and the iMessages exchange look like this:
  Child :  &amp;ldquo;Mama is trying to make me wear an incredibly uncomfortable shirt and is yelling like a siren.&amp;rdquo;   Me :  &amp;ldquo;Why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas Tree Small Story</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/23/a-christmas-tree-small-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/23/a-christmas-tree-small-story/</guid>
      <description>Last year we had a plastic Christmas tree. Wife was not happy. This year she wanted a real one, so this morning the child and I went on the quest of getting it. Most families in the States will get a Christmas tree right after Thanksgiving, but I am used to get it the day before Christmas. Of course, if I wait for that day there will be none left. So it is today, or never1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas Tree</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/12/19/a-christmas-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/12/19/a-christmas-tree/</guid>
      <description>After a small, but heated battle, on whether or not to buy a real tree for Christmas (Kent and I said no, Kim said yes), Kent and Alyssa are now decorating a Fraser pine tree. I am sure you guessed who won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/16/happy-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/16/happy-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Today, a few years ago, a wonderful person &amp;ndash;at least very wonderful to me&amp;ndash; was born. A few years later I was lucky enough to meet her and become her husband.
Today Kim reaches a new milestone and it is with love that Kent I have to say: HAPPY BIRTHDAY MOM!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The three of us</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/05/the-three-of-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/05/the-three-of-us/</guid>
      <description>For one reason or another, we have very few pictures on which the three of us are present. Even today, went I tried to snap one I failed. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, photos we have, but none of them pleases us &amp;ndash;Kim&amp;ndash; to put online for the viewing audience (the very small one we have here).
A couple of days ago I took one photo that I decided to put online, because I like they way KM eyes look and because it represents the priority level in our family: kid goes first, then us.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>