<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tidbits on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/tidbits/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tidbits on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/tidbits/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Beat a Polygraph Test</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/03/how-to-beat-a-polygraph-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/03/how-to-beat-a-polygraph-test/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;He used to advise trainees to clench their anus but has since concluded that terrifying mental imagery works better.&amp;rdquo;
 When you get a control question, which is more general, envision the scariest thing you can in order to trigger physiological distress; the polygraph&amp;rsquo;s tubes around your chest measure breathing, the arm cuff monitors heart rate and electrodes attached to you fingertips detect perspiration. What is your greatest fear? Falling? Drowning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy 2015!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/12/31/happy-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/12/31/happy-2015/</guid>
      <description>Here we go again. Not complaining, as there is nothing to complain about. Just another year. It seems 2014 flew by quite fast, will you agree? Nevertheless, happy 2015 everyone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy MMXIV everyone!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/01/happy-mmxiv-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/01/happy-mmxiv-everyone/</guid>
      <description>Now that we have gone around the Sun one more time, we simply start doing it again. We don&amp;rsquo;t fool ourselves, it is not by choice. And with this new elliptical orbit we walk into age, which will lead, ultimately, to our demise. It is a simple concept.
Leaving the obvious behind, what&amp;rsquo;s left is to enjoy what we have. To try being nice to others, to the best of our abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/it-is-christmas-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/it-is-christmas-day/</guid>
      <description>One of the many things to look forward to each year is, of course, the end of year holidays. Christmas, Festivus, or whatever you call it, the end of December is always a special time. My only complain, and that might be yours too, is that it comes and goes so fast! Kent has finished opening his presents, and somehow it feels &amp;ldquo;it is all over.&amp;rdquo; But we waited the whole year for this!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming presidential elections</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/05/13/upcoming-presidential-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/05/13/upcoming-presidential-elections/</guid>
      <description>I really need to get into politics &amp;mdash;as much as I hate it&amp;mdash; to prepare for the upcoming presidential elections. I have the feeling that it’s going to be nasty&amp;hellip; as always.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unknown Unknowns</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/12/unknown-unknowns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/12/unknown-unknowns/</guid>
      <description>It is all about the unknown unknowns, of course!
 &amp;ldquo;There are known knowns; there are things we know we know. We also know there are known unknowns; that is to say we know there are some things we do not know. But there are also unknown unknowns &amp;mdash; the ones we don&amp;rsquo;t know we don&amp;rsquo;t know.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;mdash; Donald Rumsfeld, DoD News briefing.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safari 4 Beta</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/02/24/safari-4-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/02/24/safari-4-beta/</guid>
      <description>Safari 4 Beta is out and it is rocking. Apple has adopted (copied) quite a bit from Chrome interface and I have to say the browser looks and behaves awesomely under Windows 7.
But, why bore you with senseless praise? Go download it, and see it for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winds of change</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/11/08/winds-of-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/11/08/winds-of-change/</guid>
      <description>It seems winds of change had blown, brought by the mid-term elections. And yes, change was (is) what we needed. I am cautiously happy. After all, it is politics what we are talking about here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob Muglia on Longhorn</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/21/bob-muglia-on-longhorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/21/bob-muglia-on-longhorn/</guid>
      <description>Dreaming of Longhorn.
 &amp;ldquo;When I think of Linux, I don&amp;rsquo;t think about it as our competitor. I think about Linux as a technology that is used by our competitors to build competitive offerings.&amp;rdquo; Very different from what Steve Ballmer and Bill Gates have been saying but Muglia says &amp;ldquo;he&amp;rsquo;s trying to teach them a thing or two.&amp;rdquo;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software gentlemans</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/21/software-gentlemans/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/21/software-gentlemans/</guid>
      <description>Guidelines to help fight deceptive Internet software. &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;We will strive to distribute our software only in bundles where all applications meet the above guidelines&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>