<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>911 on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/911/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 911 on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/911/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>September 11th</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/09/11/september-11th/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/09/11/september-11th/</guid>
      <description>We will never forget.
Today, eight years ago, a group of humans, guided by a political agenda, a deep hatred towards the United States, and a mad religious fanaticism slammed airplanes into the World Trade Center, destroying the Twin Towers, damaging other buildings, and killing almost 3,000 people. A second airplane hit The Pentagon, and a third crashed near Pennsylvania after some of its passengers and flight crew attempted to retake control of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We remember: Six years ago</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/09/11/we-remember-six-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/09/11/we-remember-six-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>Today, six years ago, a group of animals belonging to the human race decided to take away thousands of innocent lives by destroying the Twin Towers (see World Trade Center). Let us not to forget how stupid they were, how criminal they were, how inhuman they were. Let us remember our brothers and sisters who died that day. For me The Towers stand tall. They always will.
September 11th, 2001: We will never forget!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembrance</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/09/11/remembrance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/09/11/remembrance/</guid>
      <description>Today, three years ago, a group of animals belonging to the human race decided to take away thousands of innocent lives by destroying the Twin Towers (see World TradeCenter). Let us not to forget how stupid they were, how criminal they were, how non human they were. Let us remember our brothers and sisters who died that day. For me The Towers stand tall. They always will.
September 11th, 2001: We will never forget!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>