<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ebay on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/ebay/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ebay on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/ebay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Selling iPhone</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/10/13/selling-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/10/13/selling-iphone/</guid>
      <description>In an effort to start saving money towards an Android based device (would love HTC Hero), I am selling my 2G 16GB iPhone. As the eBay listing reads, it is a very well kept, 2G 16GB iPhone, unlocked and jailbroken. No scratches, no blemishes. Bid starts at $1, no reserve. Yes, $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eBay sues Craigslist</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/23/ebay-sues-craigslist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/23/ebay-sues-craigslist/</guid>
      <description>Referring to an eBay Press release:
 Tainted Love &amp;ndash; We are surprised and disappointed by Ebay&amp;rsquo;s unfounded allegations, which came to us out of the blue, without any attempt to engage in a dialogue with us.
Coming from a shareholder that views craigslist as a prime competitor, filing suit without so much as mentioning these assertions beforehand seems unethical, and hints at ulterior motives.
 Why they ever got in business with eBay is beyond my understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ebay feedback blackmail</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/07/05/ebay-feedback-blackmail/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/07/05/ebay-feedback-blackmail/</guid>
      <description>If you do business on Ebay, whether you are power seller with your own store there or simply a John Doe such as myself, please follow the following etiquette:  If you are selling, and the item(s) you sold get paid (right away or in a timely manner), leave your feedback right away. No need to wait till the buyer leaves his. Doing so is bad, really bad. If you are buying, wait till the item arrives and then leave a feedback accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>