<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>politics on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/categories/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in politics on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 21:19:21 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/categories/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Meltdown</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/another-meltdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 21:19:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/another-meltdown/</guid>
      <description>Someone is having another meltdown.
 The Mueller probe should never have been started in that there was no collusion and there was no crime. It was based on fraudulent activities and a Fake Dossier paid for by Crooked Hillary and the DNC, and improperly used in FISA COURT for surveillance of my campaign. WITCH HUNT!
 😂
Now, there is a background for his latest fit.
Yesterday, 16 March, Jeff Sessions fired Andrew McCabe, the FBI deputy director.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Goes After Trump Org</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/15/mueller-goes-after-trump-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 19:50:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/15/mueller-goes-after-trump-org/</guid>
      <description>I have disliked other presidents in the past, for actions taken while they were in the office that I — and many others — considered stupid, crazy, or just plain wrong. My dislike for the current president eclipses any of my previous. I voted for Hillary, and wrongly predicted that she would win the presidency.
Today news, although perhaps inconsequential, brings joy to an otherwise political nightmare.
 The special counsel, Robert S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unalloyed irony</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/12/08/unalloyed-irony/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 13:14:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/12/08/unalloyed-irony/</guid>
      <description>Soon to be ex-Senator Al Franken announced, on an emotional speech, his resignation yesterday. He is leaving the Senate after been accused of sexual misconduct.
 &amp;ldquo;I, of all people, am aware that there is some irony in the fact that I am leaving while a man who has bragged on tape about his history of sexual assault sits in the Oval Office, and a man who has repeatedly preyed on young girls campaigns for the Senate with the full support of his party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A downright moron</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/10/05/a-downright-moron/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 05:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/10/05/a-downright-moron/</guid>
      <description>Henry Louis Mencken wrote an article on the Baltimore Sun, on 26 July, 1920, that amongst other things read:
 As democracy is perfected, the office represents, more and more closely, the inner soul of the people. We move toward a lofty ideal. On some great and glorious day the plain folks of the land will reach their heart&amp;rsquo;s desire at last, and the White House will be adorned by a downright moron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comey Sacking</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/05/11/comey-sacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 16:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/05/11/comey-sacking/</guid>
      <description>This is, at least for me, completely surreal. It is not only that Trump sacked the FBI director &amp;mdash; who arguably helped him getting elected President &amp;mdash; while he was conducting an investigation on Trump&amp;rsquo;s presidential campaign, but the way he wrote the sacking letter (I emphasised):
 Dear Director Comey:
I have received the attached letters from the Attorney General and Deputy Attorney General of the United States recommending your dismissal as the Director of the Federal Bureau of Investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Intelligent Person</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/27/an-intelligent-person/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 19:59:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/27/an-intelligent-person/</guid>
      <description>From Twitter:
 The most amazing thing about the Trump presidency is that it’s made GWB look like a reasonably intelligent person.
&amp;mdash; Derek Powazek (@fraying) February 27, 2017
 And from The New York Times:
 Former President George W. Bush said Monday &amp;ldquo;we all need answers&amp;rdquo; on the extent of contact between President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s team and the Russian government, and didn&amp;rsquo;t rule out the idea that a special prosecutor could be necessary to lead an investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Silence of the Hacks</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/18/the-silence-of-the-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 21:32:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/18/the-silence-of-the-hacks/</guid>
      <description>There is a reason why I subscribed to the digital edition of The New York Times. Its journalists are superb; it is a paper I trust, and have found to be veridical after cross referencing the news they post with other major, equally trusted, news sources.
From yesterday&amp;rsquo;s edition (some emphasis mine):
 The story so far: A foreign dictator intervened on behalf of a U.S. presidential candidate — and that candidate won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incapable of Serving</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/14/incapable-of-serving/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 05:49:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/14/incapable-of-serving/</guid>
      <description>From the opinion pages of The New York Times yesterday, 13 of February, 2017, also appearing in print today. Some emphasis mine.
 Mr. Trump’s speech and actions demonstrate an inability to tolerate views different from his own, leading to rage reactions. His words and behavior suggest a profound inability to empathize. Individuals with these traits distort reality to suit their psychological state, attacking facts and those who convey them (journalists, scientists).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard to Believe</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/09/hard-to-believe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 14:30:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/09/hard-to-believe/</guid>
      <description>If you hear or read this somewhere else &amp;mdash; whether on social media, or via your clueless uncle Olaf &amp;mdash; you will find it hard, if not impossible, to believe. Now, finding it on Reuters is a different story.
 In his first call as president with Russian leader Vladimir Putin, Donald Trump denounced a treaty that caps U.S. and Russian deployment of nuclear warheads as a bad deal for the United States, according to two U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unpresidential</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/01/12/unpresidential/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 20:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/01/12/unpresidential/</guid>
      <description>Not presidential at all.
 “President-elect Donald J. Trump’s aides often cite his appearances at professional wrestling matches as an inspiration for his outsize political speaking style, and his buoyantly belligerent news conference in New York on Wednesday proved he has no plans to betray his brawler’s roots in the service of seeming more presidential.”
&amp;mdash; New York Times
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I was wrong</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/11/09/i-was-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/11/09/i-was-wrong/</guid>
      <description>Back in October 5th, 2015, I wrote a prediction, which I saved in a file for which I posted a hash. I predicted that Hillary Clinton would win the United States presidential elections. Sadly, I was wrong.
I really do not have much else to say. I am sorry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders keeps fighting</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/06/09/bernie-sanders-keeps-fighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/06/09/bernie-sanders-keeps-fighting/</guid>
      <description>Bernie Sanders has had a good run. Yet numbers are pilled against him, and he should know it. After all he said he was &amp;ldquo;pretty good in arithmetic.&amp;rdquo; Hillary has beaten him, and the right and honorable thing for him to do is to call it quits.
 “If, on November 8th of this year, Hillary Clinton is elected President, we will have only begun to fight,” Sanders told a packed rally in San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Dangerous Precedent</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/02/17/a-dangerous-precedent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/02/17/a-dangerous-precedent/</guid>
      <description>The United States government demanded that Apple weakens the security on iOS. Tim Cook, Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, replied.
 Rather than asking for legislative action through Congress, the FBI is proposing an unprecedented use of the All Writs Act of 1789 to justify an expansion of its authority.
The government would have us remove security features and add new capabilities to the operating system, allowing a passcode to be input electronically. This would make it easier to unlock an iPhone by “brute force,” trying thousands or millions of combinations with the speed of a modern computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumping Dollars Left and Right</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/11/02/dumping-dollars-left-and-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/11/02/dumping-dollars-left-and-right/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;DOD charged the American taxpayer $43 million for what is likely the world&amp;rsquo;s most expensive gas station.&amp;rdquo;
That&amp;rsquo;s what Special Inspector General John F. Sopko found when he looked at the construction of a natural gas station in Sheberghan, Afghanistan.
According to the report, at most that station should have cost about $500,000. But in this case, the Department of Defense&amp;rsquo;s Task Force for Stability and Business Operations awarded Central Asian Engineering a contract to build the station for a little under $3 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Two Child Policy</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/29/chinas-two-child-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/29/chinas-two-child-policy/</guid>
      <description>This one is worth documenting, as it doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen every day. As a matter of fact, it hasn&amp;rsquo;t happened for over three decades.
 &amp;ldquo;It is the latest twist in the most ambitious and ruthless social-engineering program ever undertaken by a modern state: Beijing announced Thursday that the Chinese Communist Party will officially abandon its one-child policy. Yet it has no plans to relinquish authority over its subjects’ birth patterns; rather, Beijing has simply changed the ration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russians and Syria</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/08/russians-and-syria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/08/russians-and-syria/</guid>
      <description>We bomb. From the air, from the ground, from afar, from ships. And so do the Russians now. We target what we believe are terrorists, sometimes we miss. Russians are doing the same now.
We removed Saddam, and the Taliban, just to mention two, and that created&amp;mdash;or increased&amp;mdash;a mess that continues until today. The Russian&amp;rsquo;s tactic is different, they are targeting both, the terrorists fighting against the &amp;ldquo;official&amp;rdquo; regime, and those which we are targeting as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/prediction/</guid>
      <description>Next year we will have our Presidential Elections. Everyone knows that, of course, because the politicians have been campaining for almost a year now.
Below is the name of a file with my winner&amp;rsquo;s prediction on the United States 2016 Presidential Elections written on it. It is a hash algorithm of a file containing a sentence with my prediction. I will refer to this post the day after elections, as the results are known.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presidential Elections 2016</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/27/presidential-elections-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/27/presidential-elections-2016/</guid>
      <description>Back in 2011 was the last time I wrote about Presidential Elections (2012). I can&amp;rsquo;t believe we are about to get into them again. In 2012 I knew exactly who to vote for, but in 2016, with the selection we have thus far, I really have no idea about who is the most viable&amp;mdash;if there is one. Certainly not this one:
 Question: &amp;ldquo;How will you bring back the American Dream?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huckabee offers his Support</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/02/huckabee-offers-his-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/02/huckabee-offers-his-support/</guid>
      <description>Mike Huckabee, a christian pastor turned politician has offered his support to the Court clerk in Kentucky who, against Supreme Court order, refuses to issue gay marriage licenses.
 &amp;ldquo;I spoke with Kim Davis this morning to offer my prayers and support. I let her know how proud I am of her for not abandoning her religious convictions and standing strong for religious liberty. She is showing more courage and humility than just about any federal office holder in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming presidential elections</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/05/13/upcoming-presidential-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/05/13/upcoming-presidential-elections/</guid>
      <description>I really need to get into politics &amp;mdash;as much as I hate it&amp;mdash; to prepare for the upcoming presidential elections. I have the feeling that it’s going to be nasty&amp;hellip; as always.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. credit rating lowered</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/04/18/us-credit-rating-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/04/18/us-credit-rating-down/</guid>
      <description>It seems our credit “worthiness” (and hence our capabilities to acquired loans in the future) has diminished:
 S&amp;amp;P maintained its ‘AAA/A-1+’ credit rating on U.S. sovereign debt, saying the nation’s “highly diversified” economy and “effective monetary policies” have helped support growth.
But the ratings agency lowered its outlook for America’s long-term credit rating to “negative” from “stable,” based on the uncertain political debate around the nation’s fiscal problems.
— CNN Money</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glad I am not in North Korea</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/12/03/glad-i-am-not-in-north-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/12/03/glad-i-am-not-in-north-korea/</guid>
      <description>From the Wall Street Journal:
 North Korea said on Monday it would issue new won currency this week that would in effect lop two zeros off the old &amp;mdash;requiring 1,000-won bills, for example, to be exchanged for 10-won notes with, theoretically, the same buying power.
It said it would limit the amount of old currency it would accept in exchange, to the equivalent of about $40 worth at unofficial exchange rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From today&#39;s Barack&#39;s email</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/07/from-todays-baracks-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/07/from-todays-baracks-email/</guid>
      <description>News broke this morning that Senator Clinton made three separate loans to her campaign in the past 30 days &amp;mdash;including one as recently as Monday.
These loans total more than $6.4 million, which combined with her previous personal loans, add up to at least $11.4 million she&amp;rsquo;s loaned her campaign since February.
A spokesman said she may continue to &amp;ldquo;loan the campaign additional money out of her jointly-held assets&amp;rdquo; &amp;mdash;which include more than $100 million in income since her husband left the White House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary speaks like Bush</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/06/hillary-speaks-like-bush/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/06/hillary-speaks-like-bush/</guid>
      <description>Obama accuses Clinton of using the language of Bush on Iran
 In the sharpest attack, Obama said that Clinton&amp;rsquo;s threat to &amp;ldquo;totally obliterate&amp;rdquo; Iran should it attempt a nuclear attack on Israel was inappropriate. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s not the language we need right now. It&amp;rsquo;s language that&amp;rsquo;s reflective of George Bush,&amp;rdquo; he said.
Obama said it was time to get away from a foreign policy of &amp;ldquo;bluster and sabre-rattling and tough talk&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia warned over Georgia move</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/30/nato-warns-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/30/nato-warns-russia/</guid>
      <description>Russia warned over Georgia move
 Nato has warned Russia that its recent troop build-up in Georgia&amp;rsquo;s two breakaway regions undermines its neighbour&amp;rsquo;s territorial integrity.
 Would everyone chill out, please? This time Russians, specially. I think a &amp;ldquo;Back off, and chill&amp;rdquo; behavior is mandatory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinton wins in Pennsylvania, projected</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/22/clinton-wins-pennsylvania/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/22/clinton-wins-pennsylvania/</guid>
      <description>Clinton wins in Pennsylvania &amp;ndash; NBC News projected Tuesday night that Sen. Hillary Rodham Clinton had won Pennsylvania&amp;rsquo;s presidential primary, a victory that analysts said she had to have if she were to remain a credible candidate for the Democratic nomination.
 I find it incredible how she has been able to get as many votes as she has. But after seeing McCain take over the Republican&amp;rsquo;s vote I should have expected anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linuxers for Obama</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/21/linuxers-for-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/21/linuxers-for-obama/</guid>
      <description>Linuxers for Obama &amp;ndash; LinuxersForObama is a campaign for all Free and Open Source Software advocates to contribute to the Obama campaign. Sorry for the shorthand &amp;ldquo;LinuxForObama&amp;rdquo;, I know it should have been &amp;ldquo;FLOSSGNUX11BSDApacheMySQLForObama&amp;rdquo;, but I went for short and simple.
Hopefully team LinuxForObama can do some nice fund raising for Obama and we can settle once and for all the argument about which operating system is the best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics for sports</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/10/olympics-for-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/10/olympics-for-sports/</guid>
      <description>Olympics Games relate to sport. The Olympic Games is where the World most accomplished athletes and teams compete for medals, for the win. Making the Olympics Games a political chess board goes against what Olympic Games are all about. And it is a nasty thing to do.
We&amp;mdash;as in the U.S.A.&amp;mdash;are not being fair with China. Our government and our politicians (including Presidential aspirants) are all playing politics with the Olympics for their own political advantage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk radio after 3PM</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/20/talk-radio-after-3pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/20/talk-radio-after-3pm/</guid>
      <description>I used to listen to talk radio after 3PM. I listened at the Sean Hannity show, on WDBO 580AM. I just realized yesterday his &amp;lsquo;show&amp;rsquo; is a radio political &amp;ndash;and biased&amp;ndash; version of &amp;ldquo;The Jerry Springer&amp;rdquo; show. Full of junk, inaccuracies, lies sprinkled with some trues, repetitive. I should have stopped at junk.
And I listened for the entertainment, for the laugh it gives every once in a while, and as a background noise on my way home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vicepresident? No, thank you</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/11/vicepresident-no-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/11/vicepresident-no-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Obama spurns double ticket hints
 &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know how somebody who is in second place is offering the vice presidency to somebody who is in first place,&amp;rdquo; he told a rally in Columbus, Mississippi.
&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t want anybody here thinking that somehow &amp;lsquo;well, you know, maybe I can get both.&amp;rsquo; Don&amp;rsquo;t think that way. You have to make a choice in this election.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not running for vice president. I am running for president of the United States of America,&amp;rdquo; he added.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overturning the unconstitutional</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/08/overturning-the-unconstitutional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/08/overturning-the-unconstitutional/</guid>
      <description>Overturning nightmares
 As president, he said he would ask his attorney general &amp;ldquo;to review every executive order&amp;rdquo; of the Bush administration. &amp;ldquo;We are going to overturn those that were unconstitutional. We are going to overturn those that are unnecessary.&amp;rdquo;
 I don&amp;rsquo;t think it is a slogan, I don&amp;rsquo;t think they are empty words. Yes, we can!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John McCain on religion</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/07/john-mccain-on-religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/07/john-mccain-on-religion/</guid>
      <description>John McCain on religion.
 &amp;ldquo;I just have to say in all candor that since this nation was founded primarily on Christian principles&amp;hellip;personally, I prefer someone who I know who has a solid grounding in my faith&amp;hellip;I think the number one issue people should make [in the] selection of the President of the United States is, &amp;lsquo;Will this person carry on in the Judeo Christian principled tradition that has made this nation the greatest experiment in the history of mankind?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That 3:00AM call</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/07/that-300am-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/07/that-300am-call/</guid>
      <description>Comment posted on Larry David: On the Red Phone
 &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s 3AM and your children are sleeping. But the phone is ringing. It&amp;rsquo;s your mortgage lender, calling to let you know that you are 180 days late on your payment for that crazy mortgage you agreed to. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, because your phone was disconnected a long time ago. But no worries, Hillary Clinton is working late, at some desk somewhere, doing a Sudoku puzzle maybe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bush endorses McCain</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/06/bush-endorses-mccain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/06/bush-endorses-mccain/</guid>
      <description>Bush endorses McCain in US race
 US President George W Bush has endorsed John McCain&amp;rsquo;s White House bid after the Vietnam veteran sealed the Republican nomination on Tuesday.
Mr Bush said his one-time rival would be a president with the &amp;ldquo;determination to defeat an enemy and a heart big enough to love those who hurt&amp;rdquo;.
 Now you know who not to vote for. Clear, right? Any questions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The $2 Trillion Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/05/the-2-trillion-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/05/the-2-trillion-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>The $2 Trillion Nightmare
 &amp;ldquo;Normally, when America goes to war, nonessential spending programs are reduced to make room in the budget for the higher costs of the war. Individual programs that benefit specific constituencies are sacrificed for the common good &amp;hellip; And taxes have never been cut during a major American war. For example, President Eisenhower adamantly resisted pressure from Senate Republicans for a tax cut during the Korean War.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I just hope...</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/04/i-just-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/04/i-just-hope/</guid>
      <description>I just hope she doesn&amp;rsquo;t win. I am talking about politics, if you are following the news, you know who I am talking about. Hard not to follow politics these days, but you never know.
Yes, I hope she looses.
Update: She didn&amp;rsquo;t loose. She won three states. Obama still leads on delegates. There is still hope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Super Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/02/07/after-super-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/02/07/after-super-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s Super Tuesday speech.
A rather lengthy, yet inspiring speech. This man has charisma, something I have not seeing on the rest. I like him. I think he would do a good President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What counts as an issue...</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/02/01/what-counts-as-an-issue-in-the-clinton-obama-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/02/01/what-counts-as-an-issue-in-the-clinton-obama-race/</guid>
      <description>George Lakoff: What Counts as an &amp;ldquo;Issue&amp;rdquo; In the Clinton-Obama Race?
 There is a reason that Obama recently spoke of Reagan. Reagan understood that you win elections by drawing support from independents and the opposite side. He understood what unified the country so that he could lead it according to his vision. His vision was a radical conservative one, a vision devastating for the country and contradicted by his economic policies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I will vote</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/01/29/i-will-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/01/29/i-will-vote/</guid>
      <description>I will vote today, on Florida&amp;rsquo;s primary elections. I am registered republican and, hence, I can only vote for a running republican. As such, I will vote for Ron Paul. On the elections day, I shall vote for Barack Obama (I know this implies that he will win the nomination for the Democratic Party. I hope &amp;mdash; and wish &amp;mdash; he does) for President, Democrat.
Please, whatever State you are in, vote as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The truth is useless</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/01/14/the-truth-is-useless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/01/14/the-truth-is-useless/</guid>
      <description>On Digg, someone submitted, Jeb Bush, the truth is useless, to which a reader commented:
Digg - Jeb Bush: &amp;lsquo;The truth is useless&amp;rsquo;
 [&amp;hellip;] This is not just the Bushes, though. This is human nature. This sort of thing develops when you elevate yourself to stratospheric heights and start to believe your own hype. It happens to Hollywood actors, musicians, moguls, models, magicians, shop managers, morticians, bankers, soldiers, physicians&amp;hellip; Even the guy temporarily assigned to run the night shift cleaning crew while the regular dick is out on sick leave starts to walk more proudly thinking he best be listened to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You are a prisoner, keep quiet!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/27/you-are-a-prisoner-keep-quiet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/27/you-are-a-prisoner-keep-quiet/</guid>
      <description>U.S. Seeks Silence on CIA Prisons
 The Bush administration has told a federal judge that terrorism suspects held in secret CIA prisons should not be allowed to reveal details of the &amp;ldquo;alternative interrogation methods&amp;rdquo; that their captors used to get them to talk.
The government says in new court filings that those interrogation methods are now among the nation&amp;rsquo;s most sensitive national security secrets and that their release &amp;ndash; even to the detainees&amp;rsquo; own attorneys &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;could reasonably be expected to cause extremely grave damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ron Paul on War and Foreign Policy</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/17/ron-paul-on-war-and-foreign-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/17/ron-paul-on-war-and-foreign-policy/</guid>
      <description>Ron Paul: War and Foreign Policy
 We can continue to fund and fight no-win police actions around the globe, or we can refocus on securing America and bring the troops home. No war should ever be fought without a declaration of war voted upon by the Congress, as required by the Constitution.
Under no circumstances should the U.S. again go to war as the result of a resolution that comes from an unelected, foreign body, such as the United Nations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primary elections</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/13/primary-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/13/primary-elections/</guid>
      <description>It is my desire that the U.S. primary elections were available to everyone, to vote for anyone, regardless of the political part affiliation 1. In fact, I would not make a requirement to affiliate to a specific party at all.
Why? If I am registered, for example, democrat, but I see that the choices of the Democratic Party are not &amp;ldquo;presidential&amp;rdquo; material, then I would like to be able to vote (even at the primaries) for the best of the other party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a load of crock!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/11/06/what-a-load-of-crock/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/11/06/what-a-load-of-crock/</guid>
      <description>If it weren&amp;rsquo;t enough that you have to go through airport hell every time you must take an airplane, some people is trying to cash in, and they are using terrorism to their advantage. Enter Clear card.
From their CEO (read while playing patriotic music on the background, waving an American flag) :
 &amp;ldquo;I started Verified Identity Pass with a simple idea: In the post 9-11 era we have to take new measures to protect ourselves yet not destroy our way of life by strangling the free flow of people and commerce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winds of change</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/11/08/winds-of-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/11/08/winds-of-change/</guid>
      <description>It seems winds of change had blown, brought by the mid-term elections. And yes, change was (is) what we needed. I am cautiously happy. After all, it is politics what we are talking about here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electoral signs: my approach</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/11/06/electoral-signs-my-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/11/06/electoral-signs-my-approach/</guid>
      <description>On every single election &amp;ldquo;season&amp;rdquo; I can see a multitude of signs and advertising that often remains until &amp;ldquo;natural decay&amp;rdquo; or the city gets them removed, 6 months &amp;ndash;or more&amp;ndash; after the elections are over. That really makes me mad. I would make it part of the process of being elected: if you win, you cannot take over office until you clean up all your garbage. And if they don&amp;rsquo;t, a hefty fine gets applied, they get ridiculed and their seat is up for claiming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Military Commissions Act of 2006</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/10/20/the-military-commissions-act-of-2006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/10/20/the-military-commissions-act-of-2006/</guid>
      <description>David Wu, democratic congressman representing the state of Oregon reportedly said, referring to the Military Commissions Act of 2006 recently signed into law:
 Let us say that my wife, who is here in the gallery with us tonight, a sixth generation Oregonian, is walking by the friendly, local military base and is picked up as an unlawful enemy combatant. What is her recourse? She says, I am a U.S. citizen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three years ago</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/10/18/three-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/10/18/three-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>In light of everything happening in Asia, specifically on the Korean peninsula, I remembered what I wrote three years ago, more or less. It took them three years to develop something that can be tested (a bomb), or were they working already on it for a long time and our intelligence was &amp;lsquo;asleep&amp;rsquo;? If it was the first, they could already have a way to deliver it overseas, and if it is the second, we may not even know it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chocolate Imbecile</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/01/18/the-chocolate-imbecile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/01/18/the-chocolate-imbecile/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t get it out of mind. How a person can be so idiotic? The major of New Orleans, Ray Nagin said, among other things:
 &amp;ldquo;Surely God is mad at America. He sent us hurricane after hurricane after hurricane, and it&amp;rsquo;s destroyed and put stress on this country&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;Surely he doesn&amp;rsquo;t approve of us being in Iraq under false pretenses.&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;But surely he is upset at black America also.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Britons, our brothers and sisters</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/07/08/britons-our-brothers-and-sisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/07/08/britons-our-brothers-and-sisters/</guid>
      <description>Once again some (insert some lots of bad words here) terrorists have tried to affect the civilized world by detonating bombs and killing innocent people. They&amp;rsquo;ve cause pain, allright, but their final goal has failed, as it will always do. Britons are not afraid, civilized world is more united because of those dumb (some more bad words here).
We are more united than ever. United Kingdom of England and North Ireland, all our love and support from the other side of the ocean!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mention two</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/07/06/mention-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/07/06/mention-two/</guid>
      <description>My parents are visiting. They got here July 3rd and on July 4th dad was telling me they needed to leave the coming Friday. My old people are really something, but that is not what I wanted to post about.
My father talks, continuously, a lot. He will start with a simple answer to a question I asked and go on into various topics and anecdotes that seem not to have an end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downing Street Memo</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/17/downing-street-memo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/17/downing-street-memo/</guid>
      <description>I have known about this since it was released to the News media, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t comment about it here. I am providing a link to the contents of the Memo (pretty small read, I assure you) as they showed on the Times Online on May 1st, 2005. Draw your conclusions. I just want to quote a few parts of it. The document itself says it all, really.
 &amp;hellip;C reported on his recent talks in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA PATRIOT Act</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/17/usa-patriot-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/17/usa-patriot-act/</guid>
      <description>A lot has been said and written about the &amp;#8220;Uniting and Strengthening America by Providing Appropriate Tools Required to Intercept and Obstruct Terrorism Act&amp;#8221;, commonly known as USA PATRIOT Act, but they are quite diverse interpretations &amp;#8212;some biased&amp;#8212;, mainly because the whole Act is written on 300 pages of legalese. Recently I found the Electronic Frontier Foundation page about such Act, which sums it up in the following points (as far as why should we care):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No more Freedom Fries?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/13/no-more-freedom-fries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/13/no-more-freedom-fries/</guid>
      <description>It was really interesting to read on the BBC News:
 A pro-Iraq war US congressman who campaigned for French fries to be renamed &amp;ldquo;freedom fries&amp;rdquo; is now calling for US troops to return home from Iraq. Republican Representative Walter Jones is to introduce legislation demanding a timetable for the withdrawal.
[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;I just feel that the reason of going in for weapons of mass destruction, the ability of the Iraqis to make a nuclear weapon, that&amp;rsquo;s all been proven that it was never there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chosen by God?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/12/chosen-by-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/12/chosen-by-god/</guid>
      <description>I have heard in several occasions, and read quite a few times, that President George W. Bush believes he was chosen (appointed) by God to be our President. God, supposedly, wants nothing but well being for us all, right? Then I would like to know what Mr. Bush is doing to end the killing, abuse and hunger (among other things) from places like Central, South America and Caribbean, Africa and great parts of Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the spanish elections</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/03/20/about-the-spanish-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/03/20/about-the-spanish-elections/</guid>
      <description>The overturn of the elections in Spain was driven by several factors. Leftists accused the PP (Popular Party) of lying and one have to assume that socialists voters believed it. Aznar got Spain into a war that was considered by many as non-needed, following an agresive and self-centered ideology.
The truth is that while the war was out of spanish campgrounds everything was limited to talks about veracity of the (war) facts, justice and geostrategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money for your hobby?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/09/15/money-for-your-hobby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/09/15/money-for-your-hobby/</guid>
      <description>I have seeing an increasing amount of weblogs that are, either running Google AdSense to make money or asking for donations. Does that works? I mean, does Google AdSense can be enough for someone to actually make a living out if it? And, on a related token, would the amount of &amp;ldquo;donations&amp;rdquo; add up enough to pay the rent? I am curious.
On politics. I am a republican although I am not sure if I will vote like so on the next Presidential elections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The lack of evidence</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/06/06/the-lack-of-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/06/06/the-lack-of-evidence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am proudly a republican. I did not vote on the last presidential election for a technicality: I moved from one county to another a week before elections and I lost my right to vote, just because of bad timing. But I would have voted for Mr. Bush.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also supported the war against Saddam Hussein and his army, because I think the world is better off without a man like him on power. I did not care whether or not he had &amp;ldquo;weapons of mass destruction&amp;rdquo;, I knew the guy history and that was enough justification for me. But, if I remember well, the war was sold, &lt;b&gt;mainly&lt;/b&gt;, on the existence of WMD, whilst it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t. We had thousands of other reasons to go to war against that mad man. Why WMD were made the &amp;ldquo;key&amp;rdquo; reason I do not know. And now we have a problem in our hands.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuclear Blackmail, North Korean Style</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/01/21/nuclear-blackmail-north-korean-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/01/21/nuclear-blackmail-north-korean-style/</guid>
      <description>Looks like the only thing a poor country, or a country in deep economical problems, has to do to turn things around and get all major powers striving to come up with a solution &amp;mdash;which in the case I am talking about is recognition, non-aggression treaty and, most important of all, economical aid&amp;mdash; is to publicly say it is going to build a nuclear bomb or that is in the process to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iraq, are we going to war?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/01/18/iraq-are-we-going-to-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2003 18:14:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/01/18/iraq-are-we-going-to-war/</guid>
      <description>If you have been following the news you already know about the Iraq situation. You might still be asking yourself why are we building up such a massive military power in the area, that is, Middle East. Right, you are not questioning that, since you know the answer: we are going to war. What you might be thinking is whether or not we should be there, should we care. All valid questions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>