<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>movies on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in movies on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Martian</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/10/the-martian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/10/the-martian/</guid>
      <description>We just came from seeing the movie &amp;ldquo;The Martian.&amp;rdquo; Minus the obvious, very predictable, Hollywood scenes, the movie was quite alright. It made me wish I could live to see the first few missions to the Red Planet. Being the selfless guy that I am, thought, I would be willing to settle if my child gets to see them instead.
While on the topic of movies, and theaters, it is amazing how expensive it is to see a movie these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sands of Time</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/04/the-sands-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/04/the-sands-of-time/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It is said that some lives are linked across time connected by an ancient calling that echoes through the ages. Destiny.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;mdash; Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time
 I do not believe on such thing as destiny, but the line above from the movie is certainly touching. The movie itself is quite nice. Last night we watched it for the fourth time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is All around Us</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/29/it-is-all-around-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/29/it-is-all-around-us/</guid>
      <description>Love. It really is.
 &amp;ldquo;Whenever I get gloomy with the state of the world, I think about the arrivals gate at Heathrow Airport. General opinion&amp;rsquo;s starting to make out that we live in a world of hatred and greed, but I don&amp;rsquo;t see that. It seems to me that love is everywhere. Often it&amp;rsquo;s not particularly dignified or newsworthy, but it&amp;rsquo;s always there &amp;mdash; fathers and sons, mothers and daughters, husbands and wives, boyfriends, girlfriends, old friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies to Watch during Christmas</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/movies-to-watch-during-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/movies-to-watch-during-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Christmas is not the same without watching certain movies. The ones that are always a must for me are &amp;ldquo;National Lampoon&amp;rsquo;s European Vacation&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;National Lampoon&amp;rsquo;s Christmas Vacation&amp;quot;. As I type this I am getting ready to watch them both. Those are the ones to laugh to tears and have fun. The other favorite one &amp;ndash;please don&amp;rsquo;t hate me&amp;ndash; is &amp;ldquo;The Sound of Music.&amp;rdquo; There is something about it that just does it for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clan of the Cave Bear</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/24/clan-of-the-cave-bear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/24/clan-of-the-cave-bear/</guid>
      <description>Just saw the Clan of the Cave Bearmovie, for the first time, on it&amp;rsquo;s entirety. Great movie. Touching; got me a knot on the throat in more than one occasion. I think it is a sad movie, and brought up many memories. Sometimes movies, like music, have that effect. Sometimes it is just us, and how our mind works.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>