<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>obama on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/obama/</link>
    <description>Recent content in obama on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/obama/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary speaks like Bush</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/06/hillary-speaks-like-bush/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/06/hillary-speaks-like-bush/</guid>
      <description>Obama accuses Clinton of using the language of Bush on Iran In the sharpest attack, Obama said that Clinton&amp;rsquo;s threat to &amp;ldquo;totally obliterate&amp;rdquo; Iran should it attempt a nuclear attack on Israel was inappropriate. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s not the language we need right now. It&amp;rsquo;s language that&amp;rsquo;s reflective of George Bush,&amp;rdquo; he said.
Obama said it was time to get away from a foreign policy of &amp;ldquo;bluster and sabre-rattling and tough talk&amp;rdquo;. He reminded Clinton that she had urged caution in terms of speculating about Iran on the campaign trail &amp;ldquo;yet a few days before an election she&amp;rsquo;s willing to use that language&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinton wins in Pennsylvania, projected</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/22/clinton-wins-pennsylvania/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/22/clinton-wins-pennsylvania/</guid>
      <description>Clinton wins in Pennsylvania&amp;ndash; NBC News projected Tuesday night that Sen. Hillary Rodham Clinton had won Pennsylvania&amp;rsquo;s presidential primary, a victory that analysts said she had to have if she were to remain a credible candidate for the Democratic nomination.
 I find it incredible how she has been able to get as many votes as she has. But after seeing McCain take over the Republican&amp;rsquo;s vote I should have expected anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linuxers for Obama</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/21/linuxers-for-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/21/linuxers-for-obama/</guid>
      <description>Linuxers for Obama&amp;ndash; LinuxersForObama is a campaign for all Free and Open Source Software advocates to contribute to the Obama campaign. Sorry for the shorthand &amp;ldquo;LinuxForObama&amp;rdquo;, I know it should have been &amp;ldquo;FLOSSGNUX11BSDApacheMySQLForObama&amp;rdquo;, but I went for short and simple.
Hopefully team LinuxForObama can do some nice fund raising for Obama and we can settle once and for all the argument about which operating system is the best.
 I just donated a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vicepresident? No, thank you</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/11/vicepresident-no-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/11/vicepresident-no-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Obama spurns double ticket hints &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know how somebody who is in second place is offering the vice presidency to somebody who is in first place,&amp;rdquo; he told a rally in Columbus, Mississippi.
&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t want anybody here thinking that somehow &amp;lsquo;well, you know, maybe I can get both.&amp;rsquo; Don&amp;rsquo;t think that way. You have to make a choice in this election.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not running for vice president. I am running for president of the United States of America,&amp;rdquo; he added.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Super Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/02/07/after-super-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/02/07/after-super-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s Super Tuesday speech.
A rather lengthy, yet inspiring speech. This man has charisma, something I have not seeing on the rest. I like him. I think he would do a good President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What counts as an issue...</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/02/01/what-counts-as-an-issue-in-the-clinton-obama-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/02/01/what-counts-as-an-issue-in-the-clinton-obama-race/</guid>
      <description>George Lakoff: What Counts as an &amp;ldquo;Issue&amp;rdquo; In the Clinton-Obama Race? There is a reason that Obama recently spoke of Reagan. Reagan understood that you win elections by drawing support from independents and the opposite side. He understood what unified the country so that he could lead it according to his vision. His vision was a radical conservative one, a vision devastating for the country and contradicted by his economic policies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I will vote</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/01/29/i-will-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/01/29/i-will-vote/</guid>
      <description>I will vote today, on Florida&amp;rsquo;s primary elections. I am registered republican and, hence, I can only vote for a running republican. As such, I will vote for Ron Paul. On the elections day, I shall vote for Barack Obama(I know this implies that he will win the nomination for the Democratic Party. I hope &amp;mdash; and wish &amp;mdash; he does) for President, Democrat.
Please, whatever State you are in, vote as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>