<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>social on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/categories/social/</link>
    <description>Recent content in social on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/categories/social/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>American Parenting killing Marriage</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/11/08/american-parenting-killing-marriage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/11/08/american-parenting-killing-marriage/</guid>
      <description>This article sounds very true, although I would not go as far as generalizing it for all Americans.
 Mothers must devote themselves to their children above anyone or anything else, but many wives would be offended if their husbands said, “You’re pretty great, but my love for you will never hold a candle to the love I have for John Junior.”
Mothers are also holy in a way that fathers are not expected to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Two Child Policy</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/29/chinas-two-child-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/29/chinas-two-child-policy/</guid>
      <description>This one is worth documenting, as it doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen every day. As a matter of fact, it hasn&amp;rsquo;t happened for over three decades.
 &amp;ldquo;It is the latest twist in the most ambitious and ruthless social-engineering program ever undertaken by a modern state: Beijing announced Thursday that the Chinese Communist Party will officially abandon its one-child policy. Yet it has no plans to relinquish authority over its subjects’ birth patterns; rather, Beijing has simply changed the ration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Red Bus</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/22/big-red-bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/22/big-red-bus/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Hi guys, don&amp;rsquo;t forget to donate today!&amp;rdquo; says the lady with the oneblood.org t-shirt. The Big Red Bus parks on campus often, sometimes they seem to be here every day. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ll give you a t-shirt and a cookie!&amp;rdquo; She says. That&amp;rsquo;s the price of your donation, but is it?
A typical pint of blood costs $130-150, and sometimes even more. A lucrative business, don&amp;rsquo;t you agree? Yet, oneblood.org is non-profit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Francis</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/22/protecting-francis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/22/protecting-francis/</guid>
      <description>The Pope has recently been to Cuba, and today he will be arriving to the United States. Like any other dignitary, the Pope needs protection from both, bad people, and adoring crowds. Yet, doing so is not easy feat.
 “The crowds throw things,” Mr. Clancy, who took over as the head of the Secret Service last October, said in an interview. “They throw flags, dolls and, obviously, babies towards him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Beat a Polygraph Test</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/03/how-to-beat-a-polygraph-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/03/how-to-beat-a-polygraph-test/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;He used to advise trainees to clench their anus but has since concluded that terrifying mental imagery works better.&amp;rdquo;
 When you get a control question, which is more general, envision the scariest thing you can in order to trigger physiological distress; the polygraph&amp;rsquo;s tubes around your chest measure breathing, the arm cuff monitors heart rate and electrodes attached to you fingertips detect perspiration. What is your greatest fear? Falling? Drowning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. credit rating lowered</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/04/18/us-credit-rating-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/04/18/us-credit-rating-down/</guid>
      <description>It seems our credit “worthiness” (and hence our capabilities to acquired loans in the future) has diminished:
 S&amp;amp;P maintained its ‘AAA/A-1+’ credit rating on U.S. sovereign debt, saying the nation’s “highly diversified” economy and “effective monetary policies” have helped support growth.
But the ratings agency lowered its outlook for America’s long-term credit rating to “negative” from “stable,” based on the uncertain political debate around the nation’s fiscal problems.
— CNN Money</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 11th</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/09/11/september-11th/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/09/11/september-11th/</guid>
      <description>We will never forget.
Today, eight years ago, a group of humans, guided by a political agenda, a deep hatred towards the United States, and a mad religious fanaticism slammed airplanes into the World Trade Center, destroying the Twin Towers, damaging other buildings, and killing almost 3,000 people. A second airplane hit The Pentagon, and a third crashed near Pennsylvania after some of its passengers and flight crew attempted to retake control of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China earthquake help</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/15/china-earthquake-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/15/china-earthquake-help/</guid>
      <description>Cities completely wipe out, thousands dead, thousands missing, thousands without anything left. China needs our help, and every little thing would help. Ten dollars might not be much for you, but when many donate we can make a difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesbos islanders dispute gay name</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/01/lesbian-islanders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/01/lesbian-islanders/</guid>
      <description>Who has the right to be called Lesbian?
 Campaigners on the Greek island of Lesbos are to go to court in an attempt to stop a gay rights organisation from using the term &amp;ldquo;lesbian&amp;rdquo;.
The islanders say that if they are successful they may then start to fight the word lesbian internationally.
The issue boils down to who has the right to call themselves Lesbians.
Is it gay women, or the 100,000 people living on Greece&amp;rsquo;s third biggest island &amp;mdash;plus another 250,000 expatriates who originate from Lesbos?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prepare to pay more</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/30/prepare-to-pay-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/30/prepare-to-pay-more/</guid>
      <description>It seems that within four years &amp;ndash;if nothing is done to prevent it (and nobody really knows what to do)&amp;ndash; we [americans] will be paying $7 for a gallon of gasoline.
A very interesting post over Wired explains some of the reasons. A brief summary of them:
 Oil companies getting tax breaks, and not passing those savings down, but pocketing them. The economic development in China and India, which increases the demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eBay sues Craigslist</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/23/ebay-sues-craigslist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/23/ebay-sues-craigslist/</guid>
      <description>Referring to an eBay Press release:
 Tainted Love &amp;ndash; We are surprised and disappointed by Ebay&amp;rsquo;s unfounded allegations, which came to us out of the blue, without any attempt to engage in a dialogue with us.
Coming from a shareholder that views craigslist as a prime competitor, filing suit without so much as mentioning these assertions beforehand seems unethical, and hints at ulterior motives.
 Why they ever got in business with eBay is beyond my understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only in Russia</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/17/only-in-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/17/only-in-russia/</guid>
      <description>Drunk Russian sleeps off knifing &amp;ndash; A Russian man trying to sleep off a night of after-work drinking failed to notice a six inch (15 cm) knife in his back - until his wife woke him up.
Yuri Lyalin, 53, took a bus home, ate breakfast and apparently slept like a baby before his spouse noticed a handle sticking out of his back.
He was rushed to casualty but doctors found no vital organs damaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCO Receives Nasdaq Notice Letter</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/28/sco-receives-nasdaq-notice-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/28/sco-receives-nasdaq-notice-letter/</guid>
      <description>SCO Receives Nasdaq Notice Letter &amp;mdash; Yahoo! Finance
 The SCO Group, Inc. (&amp;ldquo;SCO&amp;rdquo;) (Nasdaq: SCOX - News), a leading provider of UNIX&amp;trade; software technology and mobile services, today announced that it received a Nasdaq Staff Determination letter on December 21, 2007 indicating that as a result of having filed for protection under Chapter 11 of the U.S. Bankruptcy Code, the Nasdaq Listing Qualifications Panel has determined to delist the company&amp;rsquo;s securities from the Nasdaq Stock Market and will suspend trading of the securities effective at the open of business on Thursday, December 27, 2007.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honeymoon&#39;s are over, honey</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/17/honeymoons-are-over-honey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/17/honeymoons-are-over-honey/</guid>
      <description>FL woman has 10 husbands, charges say - Yahoo News
 Eunice Lopez has been charged with bigamy, accused of marrying 10 men between 2002 and 2006 without divorcing any of them, federal immigration authorities say. The Miami Herald reported Saturday that a records search by the newspaper found seven additional marriages under the bride&amp;rsquo;s name and birth date.
Lopez arrived in South Florida from Cuba in 2002 and was a legal U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When you thought you hear it all</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/10/31/when-you-thought-you-hear-it-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/10/31/when-you-thought-you-hear-it-all/</guid>
      <description>BBC NEWS: Toilet conference opens in Delhi
 A World Toilet Summit has opened in the Indian capital, Delhi, with more than 40 countries taking part.
The four-day meeting will examine solutions and technologies that can be used to provide a basic need for nearly half the worlds population.
According to estimates, 2.6bn people around the world lack access to a hygienic toilet. The United Nations hopes to halve this figure by 2015 as part of its millennium development goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We remember: Six years ago</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/09/11/we-remember-six-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/09/11/we-remember-six-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>Today, six years ago, a group of animals belonging to the human race decided to take away thousands of innocent lives by destroying the Twin Towers (see World Trade Center). Let us not to forget how stupid they were, how criminal they were, how inhuman they were. Let us remember our brothers and sisters who died that day. For me The Towers stand tall. They always will.
September 11th, 2001: We will never forget!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women of color?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/13/women-of-color/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/13/women-of-color/</guid>
      <description>That term, women of color, emphasized by me below has always puzzled me. Aren&amp;rsquo;t all women and, as a matter of fact, all of us &amp;ldquo;of color&amp;rdquo;? What kind of silly (avoiding the use of a stronger word) terminology is that? And, why aren&amp;rsquo;t those &amp;ldquo;people of goodwill&amp;rdquo; asking for the same treatment to be given to rappers, comedians, writers, etc? Utterly stupid.
 CBS chairman, Leslie Moonves &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Those who have spoken with us the last few days represent people of goodwill from all segments of our society &amp;ndash;all races, economic groups, men and women alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is there any difference?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/03/21/is-there-any-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/03/21/is-there-any-difference/</guid>
      <description>Is has always amazed me how people or groups of people self segregate, while voicing their concerns about discrimination and inequality.
Some websites have come across lately that really puzzle me. To show a couple, Black Engineer and The Black Collegian. Why? It doesn&amp;rsquo;t make any sense to me. Are engineers different because of their ethnic background, or because of their field of knowledge? Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t all Colleges teach the same, regardless of the ethnicity of their students?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Katrina crime increase</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/01/08/post-katrina-crime-increase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/01/08/post-katrina-crime-increase/</guid>
      <description>Ever since after Katrina we have seeing crime increase to levels never saw before in Orlando. Crime has been so high, that it has placed our city on the top most 25 dangerous cities in the States. Orlando, City Beautiful, rated higher than Miami on crime. Every single day more than 4-5 people die victim of a violent crime. Others get injured. It seems other cities/states are experiencing similar problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nazi crimes archives set to open</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/05/16/nazi-crimes-archives-set-to-open-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/05/16/nazi-crimes-archives-set-to-open-2/</guid>
      <description>BBC News: Nazi crimes archives to set open.
 The 47 million files hold Nazi records of forced labourers, concentration camp victims and political prisoners. They have been used to help people trace their relatives, but were kept closed to protect victims&amp;rsquo; privacy. Many people felt the files should be opened to historical researchers to ensure the details of the Holocaust (Nazis genocide) are not forgotten.
 Yes, we must not forget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terri&#39;s autopsy: What does it means?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/15/terri-autopsy-what-does-it-means/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/15/terri-autopsy-what-does-it-means/</guid>
      <description>The results of Terri Schiavo&amp;rsquo;s autopsy were released today. BBC News reported:
 Examiner John Throgmartin said there was no evidence of trauma or strangulation prior to Schiavo&amp;rsquo;s collapse. The autopsy also could not prove that she was suffering from an eating disorder at the time &amp;ndash; her diminished potassium levels at the time could have been affected by emergency treatment. The 41-year-old was found not to have suffered a heart attack or been administered harmful drugs or other substances before her death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not guilty!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/13/not-guilty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/13/not-guilty/</guid>
      <description>This is just news:
 Singer Michael Jackson has been found innocent on all 10 charges of child abuse at the end of his trial.
The singer strenuously denied the charges of molesting a 13-year-old boy. There were cheers from his fans outside the court as the verdicts were read.
He was also cleared of giving the child alcohol and conspiring to kidnap him and his family. &amp;ndash; BBC News</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Privacy at stake</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/03/31/your-privacy-at-stake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/03/31/your-privacy-at-stake/</guid>
      <description>Something very infortunated has happened and I want to encourage you, and the people you know, to help amend this by signing the petition and emailing your elected officials as soon as possible.
The NTIA, which is the telecommunications and Internet arm of the Department of Commerce, has disallowed private registrations for .US domain names. This unfortunate decision was made by the NTIA, without a hearing or an opportunity for a response by those affected &amp;ndash; in fact; there was no due process of any kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex is everything</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/01/12/sex-is-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/01/12/sex-is-everything/</guid>
      <description>For spammers &amp;ndash;and others&amp;ndash;, that is. Other than the trackback attack that a good group of people including me received recently, sex related spam seems to have doubled as the year increased by one. And all comes down to this: human beings are a bunch of sex driven machines. Take it or leave it. We all like it, enjoy it and are driven to it in a multifaceted spectrum. It goes beyond the Mother Nature purpose of procreation (continuity).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembrance</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/09/11/remembrance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/09/11/remembrance/</guid>
      <description>Today, three years ago, a group of animals belonging to the human race decided to take away thousands of innocent lives by destroying the Twin Towers (see World TradeCenter). Let us not to forget how stupid they were, how criminal they were, how non human they were. Let us remember our brothers and sisters who died that day. For me The Towers stand tall. They always will.
September 11th, 2001: We will never forget!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is the Marketers fault!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/08/25/marketers-fault/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/08/25/marketers-fault/</guid>
      <description>While reading my daily doses of irrelevant information on Slashdot today, I saw that &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;The UK Advertising Standards Authority has upheld complaints that Microsoft misled consumers by running advertisements claiming Linux is 10 times more expensive than Windows&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; While they did not lied, they forgot to mention that the &amp;ldquo;independent research&amp;rdquo; used as a reference Linux running on an expensive Mainframe and Windows running on a common PC. That does not surprises me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobility 20-20</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/10/07/mobility-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/10/07/mobility-2020/</guid>
      <description>If you do not live in Orlando you will not know what I am talking about here. Today was also voting day here, in Orlando, FL, but for a different reason than the Californians. Let me explain.
As you may or may not know every city has its budget. I bet that even every county has its own as well. Talking about a city budget, some people, perhaps even a bunch of people, get paid big money to come up with the numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you have a weblog, read</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/06/09/if-you-have-a-weblog-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/06/09/if-you-have-a-weblog-read/</guid>
      <description>Recently, one of the weblogs I used to read often closed it&amp;rsquo;s doors. It was kind of sad to see it happen, but I am sure sooner or later it&amp;rsquo;s doors will open for something, even yet, more interesting. It is (or was?) Joaquin Bernal &amp;ldquo;bitacora&amp;rdquo;, a weblog in spanish.
I decided to poorly translate his last post, which I found quite informative and interesting. I say poorly translate, first because english is not my mother tongue, and second, because with every translation you loose a lot of meaning that can be only understood completely on the language the text was written.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>