<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>philosophy on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/philosophy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in philosophy on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/philosophy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Meaning of Life</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2012/02/02/the-meaning-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2012/02/02/the-meaning-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Will Durant sent a letter to a few notable figures, asking them for the meaning of life.
 Spare me a moment to tell me what meaning life has for you, what keeps you going, what help—if any—religion gives you, what are the sources of your inspiration and your energy, what is the goal or motive-force of your toil, where you find your consolations and your happiness, where, in the last resort, your treasure lies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steal everything</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/04/steal-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/04/steal-everything/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Nothing is original. Steal from anywhere that resonates with inspiration or fuels your imagination. Devour old films, new films, music, books, paintings, photographs, poems, dreams, random conversations, architecture, bridges, street signs, trees, clouds, bodies of water, light and shadows. Select only things to steal from that speak directly to your soul. If you do this, your work (and theft) will be authentic. Authenticity is invaluable; originality is nonexistent. And don’t bother concealing your thievery—celebrate it if you feel like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragons can be killed</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/10/08/dragons-can-be-killed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/10/08/dragons-can-be-killed/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fairy tales do not tell children the dragons exist. Children already know that dragons exist. Fairy tales tell children the dragons can be killed.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;mdash; G. K. Chesterton
 &amp;ldquo;By confining your child to blameless stories of child life in which nothing at all alarming ever happened, you would fail to banish the terrors, and would succeed in banishing all that can ennoble them or make them endurable. For in the fairy tales, side by side with the terrible figures, we find the immemorial comforters and protectors, the radiant ones; and the terrible figures are not merely terrible, but sublime.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>