<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jekyll on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/jekyll/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jekyll on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 19:28:16 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/jekyll/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A few technical changes</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/03/05/a-few-technical-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 19:28:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/03/05/a-few-technical-changes/</guid>
      <description>A few things have happened on my current server setup. The biggest one was my move from FreeBSD to Ubuntu. I do not have complains about FreeBSD &amp;mdash; how could I? &amp;mdash; but I wanted to play with more recent stuff, and it was becoming very hard to do under BSD. I also wanted a refresh, since I had been running that VPS for a while and it was starting to feel &amp;ldquo;dirty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jekyll and Git</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/08/29/jekyll-and-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/08/29/jekyll-and-git/</guid>
      <description>I have been using Jekyll for a while now, but all this time I have been generating it on the server, That is, I had had a directory on the server holding the Jekyll files, in which I would run jekyll build to generate the website. Not too streamlined.
Before hosting this weblog on Vultr, I had it on GitHub, and their Pages would do the publishing for me, right after a commit, which was great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding little to talk about</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/03/30/little-to-talk-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/03/30/little-to-talk-about/</guid>
      <description>The main problem with Jekyll is that is out of the way. Unlike other weblog engines, which are managed via the web, I come to the shell to type and process this. Perhaps I need to research a better workflow?
 I am finding little to talk about lately, and that is keeping things here rather quiet. It is not only that I do not have much to write, but that when the desire arrives it gets lost in translation, mostly because of the way I have decided to handle this little space of mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World, or Hello Again!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/21/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/21/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post. It seems I have started writing occasionally again. I still conserve the old posts, from the previous weblog. Not sure many of them were worth of keeping, but I might browse through them and pick one or two to bring back here.
This time I will keep this simple. Well, as simple as a person with slight OCD can keep it. I promise, I think. This little site is generated by Jekyll and hosted on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create files on GitHub</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2012/12/05/files-on-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2012/12/05/files-on-github/</guid>
      <description>There is a new feautre on GitHub, and this one allows you to create files directly from the web interface. This is very handy, for those of us running Jekyll.
This is my first test of the feature, I had to try it right away. Only wishing now to have a friendlier Markdown/kramdown editor. But it&amp;rsquo;s a start. I like it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Many changes coming soon</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/04/01/many-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/04/01/many-changes/</guid>
      <description>Just very recently I wrote about me moving to Jekyll from WordPress:
 After much thought, and tinkering, I decided to ditch my six year old or so WordPress and start blogging like a hacker with the awesome Jekyll.
 I also wrote —fairly recently— about living on a Linode:
 Moved to Linode. Love it, highly recommend it. They reward customers that bring referrals, but notice my links do not have any referral code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forget Hyde, moved to Jekyll!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/02/03/forget-hyde-get-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/02/03/forget-hyde-get-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>After much thought, and tinkering, I decided to ditch my six year old or so WordPress and start blogging like a hacker with the awesome Jekyll.
I am still getting a few things in place, like making sure all entries are properly converted to markdown, but overall I am liking this. A lot. I do not longer need MySQL, nor PHP. It is a no sweat setup! Some might say, back to basics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>