<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>notes on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in notes on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:54:11 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Happiness?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/08/24/what-is-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:54:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/08/24/what-is-happiness/</guid>
      <description>After questioning myself on the meaning of life &amp;mdash; something I still do, by the way &amp;mdash; I long settled that, regardless of what it might be, living a happy life and aiming to be happy is what life is all about. Happiness, though, isn&amp;rsquo;t a fixed thing. Just like the many avatars of gods, their many incarnations, happiness comes from many sources, and is often found in subtle contexts throughout life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Impermanence of Things</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/01/21/about-the-impermanence-of-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 11:13:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/01/21/about-the-impermanence-of-things/</guid>
      <description>Thinking about the impermanence of things is a reoccurring theme for me. It usually happens if I get mad at something I don&amp;rsquo;t like, which used to be quite often no long ago. I still notice situations that are less than desirable for my point of view, but I no longer get mad every single time. I am trying my very best not to get upset for anything, or with anyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neighbors</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/20/neighbors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/20/neighbors/</guid>
      <description>Our neighbors are moving. The ones on the left, that is. They have been our neighbors for fifteen years, and lived here for seventeen, since the community was built. Quiet neighbors, the best kind. Now we roll the dice, and hope for the best, for whoever comes next.
The house on the right has had three owners; we have known them all. The first were the previous owners of our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space for the Dead</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/space-for-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/space-for-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>I read an article today on The Guardian, which showed up on the eight page of Hacker’s News. It talks about the lack of space for the dead, in the world of the living.
 &amp;ldquo;Some 55 million people are reckoned to pass away each year (about 0.8% of the planet’s total population – equivalent to 100% of England’s). Yet urban planners and developers focus overwhelmingly on accommodating and making money from the living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tempus Fugit</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/tempus-fugit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/tempus-fugit/</guid>
      <description>Time seems to be passing by too fast. Way too fast.
A week starts and then it is over when I blink. Same applies to weekends. It used to be that time seemed to pass quick only when engaged in something. Lately it is the same, whether I am busy or not. I am afraid I will blink again, and I will be gone.
Amongst the many things we can’t control, time is the one that hurts the most, especially as we grow older.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/26/saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/26/saturday/</guid>
      <description>Respect others, seek peace, do not be irascible. Give, help, construct; never the opposite. Turn lemons into lemonade. Hard things to do, most of the time, even more so all the time. We are so recalcitrant by nature!
Yet, our existence would be idyllic if we could manage to, at least, try to do all of the above often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Living to 200 Years Old</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/16/secrets-of-living-to-200-years-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/16/secrets-of-living-to-200-years-old/</guid>
      <description>This article refers to aging as not being an inevitable fact of life. It goes to describe the marvelous capabilities that some animals have to live, seemingly, forever. Yet, do we really want to? With all the problems we are having with over population, do we want to pursue the holy grail, and extend life to last hundreds?
We have already &amp;ldquo;extended&amp;rdquo; our lives considerably, taking into account that in 1950 the world average on life expectancy was 48 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specialization is for Insects</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/specialization-is-for-insects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/specialization-is-for-insects/</guid>
      <description>From Robert Heinlein&amp;rsquo;s science fiction book, Time Enough for Love:
 &amp;ldquo;A human being should be able to change a diaper, plan an invasion, butcher a hog, conn a ship, design a building, write a sonnet, balance accounts, build a wall, set a bone, comfort the dying, take orders, give orders, cooperate, act alone, solve equations, analyze a new problem, pitch manure, program a computer, cook a tasty meal, fight efficiently, die gallantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy MMXIV everyone!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/01/happy-mmxiv-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/01/happy-mmxiv-everyone/</guid>
      <description>Now that we have gone around the Sun one more time, we simply start doing it again. We don&amp;rsquo;t fool ourselves, it is not by choice. And with this new elliptical orbit we walk into age, which will lead, ultimately, to our demise. It is a simple concept.
Leaving the obvious behind, what&amp;rsquo;s left is to enjoy what we have. To try being nice to others, to the best of our abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is All around Us</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/29/it-is-all-around-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/29/it-is-all-around-us/</guid>
      <description>Love. It really is.
 &amp;ldquo;Whenever I get gloomy with the state of the world, I think about the arrivals gate at Heathrow Airport. General opinion&amp;rsquo;s starting to make out that we live in a world of hatred and greed, but I don&amp;rsquo;t see that. It seems to me that love is everywhere. Often it&amp;rsquo;s not particularly dignified or newsworthy, but it&amp;rsquo;s always there &amp;mdash; fathers and sons, mothers and daughters, husbands and wives, boyfriends, girlfriends, old friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/it-is-christmas-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/it-is-christmas-day/</guid>
      <description>One of the many things to look forward to each year is, of course, the end of year holidays. Christmas, Festivus, or whatever you call it, the end of December is always a special time. My only complain, and that might be yours too, is that it comes and goes so fast! Kent has finished opening his presents, and somehow it feels &amp;ldquo;it is all over.&amp;rdquo; But we waited the whole year for this!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Meaning of Life</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2012/02/02/the-meaning-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2012/02/02/the-meaning-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Will Durant sent a letter to a few notable figures, asking them for the meaning of life.
 Spare me a moment to tell me what meaning life has for you, what keeps you going, what help—if any—religion gives you, what are the sources of your inspiration and your energy, what is the goal or motive-force of your toil, where you find your consolations and your happiness, where, in the last resort, your treasure lies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Social</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/08/03/non-social/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/08/03/non-social/</guid>
      <description>Almost over two years ago I left Facebook. A few months ago I left LinkedIn and Twitter. Two weeks ago I left Google+. I also left Groupon (I don&amp;rsquo;t even know why I ever sign up for that junk!). Next is to leave here. I guess this is my way to pursuit happiness.
As Mark weblog is gone1 &amp;mdash;perhaps step 9 was, &amp;ldquo;Get rid of the weblog&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash; I enumerate what he wrote:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ritual of Seduction</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/05/27/operation-seduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/05/27/operation-seduction/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The ritual &amp;mdash;considered old-fashioned nowadays by just about everyone under the age of 60&amp;mdash; was traditionally a ceremonial, sacred gesture; its history can be traced to ancient Greece and Rome. In the Middle Ages, a vassal paid homage to his lord by kissing his hand. By the 19th century, hand kissing had been reinvented to convey a man&amp;rsquo;s gallantry and politesse toward a woman. Those men who still practice it today know the rules: never kiss a gloved hand or the hand of a young girl; kiss the hand only of a married woman, and do so only indoors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I thought when my plane crashed</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/05/12/what-i-thought-when-my-plane-crashed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/05/12/what-i-thought-when-my-plane-crashed/</guid>
      <description>From CNN Opinion, this article, written by Ric Elias I liked. I liked it so much, I decided to keep it here, for when it is not longer available at CNN. As I did with a previous article I kept from the WSJ, if CNN does not likes what I have done, let me know and I will remove it, or adapt it to a compromise. Please do not sue me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawing a blank, again</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/04/11/drawing-a-blank-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/04/11/drawing-a-blank-again/</guid>
      <description>Drawing a blank.
 Lost in a search of identity, on a broader scale Consumed by the unknowns Overflowed by love; furious for not knowing why Feeling I am missing something Moving towards the end  Drawing a blank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find what you love</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/04/11/find-what-you-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/04/11/find-what-you-love/</guid>
      <description>Steve Jobs commencement address at Stanford University, in 2005:
 Remembering that I’ll be dead soon is the most important tool I’ve ever encountered to help me make the big choices in life. Because almost everything — all external expectations, all pride, all fear of embarrassment or failure — these things just fall away in the face of death, leaving only what is truly important. Remembering that you are going to die is the best way I know to avoid the trap of thinking you have something to lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NETBROS.COM for sale</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/12/02/netbros-com-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/12/02/netbros-com-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I am selling this domain, which I have have since, well, I already lost count. If you are interested on buying this domain, please contact me. I would rather sell it directly than going through a broker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MCITP - Enterprise Server Administrator</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/08/10/mcitp-enterprise-server-administrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/08/10/mcitp-enterprise-server-administrator/</guid>
      <description>The last two weeks were very busy ones. I went through a Boot Camp and obtained the Microsoft Certified Information Technology Professional certification, as an Enterprise Server 2008 Administrator. Much more to do with the product, but migration is on my close horizon.
As a side note, and totally unrelated, I will change the way this weblog look soon. I will probably start over as well, all the old content gone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration and comments disabled</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/07/02/registration-and-comments-disabled/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/07/02/registration-and-comments-disabled/</guid>
      <description>I have grown tired of deleting bogus accounts. They do not do anything, they do not cause harm; it is just tiresome to delete, each day, 20 or 30 of them. So enough&amp;hellip; for now. Those who had an account (which was created using OpenID), still can comment, but no new registrations anymore.
As a matter of fact&amp;hellip; I think I will change this site completely. Soon&amp;hellip; ish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesbos islanders dispute gay name</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/01/lesbian-islanders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/01/lesbian-islanders/</guid>
      <description>Who has the right to be called Lesbian?
 Campaigners on the Greek island of Lesbos are to go to court in an attempt to stop a gay rights organisation from using the term &amp;ldquo;lesbian&amp;rdquo;.
The islanders say that if they are successful they may then start to fight the word lesbian internationally.
The issue boils down to who has the right to call themselves Lesbians.
Is it gay women, or the 100,000 people living on Greece&amp;rsquo;s third biggest island &amp;mdash;plus another 250,000 expatriates who originate from Lesbos?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only in Russia</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/17/only-in-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/17/only-in-russia/</guid>
      <description>Drunk Russian sleeps off knifing &amp;ndash; A Russian man trying to sleep off a night of after-work drinking failed to notice a six inch (15 cm) knife in his back - until his wife woke him up.
Yuri Lyalin, 53, took a bus home, ate breakfast and apparently slept like a baby before his spouse noticed a handle sticking out of his back.
He was rushed to casualty but doctors found no vital organs damaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overturning the unconstitutional</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/08/overturning-the-unconstitutional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/08/overturning-the-unconstitutional/</guid>
      <description>Overturning nightmares
 As president, he said he would ask his attorney general &amp;ldquo;to review every executive order&amp;rdquo; of the Bush administration. &amp;ldquo;We are going to overturn those that were unconstitutional. We are going to overturn those that are unnecessary.&amp;rdquo;
 I don&amp;rsquo;t think it is a slogan, I don&amp;rsquo;t think they are empty words. Yes, we can!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The $2 Trillion Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/03/05/the-2-trillion-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/03/05/the-2-trillion-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>The $2 Trillion Nightmare
 &amp;ldquo;Normally, when America goes to war, nonessential spending programs are reduced to make room in the budget for the higher costs of the war. Individual programs that benefit specific constituencies are sacrificed for the common good &amp;hellip; And taxes have never been cut during a major American war. For example, President Eisenhower adamantly resisted pressure from Senate Republicans for a tax cut during the Korean War.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t step in the lines</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/01/11/dont-step-in-the-lines/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/01/11/dont-step-in-the-lines/</guid>
      <description>The child inside of us lives, I am a living proof. That, or I have some autistic tendencies. Or both. Having a child, I unintentionally behave like a child when I am with him but, also, when I am alone.
I have found myself avoiding to step on cracks on the floor, or on lines. When challenged with floors with multiple lines together, which are difficult or impossible to avoid, I either find and alternative route, or simply enlarge my pattern of what I consider lined space, like lined areas of different colors become empty spaces &amp;ndash;without lines&amp;ndash;, for example, all the black mosaic, even though it has lines, becomes a &amp;ldquo;flat&amp;rdquo; and the lines not to be stepped on become those who divide the black mosaic space from a different colored space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy 2008!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/31/happy-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/31/happy-2008/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone out there! Please, love one another. Be safe. Happy New Year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas is gone, or is it?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/27/christmas-is-gone-or-is-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/27/christmas-is-gone-or-is-it/</guid>
      <description>The long whole year wait, for many, comes to an end quite fast. It seems it takes a long time until Christmas arrives, but when it does, it goes away very quickly. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s not fair&amp;rdquo;, Kim says. Well, I am that type of crazy individual that sings Christmas Carols, listen to Christmas music and lives the &amp;ldquo;Christmas spirit&amp;rdquo; pretty much all year round. I have my ups and downs like everyone else, but I refuse to let Christmas be a one day celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa gets the extra love</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/19/santa-gets-the-extra-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/19/santa-gets-the-extra-love/</guid>
      <description>KM believes in Santa. It is that childish fantasy we do not want to spoil quite yet. But the fat guy, with red cheeks, who pilots a sleigh pulled by reindeers, gets all the extra love &amp;ndash;and credits&amp;ndash; for the job we, as parents, do during Christmas time. I challenge Santa to come up with a Wii!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ron Paul on War and Foreign Policy</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/17/ron-paul-on-war-and-foreign-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/17/ron-paul-on-war-and-foreign-policy/</guid>
      <description>Ron Paul: War and Foreign Policy
 We can continue to fund and fight no-win police actions around the globe, or we can refocus on securing America and bring the troops home. No war should ever be fought without a declaration of war voted upon by the Congress, as required by the Constitution.
Under no circumstances should the U.S. again go to war as the result of a resolution that comes from an unelected, foreign body, such as the United Nations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I had to have them</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/14/i-had-to-have-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/14/i-had-to-have-them/</guid>
      <description>I found this weblog, via Kottke, and in it, this post I like: So long Flight of the Conchords. And I loved it. I had to have the list of videos on that log here1, to show wife, to play them at a later time. Simply awesome. And here they come (links go to Youtube):
 The most beautiful girl in the room - “you could be a part-time model”. Humans are dead - the robot one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programmers != Antisocials</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/14/programmers-antisocials/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/14/programmers-antisocials/</guid>
      <description>BBC NEWS: Business: Bill Gates: The skills you need to succeed
 A lot of people assume that creating software is purely a solitary activity where you sit in an office with the door closed all day and write lots of code.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t true at all.
Software innovation, like almost every other kind of innovation, requires the ability to collaborate and share ideas with other people, and to sit down and talk with customers and get their feedback and understand their needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primary elections</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/13/primary-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/13/primary-elections/</guid>
      <description>It is my desire that the U.S. primary elections were available to everyone, to vote for anyone, regardless of the political part affiliation 1. In fact, I would not make a requirement to affiliate to a specific party at all.
Why? If I am registered, for example, democrat, but I see that the choices of the Democratic Party are not &amp;ldquo;presidential&amp;rdquo; material, then I would like to be able to vote (even at the primaries) for the best of the other party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SuperGenPass update</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/07/supergenpass-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/07/supergenpass-update/</guid>
      <description>SuperGenPass: A Free Bookmarklet Password Generator
Chris Zarate has updated his SuperGenPass bookmarlet, which now has it&amp;rsquo;s own dedicated domain. Version 1.1 comes with (from the website):  Moveable window: The SuperGenPass window can be moved by dragging the title bar. Smarter password capturing: When multiple master passwords are found, the conflict must be resolved by double-clicking the desired field. Smarter autopopulate: Autopopulate is on by default, but only for fields where the master password was found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a load of crock!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/11/06/what-a-load-of-crock/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/11/06/what-a-load-of-crock/</guid>
      <description>If it weren&amp;rsquo;t enough that you have to go through airport hell every time you must take an airplane, some people is trying to cash in, and they are using terrorism to their advantage. Enter Clear card.
From their CEO (read while playing patriotic music on the background, waving an American flag) :
 &amp;ldquo;I started Verified Identity Pass with a simple idea: In the post 9-11 era we have to take new measures to protect ourselves yet not destroy our way of life by strangling the free flow of people and commerce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When you thought you hear it all</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/10/31/when-you-thought-you-hear-it-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/10/31/when-you-thought-you-hear-it-all/</guid>
      <description>BBC NEWS: Toilet conference opens in Delhi
 A World Toilet Summit has opened in the Indian capital, Delhi, with more than 40 countries taking part.
The four-day meeting will examine solutions and technologies that can be used to provide a basic need for nearly half the worlds population.
According to estimates, 2.6bn people around the world lack access to a hygienic toilet. The United Nations hopes to halve this figure by 2015 as part of its millennium development goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The slashes</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/09/14/the-slashes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/09/14/the-slashes/</guid>
      <description>Lots of people do not get it. Lots of businesses and governmental institutions do not get it. Yesterday my call to the Federal Reserve Complain line (I called to complain about them, and their delay on ACH transfers, but there was no option to complain about them, yet, many to complain about others) had it wrong too:
The symbol &amp;ldquo;/&amp;rdquo; (without quotes, of course) is a &amp;ldquo;slash&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;stroke.&amp;rdquo; The symbol &amp;ldquo;\&amp;rdquo; is a &amp;ldquo;backslash&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farewell Maestro</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/09/06/farewell-maestro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/09/06/farewell-maestro/</guid>
      <description>Luciano Pavarotti has died. &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; One of the most popular contemporary vocal performers in the world of opera and across multiple musical genres..&amp;rdquo; The world grieves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Write Articles, Not Blog Postings</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/07/17/write-articles-not-blog-postings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/07/17/write-articles-not-blog-postings/</guid>
      <description>Write Articles, Not Blog Postings &amp;ndash; Jakob Nielsens Alertbox
Boy, do I agree with Nielsen on this one. I have been guilty of many of the things he points out. That is why I am scribbling less lately. And it will be much less in the future. Totally dislike the &amp;ldquo;tumbler&amp;rdquo; generation. Junk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I shall not censure</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/05/11/i-shall-not-censure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/05/11/i-shall-not-censure/</guid>
      <description>From today on, I shall not censure on this weblog. Any comment left (no spam comments, of course. Who needs those?) will be shown uncensored. I will only mask foul words (just because of my ICRA rating, safe for children), and correct capitalization as needed, but nothing else. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember ever censuring &amp;ndash;I don&amp;rsquo;t write enough, really. But now I have taken that idea, if ever was, away from my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women of color?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/13/women-of-color/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/13/women-of-color/</guid>
      <description>That term, women of color, emphasized by me below has always puzzled me. Aren&amp;rsquo;t all women and, as a matter of fact, all of us &amp;ldquo;of color&amp;rdquo;? What kind of silly (avoiding the use of a stronger word) terminology is that? And, why aren&amp;rsquo;t those &amp;ldquo;people of goodwill&amp;rdquo; asking for the same treatment to be given to rappers, comedians, writers, etc? Utterly stupid.
 CBS chairman, Leslie Moonves &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Those who have spoken with us the last few days represent people of goodwill from all segments of our society &amp;ndash;all races, economic groups, men and women alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thought of the day</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/09/thought-of-the-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/09/thought-of-the-day/</guid>
      <description>If your weblog or site &amp;ndash;in general&amp;ndash; advertising is slowing down the load of pages to an almost complete halt, it is time to re-think and take a different marketing approach. Your writings and your advertising are been missing. You may as well cancel your hosting and print what you want to say, along with the advertisings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small changes here and there</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/05/small-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/05/small-changes/</guid>
      <description>I have changed, once again, the theme around here, as you can see. Simple approaches have always been my favorites and this one excels in simplicity, hence the name I have given it, &amp;ldquo;Simplissimo&amp;rdquo;. It is a modified version of a WordPress theme based on an original Typo theme. As you can see, I have done slight (or not so slight) changes to make it mine. And still might change more or I might change it all together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is there any difference?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/03/21/is-there-any-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/03/21/is-there-any-difference/</guid>
      <description>Is has always amazed me how people or groups of people self segregate, while voicing their concerns about discrimination and inequality.
Some websites have come across lately that really puzzle me. To show a couple, Black Engineer and The Black Collegian. Why? It doesn&amp;rsquo;t make any sense to me. Are engineers different because of their ethnic background, or because of their field of knowledge? Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t all Colleges teach the same, regardless of the ethnicity of their students?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dabbling with OpenID</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/03/20/dabbling-with-openid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/03/20/dabbling-with-openid/</guid>
      <description>I have implemented OpenID commenting here, and I have gone one step further, by allowing commenting only after logged in, while using OpenID. This isn&amp;rsquo;t to avoid comment spam, which I think it will happen regardless. I am encouraging the use of the technology, which others might consider flawed (the CardInfo lovers, etc).
All OpenID providers are accepted, of course. I have even setup a small OpenID server of my own as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two visions?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/03/20/two-visions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/03/20/two-visions/</guid>
      <description>Mark posted yesterday that he will be working for Google, since out of the &amp;ldquo;two visions&amp;rdquo; of the web, he says, Google is the right one. I am not web savvy nor I really care much about it, but I am sure there is more than two visions on the web, there is not right and wrong, but many, many, many shades in between. But the way I see it, the bottom line in my mind: he is going to work for someone who will pay him very well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More changes coming</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/02/26/more-changes-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/02/26/more-changes-coming/</guid>
      <description>For the first time I am working on creating a complete theme here. The last time I had a decent one was back when WordPress 1.5 was around, for which themes weren&amp;rsquo;t implemented as they are now.
No much have been happening in life. I don&amp;rsquo;t have much to tell right now, other that those minor breadcrumbs of life. Actually, I have a few things I want to write, if anything to keep record online of what happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Katrina crime increase</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/01/08/post-katrina-crime-increase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/01/08/post-katrina-crime-increase/</guid>
      <description>Ever since after Katrina we have seeing crime increase to levels never saw before in Orlando. Crime has been so high, that it has placed our city on the top most 25 dangerous cities in the States. Orlando, City Beautiful, rated higher than Miami on crime. Every single day more than 4-5 people die victim of a violent crime. Others get injured. It seems other cities/states are experiencing similar problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to say goodbye</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/12/21/its-time-to-say-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/12/21/its-time-to-say-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s almost time to say goodbye to 2006 and welcome 2007. This will be &amp;ndash; I think &amp;ndash; my last entry of the year. A few has happened to the Collantes&amp;rsquo; family in 2006, but the most important thing is that we have kept together, and that we have being blessed in many ways. Kent Martin has brought joy to our lives, so much joy we did not know existed. He is the main reason I love life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Craigslist founder will not sell</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/11/07/craigslist-founder-has-no-desire-to-sell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/11/07/craigslist-founder-has-no-desire-to-sell/</guid>
      <description>The founder of craigslist, the free social-networking and classifieds Web site, said on Thursday he is not interested in selling out, just hours after MySpace.com was valued at $15 billion.
&amp;ldquo;Who needs the money? We don&amp;rsquo;t really care,&amp;rdquo; Craig Newmark said in an interview at the Picnic &amp;lsquo;06 Cross Media Week conference in Amsterdam.
&amp;ldquo;If you&amp;rsquo;re living comfortably, what&amp;rsquo;s the point of having more?&amp;rdquo; Newmark said.
[&amp;hellip;]
Newmark said raising the money to subsequently give it away to good causes also did not interest him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Military Commissions Act of 2006</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/10/20/the-military-commissions-act-of-2006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/10/20/the-military-commissions-act-of-2006/</guid>
      <description>David Wu, democratic congressman representing the state of Oregon reportedly said, referring to the Military Commissions Act of 2006 recently signed into law:
 Let us say that my wife, who is here in the gallery with us tonight, a sixth generation Oregonian, is walking by the friendly, local military base and is picked up as an unlawful enemy combatant. What is her recourse? She says, I am a U.S. citizen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We, the forgetful</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/08/14/we-the-forgetful/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/08/14/we-the-forgetful/</guid>
      <description>I am often intrigued, saddened, worried, by the human &amp;ldquo;natural&amp;rdquo; forgetful nature. Since the beginning of time, we haven&amp;rsquo;t kept memories of lost, gone ones. Did any of you remember &amp;ndash;or even knew of&amp;ndash; your great-grandparents? How many generations do you have knowledge of? When you are gone, how many years will you be remembered? Why do we forget? Why? What can we do to change that? Going through a life of accomplishments &amp;ndash;or lack of, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter&amp;ndash; and ending up in the void.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/05/23/why/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/05/23/why/</guid>
      <description>While visiting South today I found, once again, this quote that I like so much:
 The first question which you will ask and which I must try to answer is this, &amp;lsquo;What is the use of climbing Mount Everest?&amp;rsquo; and my answer must at once be, &amp;lsquo;It is no use.&amp;rsquo; We shall not bring back a single bit of gold or silver, not a gem, nor any coal or iron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Security has gone down</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/05/17/blue-security-has-gone-down-or-has-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/05/17/blue-security-has-gone-down-or-has-it/</guid>
      <description>Blue Security has announced it has ceased their anti-spam operations. From their website (which could be down as I type this):
 As we cannot build the Blue Security business on the foundation we originally envisioned, we are discontinuing all of our anti-spam activities on your behalf and are exploring other, non spam-related avenues for our technological developments. As much as it saddens us, we believe this is the responsible thing to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why e-mails are so easily missunderstood</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/05/15/why-e-mails-are-so-easily-missunderstood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/05/15/why-e-mails-are-so-easily-missunderstood/</guid>
      <description>Very interesting read and, in my case, it has proven to be as close to truth as it can be. Go read the whole thing, it is worth it.
 Though e-mail is a powerful and convenient medium, researchers have identified three major problems. First and foremost, e-mail lacks cues like facial expression and tone of voice. That makes it difficult for recipients to decode meaning well. Second, the prospect of instantaneous communication creates an urgency that pressures e-mailers to think and write quickly, which can lead to carelessness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can&#39;t do that!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/02/23/you-cant-do-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/02/23/you-cant-do-that/</guid>
      <description>Technology, Technology news, Times Online
 &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t believe that your company would allow people to make money from something that you allow people to have free access to. Is this really the case?&amp;rdquo; she asked.
&amp;ldquo;If Mozilla permit the sale of copied versions of its software, it makes it virtually impossible for us, from a practical point of view, to enforce UK anti-piracy legislation, as it is difficult for us to give general advice to businesses over what is/is not permitted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confussed</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/02/14/confussed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/02/14/confussed/</guid>
      <description>I have not written for a long time. I am in a state of confussion and change. I feel the urge to redefine life and things around me, I just don&amp;rsquo;t know how and when to start. And that urge to redefine does not relates to this weblog, even though the weblog falls into the category of &amp;ldquo;things around me.&amp;rdquo;
I am around, I am not dead (Kim and Kent need me).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chocolate Imbecile</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/01/18/the-chocolate-imbecile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/01/18/the-chocolate-imbecile/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t get it out of mind. How a person can be so idiotic? The major of New Orleans, Ray Nagin said, among other things:
 &amp;ldquo;Surely God is mad at America. He sent us hurricane after hurricane after hurricane, and it&amp;rsquo;s destroyed and put stress on this country&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;Surely he doesn&amp;rsquo;t approve of us being in Iraq under false pretenses.&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;But surely he is upset at black America also.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worse hurricane season?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/07/11/worse-hurricane-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/07/11/worse-hurricane-season/</guid>
      <description>With Dennis &amp;ndash;the hurricane, that is&amp;ndash; Florida has had 5 hurricanes in less than a year. And it seems it could get a bit worse.
 LOXAHATCHEE, FL &amp;ndash; A wildlife expert in south Florida says turtles may be giving us a sign that the hurricane season ahead is going to be a bad one.
Lyle Thomas said he&amp;rsquo;s noticed turtles at the edge of the Everglades have nested just about as high as they can in earthen levees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Britons, our brothers and sisters</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/07/08/britons-our-brothers-and-sisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/07/08/britons-our-brothers-and-sisters/</guid>
      <description>Once again some (insert some lots of bad words here) terrorists have tried to affect the civilized world by detonating bombs and killing innocent people. They&amp;rsquo;ve cause pain, allright, but their final goal has failed, as it will always do. Britons are not afraid, civilized world is more united because of those dumb (some more bad words here).
We are more united than ever. United Kingdom of England and North Ireland, all our love and support from the other side of the ocean!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downing Street Memo</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/17/downing-street-memo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/17/downing-street-memo/</guid>
      <description>I have known about this since it was released to the News media, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t comment about it here. I am providing a link to the contents of the Memo (pretty small read, I assure you) as they showed on the Times Online on May 1st, 2005. Draw your conclusions. I just want to quote a few parts of it. The document itself says it all, really.
 &amp;hellip;C reported on his recent talks in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA PATRIOT Act</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/17/usa-patriot-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/17/usa-patriot-act/</guid>
      <description>A lot has been said and written about the &amp;#8220;Uniting and Strengthening America by Providing Appropriate Tools Required to Intercept and Obstruct Terrorism Act&amp;#8221;, commonly known as USA PATRIOT Act, but they are quite diverse interpretations &amp;#8212;some biased&amp;#8212;, mainly because the whole Act is written on 300 pages of legalese. Recently I found the Electronic Frontier Foundation page about such Act, which sums it up in the following points (as far as why should we care):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terri&#39;s autopsy: What does it means?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/15/terri-autopsy-what-does-it-means/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/15/terri-autopsy-what-does-it-means/</guid>
      <description>The results of Terri Schiavo&amp;rsquo;s autopsy were released today. BBC News reported:
 Examiner John Throgmartin said there was no evidence of trauma or strangulation prior to Schiavo&amp;rsquo;s collapse. The autopsy also could not prove that she was suffering from an eating disorder at the time &amp;ndash; her diminished potassium levels at the time could have been affected by emergency treatment. The 41-year-old was found not to have suffered a heart attack or been administered harmful drugs or other substances before her death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No more Freedom Fries?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/13/no-more-freedom-fries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/13/no-more-freedom-fries/</guid>
      <description>It was really interesting to read on the BBC News:
 A pro-Iraq war US congressman who campaigned for French fries to be renamed &amp;ldquo;freedom fries&amp;rdquo; is now calling for US troops to return home from Iraq. Republican Representative Walter Jones is to introduce legislation demanding a timetable for the withdrawal.
[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;I just feel that the reason of going in for weapons of mass destruction, the ability of the Iraqis to make a nuclear weapon, that&amp;rsquo;s all been proven that it was never there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not guilty!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/13/not-guilty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/13/not-guilty/</guid>
      <description>This is just news:
 Singer Michael Jackson has been found innocent on all 10 charges of child abuse at the end of his trial.
The singer strenuously denied the charges of molesting a 13-year-old boy. There were cheers from his fans outside the court as the verdicts were read.
He was also cleared of giving the child alcohol and conspiring to kidnap him and his family. &amp;ndash; BBC News</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changes</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/10/changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/10/changes/</guid>
      <description>Changes are coming soon. After a couple of years with the same patched interface I am about to a) have it right and migrate it to WP 1.5 or b) asimilate an existing WP template and start fresh. The advances behind WP 1.5.1 are way too attracting, I am not going to wait any longer.
So, should you tomorrow (or next month) come and find things completely different, do not fret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Single sign on</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/05/29/single-sign-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/05/29/single-sign-on/</guid>
      <description>Since I am going to start migrating all my web logins to a single sign on approach (using Chris Zarate SuperGenPass), I think the best way to start is by saving the bookmarklet I will have to use over and over. There is a Greasemonkey version available, which has much more features than this bookmarklet version. I will use the latest because it works with all browsers.
The bookmarklet is: Single Sign on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Privacy at stake</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/03/31/your-privacy-at-stake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/03/31/your-privacy-at-stake/</guid>
      <description>Something very infortunated has happened and I want to encourage you, and the people you know, to help amend this by signing the petition and emailing your elected officials as soon as possible.
The NTIA, which is the telecommunications and Internet arm of the Department of Commerce, has disallowed private registrations for .US domain names. This unfortunate decision was made by the NTIA, without a hearing or an opportunity for a response by those affected &amp;ndash; in fact; there was no due process of any kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am still here</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/03/17/i-am-still-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/03/17/i-am-still-here/</guid>
      <description>It has been a while since I came to talk. I am afraid this time I will not talk much either. Between work, family, a game (I used not to play any game at all. Now the whole family has been playing Toon Town for almost 5 months. Give it a try, it is addictive! :-) ) and a few personal projects I had had little time to come here and chatter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beware!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/01/12/beware/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/01/12/beware/</guid>
      <description>There is a flu strain going around. I am not sure of how vast its geographic coverage will be, I just know I caught a drop &amp;ndash;or a bucket&amp;ndash; of it here in Orlando, Central Florida.
Now this sucker is not like any other. At least for me it isn&amp;rsquo;t. This one blocks your nose and lungs and converts you into a phlegm dispenser machine. It gives you pain in all your joins (joins, not loins!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex is everything</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/01/12/sex-is-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/01/12/sex-is-everything/</guid>
      <description>For spammers &amp;ndash;and others&amp;ndash;, that is. Other than the trackback attack that a good group of people including me received recently, sex related spam seems to have doubled as the year increased by one. And all comes down to this: human beings are a bunch of sex driven machines. Take it or leave it. We all like it, enjoy it and are driven to it in a multifaceted spectrum. It goes beyond the Mother Nature purpose of procreation (continuity).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good bye MMIV. Welcome MMV!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/01/01/good-bye-mmiv-welcome-mmv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/01/01/good-bye-mmiv-welcome-mmv/</guid>
      <description>And here I am, to wish good byes to 2004 and to greet 2005. The year 2004 was a heck of a year, too many things to write in just a couple of minutes. Just one true thing, everything we&amp;mdash;the Collantes&amp;rsquo; family&amp;mdash;did go through was worth the journey.
So, 2005 starts and with it my often erratic and/or pedantic ramblings. To all a prosperous, peaceful, hopeful, fruitful 2005. Just love one to each other, everything else comes after.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking a break</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/09/29/taking-a-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/09/29/taking-a-break/</guid>
      <description>For the very first time I feel like taking a complete break from the weblogging world. I have gone away in the past, but it was never as permanent as I said it would be. Today, for once, I feel I can really do it. That is, break away for a longer time than the previous. Reasons? Just tired, just need more time with my growing kid and family in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quiet time</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/09/25/quiet-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/09/25/quiet-time/</guid>
      <description>It has been a quiet time here. But quiet here does not means it has been so everywhere else. It has been stressful, it has been painful. It hasn&amp;rsquo;t been easy. Whoever once said &amp;ndash;or wrote&amp;ndash; that life isn&amp;rsquo;t easy wasn&amp;rsquo;t lying. But as uneasy as it might get, it is worth living it.
I will be back, right after Jeanne has passed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three in less than a month</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/09/10/three-and-you-are-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/09/10/three-and-you-are-out/</guid>
      <description>There hasn&amp;rsquo;t been that much movement around here &amp;ndash;on the weblog, I mean&amp;ndash;, since hurricanes have kept us busy during the second half of August and the first of September. First Charley, then Frances and now Ivan. The stress level of people around is pretty high, so is their worry. There is a saying, you know, &amp;ldquo;three and you are out!&amp;rdquo;. Everyone I know, whose house or properties have been undamaged, is thinking on that saying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A hell of a week</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/09/04/a-hell-of-a-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/09/04/a-hell-of-a-week/</guid>
      <description>It has been a hell of a week and continues to be so. KM has been the whole week (and still is!) sick. Sick to a point that kept me home all those days. Kim and I have been very worried and needless is to say that our days hasn&amp;rsquo;t been fun one&amp;rsquo;s, to say the least.
To top it off, now we have got Frances, the hurricane that is, about to slam on us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is the Marketers fault!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/08/25/marketers-fault/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/08/25/marketers-fault/</guid>
      <description>While reading my daily doses of irrelevant information on Slashdot today, I saw that &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;The UK Advertising Standards Authority has upheld complaints that Microsoft misled consumers by running advertisements claiming Linux is 10 times more expensive than Windows&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; While they did not lied, they forgot to mention that the &amp;ldquo;independent research&amp;rdquo; used as a reference Linux running on an expensive Mainframe and Windows running on a common PC. That does not surprises me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A busy week</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/08/21/a-busy-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/08/21/a-busy-week/</guid>
      <description>It has been a busy week. On Monday classes will start and, as you can imagine, a lot of things are left to the last moment on a Campus. It is also true that Murphy&amp;rsquo;s Law applies as well on that final week: if something is going to go wrong, it will certainly go wrong. If you are thinking Microsoft Exchange you are on the right track.
You see, when I installed Exchange 2003 I swear I installed the Enterprise version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veteran of Charley</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/08/15/veteran-of-charlie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/08/15/veteran-of-charlie/</guid>
      <description>Mother Nature, just as humans, changes her mind. That is the case of hurricane Charley. All forecasts read that Tampa, FL would be the one beaten by him but Mother Nature, with it&amp;rsquo;s natural (no pun intended) ambivalence made a twist and brought it directly near Fort Myers, and then to us in Orlando, FL.
Needless is to say we had winds. We had winds all right. Actually, we got everything: homes, commercial buildings, trees&amp;hellip; all destroyed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small catching up</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/08/07/small-catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/08/07/small-catching-up/</guid>
      <description>Last week was a busy week. The Exchange server went into 3&amp;frasl;4 full production and, yes, it crashed. For the first time I had to recover the PRIV and PUB databases and the server wasn&amp;rsquo;t been on production not even a week! Oh boy&amp;hellip;
I got the Lingo gateway (VoIP gateway, that is) and the quality is excellent, while reaching their technical support is close to impossible. When I finally got a techie I told him I was starting to think Lingo technical support was a myth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Way too early</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/31/way-too-early/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/31/way-too-early/</guid>
      <description>I woke up at 7:00 AM today, perhaps a bit earlier. The same thing happens every weekend, I cannot sleep as I wish, my internal clock just wouldn&amp;rsquo;t stop buzzing. So here I am, reading my favorites weblog, and news sites while feeling stressed about Monday (or should I say Sunday night?) morning changes at work. It is the weekend, for God&amp;rsquo;s sake! I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be worrying about anything in the future related to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flipping the switch</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/27/flipping-the-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/27/flipping-the-switch/</guid>
      <description>Next Monday (August 2nd) we are flipping the switch from the old reliable Linux based email system (Sendmail, Washington University IMAP/POP3) to a relatively newly deployed Microsoft Exchange 2003. Needless is to say that we &amp;ndash;TRC staff&amp;ndash; all have been busy wrapping things up to minimize the impact. But things &amp;ndash;bad things, unexpected things&amp;ndash; are bound to happen. It is just a matter of time.
With Exchange I say good bye to the taken-for-granted reliability, easy maintenance and trouble free email system that we had, to dive into the unknown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where and what you eat...</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/24/where-and-what-you-eat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/24/where-and-what-you-eat/</guid>
      <description>While browsing the &amp;ldquo;Orlando Sentinel Express&amp;rdquo; I found the section Restaurant Penalties, which I never saw before &amp;ndash;well, it is true that I do not browse the Sentinel Express everyday.
From that section, two restaurant violations caught my eye:
 Giovanni&amp;rsquo;s Restaurant &amp;amp; Pizza, 2140 S. Chickasaw Trail &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;several five gallons pans of pizza and tomato sauce also were found without covers in the walk-in cooler. Raw whole shell eggs were found stored above produce in the walk-in cooler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday morning rants</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/18/sunday-morning-rants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/18/sunday-morning-rants/</guid>
      <description>As I previously wrote, I believe IE is no match to Firefox. I will tell everyone I know about its problems, I will show those to them if I can. I will praise the goods of Firefox, so everyone I know will enjoy web browsing as much as I am. But&amp;hellip;
One thing is not using IE and another thing is not serving pages to those using it. That&amp;rsquo;s plain wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First day</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/11/first-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/11/first-day/</guid>
      <description>I must admit, before I continue, that I did not exercise last night. At least, not as I had intended. It is my fault, I became lazy and even though Kim pushed me well, it did not worked out. But&amp;hellip; I am proud the say that I just walked three miles this morning and, boy, it felt good. I know it is not a sensational &amp;ldquo;news&amp;rdquo;, but I wanted to mark the day of my come back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week recount</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/10/week-recount/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/10/week-recount/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nothing major happened during the last week that I can recall. Someone called me a copycat and accused me of copying another site, which was a totally baseless accusation and hence not worth of occupying more space here. We have been looking &amp;mdash;well, Kim more than I&amp;mdash; for a pre-school for KM without much success. That&amp;rsquo;s pretty much it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am going to try and do some exercises starting tonight, since the lack of it is taking its toll on my body. It is not only the gaining of fat on certain spots that bothers me, it is the total and generalized pain I feel on my whole body just for being out of shape. It is for a better health, I feel sick in some way. Kim has been pushing me to do exercises for quite a while, but the real truth is that I have been pushing myself much longer without much success. Thanks to her insistence and my own internal fight, I think I might be getting somewhere. It is also thanks to KM. I want him to have a father to play with.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy 4th of July!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/04/happy-4th-of-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/04/happy-4th-of-july/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America, and to the Republic for which it stands. One nation under God, indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.&amp;rdquo;
Happy 228th Birthday, America!
 On July 4th, 1776, we claimed our independence from Great Britain (now United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland) and Democracy was born. Every day thousands leave their homeland to come to the &amp;ldquo;land of the free and the home of the brave&amp;rdquo; so they can begin their American Dream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It happened again</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/03/it-happened-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/03/it-happened-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://collantes.us/2004/06/26/friday-night-photos/&#34; title=&#34;Friday night photos&#34;&gt;Last Friday&lt;/a&gt; family got together in our house and some photos were taken. Well, it happened again, just this time there was no other family around, but the three of us. We were making time to go over the airport to pick Khanh (brother-in-law) and girlfriend up, so I snapped a few photos, from which I have choosen five.  It is mainly about KM, but Kim is in one of them, for the first time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something bad about the night, before I show you the photos. Went to the airport, brother airplane was landing at 9:00PM, US Airways flight from Denver. Got there, no signs of them or the airplane. Drove around the airport circle twenty something times! Finally we learned the flight had changed to United Airlines and was arriving at 10:30PM. Now, how could that happen?! A whole hour an a half driving around! Needless is to say, brother should not take a vacation anytime soon :-)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In God we trust</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/02/in-god-we-trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/02/in-god-we-trust/</guid>
      <description>It is interesting to find out, at times when some minority wants to have removed &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;under God&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; from the Pledge of Allegiance, about this &amp;mdash;it refers to the Great Seal of the United States of America motto:
 The federal courts have held that the motto symbolizes the historical role of religion in our society, Lynch, 465 U.S. at 676, formalizes our medium of exchange, see O&amp;rsquo;Hair v. Blumenthal, 462 F.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday night photos</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/06/26/friday-night-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/06/26/friday-night-photos/</guid>
      <description>As I previously mentioned, last night some family members got together in our home to eat and drink. Oh, and to say good bye to some other family that was visiting from California. As it is normal when family gets together, everything started quite early &amp;ndash;5:30PM&amp;ndash; and finished around 9:30PM. That simply means that food and beer was no longer available at that time ;-) .
Normally I am the one taking the photos around, taking care of this kids and later on posting things here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visitor cleaning</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/06/24/visitor-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/06/24/visitor-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>I find it interesting that we &amp;ndash;and I know I am generalizing here, so correct me if I am wrong&amp;ndash; worry about organizing and cleaning the house especially when we are expecting a visit. I know that we want to give the visitor the best impression possible, but aren&amp;rsquo;t we &amp;ldquo;lying&amp;rdquo; by doing so, just because someone is coming? Who are we kidding? I mean, if we were that clean and organized we didn&amp;rsquo;t have the need to do the &amp;ldquo;visitor cleaning&amp;rdquo; to start with, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moved!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/06/22/moved/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/06/22/moved/</guid>
      <description>I have just moved Collantes.US to the new server. DNS is still running on the old one, but you should be seeing the new pages served on the new server Apache. If you see a note at the top asking not to enter a comment, please do so &amp;ndash; that is, do not enter a comment. That server is the old one and it will disappear sooner rather than later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short and sweet</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/06/17/short-and-sweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/06/17/short-and-sweet/</guid>
      <description>Just a quick post, short and sweet, while my wife and kid still sleep and I patiently wait for the ServerBeach people to fix the mess on my server (the other server). Can you believe that I lost connection last night, went to sleep and this morning I found that my IP goes to a Windows 2003 server? Boy, talk about some big time screw up!
I have 15 (fifteen, that is) invitations for Gmail that I am giving out for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just about there</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/06/08/just-about-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/06/08/just-about-there/</guid>
      <description>I know I have been writting a lot (well, not a lot, since I am holding down on writting until everything works as I want) about WP and how great it is and how happy I am to have moved away from MT, etc. I have been testing things, getting everything around to look and feel as they did a while back, when MT was still the one in command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brainstorming</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/31/brainstorming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/31/brainstorming/</guid>
      <description>Some of you might have noticed that I changed things around a little bit. I am still not decided what to have in here, but the actual interface will do for now, even though at time you might see the &amp;ldquo;blue&amp;rdquo; one that I had for quite a while before.
I have eliminated the categories, even though I still use them when writing entries. Tomorrow &amp;ndash;or the day after tomorrow&amp;ndash; I will be upgrading to 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawing a blank</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/19/drawing-a-blank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/19/drawing-a-blank/</guid>
      <description>I am drawing a blank trying to decided the new layout of this site. I have no problems with the previous one, but as I am running a new engine here I would like the layout to be new as well. I spent a significant amount of time yesterday trying to come up with something and all went to waste.
Perhaps I am procastinating until I see Wordpress 1.2 out, and have all links to be cruft free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spelling and grammar</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/04/13/spelling-and-grammar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/04/13/spelling-and-grammar/</guid>
      <description>It is not difficult to realize, even for the untrained eye, that english is not my mother language. Spanish is. I have been &amp;ldquo;using&amp;rdquo; english for eight years now, but I have improved very little. Believe me, when you are as old as I am and, on top of that, are not that good with languages, getting where I have gotten today is quite an accomplishment, although one that leaves plenty space for improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Futilely insisting</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/03/25/futilely-insisting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/03/25/futilely-insisting/</guid>
      <description>Human nature is quite interesting and I type so based on my own experience. I am talking about myself.
It amazes me that I keep going to check for new entries or read comments, once &amp;mdash; and sometimes two, three, four times &amp;mdash; a day on Ambivalent.US, when I disagree 9 out of 10 with everything the owner has to say (actually, write). Same thing happens with Hivelogic, I go there every day just to find a boring, uninteresting entry, still I go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the spanish elections</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/03/20/about-the-spanish-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/03/20/about-the-spanish-elections/</guid>
      <description>The overturn of the elections in Spain was driven by several factors. Leftists accused the PP (Popular Party) of lying and one have to assume that socialists voters believed it. Aznar got Spain into a war that was considered by many as non-needed, following an agresive and self-centered ideology.
The truth is that while the war was out of spanish campgrounds everything was limited to talks about veracity of the (war) facts, justice and geostrategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why do they even bother?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/03/19/why-do-they-even-bother/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/03/19/why-do-they-even-bother/</guid>
      <description>State institutions have a different way of doing things. Different from Corporate America, that is. For example let&amp;rsquo;s say, hypothetically, that a position opens on certain department on a state institution. A person already working for the department, a person which everyone is happy with about the job being done &amp;ndash; by the person, that is &amp;ndash; applies for the position. Odds of that person getting the job are very high, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expect changes</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/03/12/expect-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/03/12/expect-changes/</guid>
      <description>I know it has been a long time. I guess other things are using my mind and what&amp;rsquo;s left is not enough to dedicate on this. I have been back in Orlando for two weeks already, time is flying.
Wanted to get DSL, ordered and before receiving the modem cancelled. Bell South wants you to use their SMTP server and nothing else and I can not accept that. Modem is going back and I am back to my old cable modem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>