<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ucf on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/ucf/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ucf on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/ucf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>IP migration</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/09/09/ip-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/09/09/ip-migration/</guid>
      <description>I have a deadline to meet. I must migrate all my servers, and clients to a private IP space. Servers must be done &amp;mdash; if at all possible &amp;mdash; by September 30th. Clients by October 30th. That is, this year. Problem is, I have never done anything close to it, and there are so many things that need to be done at once, I don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start.
I have a Linux DNS/DHCP to change (Internet facing one).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It has been a ride, UCF</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/02/03/it-has-been-a-ride-ucf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/02/03/it-has-been-a-ride-ucf/</guid>
      <description>I am leaving the College of Business and, hence, the University of Central Florida. When I started working for UCF almost eight years ago I did not know I was going to stay that long, but most important of all, I did not know it was going to be that much fun. It has certainly been a ride, a good one. I learned a lot in all aspects and for that I am grateful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Tampa back and forth</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/01/31/to-tampa-back-and-forth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/01/31/to-tampa-back-and-forth/</guid>
      <description>In the last five days I have been in Tampa four times, twice by myself and twice with Kim and KM. One may say it is only 90 miles each way, not a biggie, but once it is done several times consecutively it does makes a difference.
Three days ago we thought we had the perfect apartment there but this morning Kim thought otherwise and, as quite often, she was right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interviewing potential candidates</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2002/09/30/interviewing-potential-candidates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2002 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2002/09/30/interviewing-potential-candidates/</guid>
      <description>Today we interviewed the first candidate for a job opening we have at work. Everybody, or at least I, was expecting to see a guy. Boy, were we in for a surprise! It just happened to be a girl (chinese nationality), pretty smart, I could say, and charming. Nevertheless, I think she did not get the job, since the language barrier is pretty strong and the position demands fluency.
As you can see, I went to work and not to the dentist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>