<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wow on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/wow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in wow on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2009 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/wow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aion, the WoW killer</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/07/11/aion-the-wow-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/07/11/aion-the-wow-killer/</guid>
      <description>Aion isn&amp;rsquo;t out yet for North America or Europe, but has already caused long time WoW players to quit. That is what my household has done, ending the life of two, four years old, accounts.
Beta 4 is coming up, July 17th and we can hardly wait. Preorder will give you access to the beta, so go ahead! Simply Google Aion and follow the appropiated link.
While we wait, it feels good to be out of WoW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yet another</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/11/12/yet-another/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/11/12/yet-another/</guid>
      <description>Yet another long downtime on World of Warcraft, just in the verge of the release of the second major expansion for the game. What a royal mess! You would think Blizzard has it figured out by now, down to a science, but&amp;hellip;
I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine how tomorrow, with the expansion release, will be. Not going to &amp;ldquo;tune in.&amp;rdquo; Instead will let others have the &amp;ldquo;fun.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here without you - WoW</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/06/01/here-without-you-wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/06/01/here-without-you-wow/</guid>
      <description>An amateur video composed of Word of Warcraft game scenes, which my kid loves dearly.
Here without you (Dimoroc and Redsword are on my server now!)
On vacation now, typing this from beautiful Sterling, Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC goes WoW again!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/10/20/bbc-goes-wow-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/10/20/bbc-goes-wow-again/</guid>
      <description>Although this new &amp;ldquo;interview&amp;rdquo; involves only Horde players, the latest BBC article about WoW is awesome and it gives some very sutil but good insides of the game.
 I&amp;rsquo;ts popularity can be primarily attributed to its accessibility. The game is easy, plain and simple.
It&amp;rsquo;s more forgiving than most other online role-playing games on the market, and does not take as much dedicated playing or &amp;ldquo;grinding&amp;rdquo; to reach the top level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC and WoW</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/09/30/bbc-and-wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/09/30/bbc-and-wow/</guid>
      <description>From one article on today&amp;rsquo;s BBC Online news:
 Occasionally gryphons and hippogriffs swept majestically overhead taking their riders to elsewhere in Azeroth or, as it is also known, the World of Warcraft (WoW).
At the edge of the computer screen chatter constantly scrolled past as other WoW players sought members forguilds, buyers for magical items, help with quests or engaged in idle banter.
 Go and read: A Walk in the World of Warcraft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still playing</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/09/12/still-playing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/09/12/still-playing/</guid>
      <description>Yes guys and gals, still playing WoW and loving it. Tryggr on Argent Dawn is already at level 48 and things are getting harder. Lots of quests can&amp;rsquo;t no longer be done alone and it is hard to find good players to group.
Soon Blizzard will allow characters moving, from server to server as well as accounts merging. I might decide then to move to another server. I am not sure it is going to be a PvP one, Anthony :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The reason of my absence</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/08/24/the-reason-of-my-absence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/08/24/the-reason-of-my-absence/</guid>
      <description>I have not been posting anything in here, and I am afraid it might not happen for a while now. The reason I have been (and will be) away is Wow (World of Warcraft). I have been playing WoW for almost a month now and my character has so far reached level 41.
If you are playing WoW, I am on Argent Dawn, RP Server and my main character is Tryggr, a dwarf warrior.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>