<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>personal on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/categories/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in personal on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 18:23:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/categories/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Close My Account, Robinhood</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2019/07/12/close-my-account-robinhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 18:23:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2019/07/12/close-my-account-robinhood/</guid>
      <description>On 23 April, 2019 I sent an email to Robinhood, using their online help tool, because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a phone number to call on their website.
 Couldn&amp;rsquo;t find […] a proper choice under &amp;ldquo;support issue,&amp;rdquo; so picked something that is close to what I want, but not quite. I would like to close, and delete my account (not just deactivate). Thanks!
 The reply promptly arrived the same day, stating, along other things:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Sorry I Was Late</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2019/04/25/i-am-sorry-i-was-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 18:38:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2019/04/25/i-am-sorry-i-was-late/</guid>
      <description>I can explain why I was so late, I swear.
I woke up this morning after a brilliant two hours of sleep and went to milk the cow. She did not really have much, so the cereal kinda blew. Anyways, as I turned on my red 1993 Chevy Malibu I realised the garage was not opening. Great, the power was down! I went upstairs with a broom and woke up the hamster, which must have fallen asleep on the job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Friend</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2019/02/11/my-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 20:22:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2019/02/11/my-friend/</guid>
      <description>Friends are not easy to come by. They are made, just like good wine, after many years of ageing. At a certain point, which is hard to pinpoint, they cease to be just friends to become family. Just like a family member would, and should, they give you the best advise, uncompromisingly, unabashedly, unreservedly. They praise your virtues and take pride on them, but are quick to call out the stupid things you are bound to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Happiness?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/08/24/what-is-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:54:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/08/24/what-is-happiness/</guid>
      <description>After questioning myself on the meaning of life &amp;mdash; something I still do, by the way &amp;mdash; I long settled that, regardless of what it might be, living a happy life and aiming to be happy is what life is all about. Happiness, though, isn&amp;rsquo;t a fixed thing. Just like the many avatars of gods, their many incarnations, happiness comes from many sources, and is often found in subtle contexts throughout life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplicity</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/22/simplicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:34:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/22/simplicity/</guid>
      <description>That is a screenshot of my macOS desktop. It could be simpler, but as it is it does what I need, and want. When I need to use an app, I simply hit command (⌘) space and start typing the app name to launch it. That is, I use Spotlight.
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great that iOS could be customized like that too? Preferably it would be a setting, that would allow to turn off the visibility of all, or any app on the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flowers Will Follow</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/flowers-will-follow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 18:17:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/flowers-will-follow/</guid>
      <description>To the untrained, this image will have little meaning. Who could imagine that those &amp;ldquo;ugly sticks,&amp;rdquo; as the child called them, will soon bloom into hundreds of beautiful yellow flowers? Yet, as it has happened each year, flowers will follow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching for The Car</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/searching-for-the-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 17:15:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/searching-for-the-car/</guid>
      <description>A year ago, Kent got his learner&amp;rsquo;s permit. With the help of John, and a little from me, he practiced driving for over 250 hours. A year later — more or less — on 9 March, he got his driver&amp;rsquo;s license, passing the practical test with a 96, out of 100 points, score. And so the asking for a car began.
What car should we get for a 17 year old?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Market for a Camera</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/04/on-the-market-for-a-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 21:12:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/04/on-the-market-for-a-camera/</guid>
      <description>We have gone through quite a few cameras. The very first one we recall was a Canon EOS D30, with an amazing 3.2 megapixel &amp;mdash; sarcasm aside, it took amazing photos. After that we had had many Sony Cyber-shots, a Canon Powershot A640, a couple of Canon Powershot Gs, and another bigger Canon, the EOS 6D. In between we have used the camera that comes with the iPhones, starting with the iPhone 2G.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Impermanence of Things</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/01/21/about-the-impermanence-of-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 11:13:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/01/21/about-the-impermanence-of-things/</guid>
      <description>Thinking about the impermanence of things is a reoccurring theme for me. It usually happens if I get mad at something I don&amp;rsquo;t like, which used to be quite often no long ago. I still notice situations that are less than desirable for my point of view, but I no longer get mad every single time. I am trying my very best not to get upset for anything, or with anyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Uber Affair</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/06/06/the-uber-affair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 11:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/06/06/the-uber-affair/</guid>
      <description>Using Uber for the first time, in France, was a delightful experience. We were able to summon a relatively cheap minivan within minutes, the drivers were nice, nothing found to complain. Then, once back home, I decided that I might want to occasionally drive for Uber, for fun. That is when the real affair started.
To begin with, the rider photo I had on my profile no longer met their requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning the plate</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/12/cleaning-the-plate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 11:04:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/12/cleaning-the-plate/</guid>
      <description>My wife has always told me, &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t eat everything in your plate, leave something!&amp;rdquo; It is her believe, and her culture&amp;rsquo;s, that only poor people eats everything, and that if I do so, it will show I am dying of hunger, and thus, poor. If it were so, what&amp;rsquo;s wrong with being poor? Why will I leave food on the plate, food that I really like, to pretend what I am not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warming up to Emoji</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/01/08/warming-up-to-emoji/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 19:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/01/08/warming-up-to-emoji/</guid>
      <description>No long ago I wrote that I loathed Emoji. My main grumble was their usage abuse, and, especially, the overuse of &amp;ldquo;smilies.&amp;rdquo;
Since Apple&amp;rsquo;s iOS 10, I have been warming up to them, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t until I came across Mu-An that they really started to captivate me. She uses them, sparingly, but with such taste! A few of her repositories exclusively deal with Emoji as well. Thus, this post is to correct myself: I don&amp;rsquo;t loathe Emoji.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What have you taught me?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/10/29/what-have-you-taught-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/10/29/what-have-you-taught-me/</guid>
      <description>His father was only giving him a small advise, worried for him. Parents worry too much, sometimes. It was not taken well.
“You suffocate me, don’t worry so much about me! Enough advise, what have you taught me, until now?” He asks. Perhaps no much, the father thinks in retrospect. Brushing the teeth, maybe? Lacing the shoes? How to clean the arse? How to respect others, and do good? To be happy, love, study hard, work hard?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Violin Lessons</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/04/29/violin-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/04/29/violin-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Just as they started, randomly, on a whim, as a child desire to learn to play the violin, the lessons that Kent has been taking for almost two years came to an end two weeks ago. It was hard to tell Julie &amp;mdash; his teacher &amp;mdash; that he was not to continue, but it was what he wanted.
Kent never intended to play violin professionally, it was no more than an artistic hobby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Alone</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/12/17/home-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/12/17/home-alone/</guid>
      <description>Just like I did on July 18, 2014, this one is mostly for keeping a record of a first time activity or occasion. This time it was Kent&amp;rsquo;s first home alone day. He is almost 15 years old, and for the first time he spent eight hours home alone, while Kim and I were at work.
Happy &amp;ldquo;graduation&amp;rdquo; step, Kent!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard and Daylight Savings Time</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/11/01/standard-and-daylight-savings-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/11/01/standard-and-daylight-savings-time/</guid>
      <description>Standard Time. When I was a child, an old lady I loved as my own grandmother used to tell me this time was &amp;ldquo;God&amp;rsquo;s time,&amp;rdquo; and that she never changed clocks when everyone else switched to &amp;ldquo;Daylight Savings Time.&amp;rdquo; I wish I could do the same, unfortunately I am not old enough not to care.
I am part of the growing group that believes DST (or time changing of any kind) is worthless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neighbors</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/20/neighbors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/20/neighbors/</guid>
      <description>Our neighbors are moving. The ones on the left, that is. They have been our neighbors for fifteen years, and lived here for seventeen, since the community was built. Quiet neighbors, the best kind. Now we roll the dice, and hope for the best, for whoever comes next.
The house on the right has had three owners; we have known them all. The first were the previous owners of our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reminders</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/19/reminders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/19/reminders/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;What did you have for lunch?,&amp;rdquo; the father asks while driving home. &amp;ldquo;Same as usual,&amp;rdquo; he replies. &amp;ldquo;And that is?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I just eat random sandwiches of what comes to whim.&amp;rdquo; The father processes that for a bit. &amp;ldquo;I see.&amp;rdquo; Later, at home, &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s there for homework today?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;No much,&amp;rdquo; he says. &amp;ldquo;Brush your teeth,&amp;rdquo; he is reminded. Later, in the evening. &amp;ldquo;Take a shower.&amp;rdquo; A few times.
Just before the father goes to sleep, and sees his bedroom lights on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP Classes</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/16/ap-classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/16/ap-classes/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday (15 October) Kent told me he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to take AP (Advanced Placement) classes next year. He also told me he might not want to be a neurological surgeon after all, and that he really doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what he will want to be, professionally. We talked more, but the rest of it has no place in here.
Amongst the many feelings I am experiencing, regret is one of them. If only my parents were alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backing up and Restoring GPG Keys</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/13/backing-up-and-restoring-gpg-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/13/backing-up-and-restoring-gpg-keys/</guid>
      <description>If you use GPG to occasionally encrypt and/or sign your email, or to encrypt your files before placing them on the cloud, you will understand how important it is to have a backup of your GPG keys. Similarly important will be to know how to restore them as well.
Backing up your keys and configuration files To back your private, and public keys, as well as your trust database, you will do1:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enticement</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/10/enticement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/10/enticement/</guid>
      <description>Someone decided to entice us to fill out a survey, by sending us a &amp;ldquo;lucky&amp;rdquo; two dollars bill with it. Normally we do not fill out any type of surveys, unless proper remuneration is provided. Two dollars isn&amp;rsquo;t really worth the effort, and normally would not be accepted as a fee. Yet, since there is no way to send it back with assurances it will reach the original sender, we have a small dilemma on hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Martian</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/10/the-martian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/10/the-martian/</guid>
      <description>We just came from seeing the movie &amp;ldquo;The Martian.&amp;rdquo; Minus the obvious, very predictable, Hollywood scenes, the movie was quite alright. It made me wish I could live to see the first few missions to the Red Planet. Being the selfless guy that I am, thought, I would be willing to settle if my child gets to see them instead.
While on the topic of movies, and theaters, it is amazing how expensive it is to see a movie these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of no Use</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/of-no-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/of-no-use/</guid>
      <description>A farmer got so old that he couldn&amp;rsquo;t work the fields anymore. So he would spend the day just sitting on the porch. His son, still working the farm, would look up from time to time and see his father sitting there.
&amp;ldquo;He&amp;rsquo;s of no use any more,&amp;rdquo; the son thought to himself, &amp;ldquo;he doesn&amp;rsquo;t do anything!&amp;ldquo;
One day the son got so frustrated by this, that he built a wood coffin, dragged it over to the porch, and told his father to get in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space for the Dead</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/space-for-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/space-for-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>I read an article today on The Guardian, which showed up on the eight page of Hacker’s News. It talks about the lack of space for the dead, in the world of the living.
 &amp;ldquo;Some 55 million people are reckoned to pass away each year (about 0.8% of the planet’s total population – equivalent to 100% of England’s). Yet urban planners and developers focus overwhelmingly on accommodating and making money from the living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tempus Fugit</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/tempus-fugit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/04/tempus-fugit/</guid>
      <description>Time seems to be passing by too fast. Way too fast.
A week starts and then it is over when I blink. Same applies to weekends. It used to be that time seemed to pass quick only when engaged in something. Lately it is the same, whether I am busy or not. I am afraid I will blink again, and I will be gone.
Amongst the many things we can’t control, time is the one that hurts the most, especially as we grow older.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On a Rock</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/01/on-a-rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/01/on-a-rock/</guid>
      <description>From our last vacation&amp;mdash;which occurred four months ago&amp;mdash;to Colorado. This one was taken somewhere around Pikes Peak. Kent was daring, and Kim was afraid. I took the photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/26/saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/26/saturday/</guid>
      <description>Respect others, seek peace, do not be irascible. Give, help, construct; never the opposite. Turn lemons into lemonade. Hard things to do, most of the time, even more so all the time. We are so recalcitrant by nature!
Yet, our existence would be idyllic if we could manage to, at least, try to do all of the above often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shogi</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/20/shogi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/20/shogi/</guid>
      <description>Kent&amp;rsquo;s latest hobby is to play Shogi. That makes me an obligatory player and fan as well since, just like chess, Shogi requires two players. We bought a cheap board from Amazon, but he has already stated that a better quality board and pieces is what he would want for Christmas (yes, he is already planning for it).
The game isn&amp;rsquo;t difficult to play, but I am having an excruciating hard time remembering each piece — labeled with kanji characters — and how they move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Loathe Emoji</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/18/i-loathe-emoji/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/18/i-loathe-emoji/</guid>
      <description>I despise Emoji and emoticons, specially graphical emoji, or people who continuously abuse them, and interject them in every single sentence they type, sometimes even more than once. I thought that I hated &amp;ldquo;LOL,&amp;rdquo; which I do, but I would rather see LOL &amp;mdash; when justified, not the moronic &amp;ldquo;LOL&amp;rdquo; without reason you see often &amp;mdash; than see the utter idiotic smiles, winks, etc., continuously, all the time. &amp;ldquo;I am an elitist asshole, but here, have an Emoji!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never-ending Homework</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/14/neverending-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/14/neverending-homework/</guid>
      <description>Ever since Kent started the 9th grade he has been having to do an unusual amount, and I mean really unusual, of homework. I might be getting too old, but I do not recall having to do that much, so early into high school. It is really messing up his sleeping schedule, and&amp;ndash;kind of&amp;ndash;mine.
Going to sleep really late each day, and waking up when sun still sleeps is wearing me out too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me, but you, but me</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/28/me-but-you-but-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/28/me-but-you-but-me/</guid>
      <description>On May 28, 2010, Mark Pilgrim wrote the entry below on his weblog. He has since long been gone, but I am keeping this entry, named &amp;ldquo;Me, but you, but me,&amp;rdquo; which I liked very much. I really wish he would come back.
I’ve been active online for 9 years now. With one exception, nothing I’ve done online has brought me closer to making 25-year friends. Life online rewards breadth, not depth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding little to talk about</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/03/30/little-to-talk-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/03/30/little-to-talk-about/</guid>
      <description>The main problem with Jekyll is that is out of the way. Unlike other weblog engines, which are managed via the web, I come to the shell to type and process this. Perhaps I need to research a better workflow?
 I am finding little to talk about lately, and that is keeping things here rather quiet. It is not only that I do not have much to write, but that when the desire arrives it gets lost in translation, mostly because of the way I have decided to handle this little space of mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy 2015!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/12/31/happy-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/12/31/happy-2015/</guid>
      <description>Here we go again. Not complaining, as there is nothing to complain about. Just another year. It seems 2014 flew by quite fast, will you agree? Nevertheless, happy 2015 everyone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where are you from?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/07/30/where-are-you-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/07/30/where-are-you-from/</guid>
      <description>In the States, looking different and/or having an accent will get you asked &amp;ldquo;Where are you from?&amp;rdquo; It doesn&amp;rsquo;t fail, it happens all the time.
Why are we so concerned about knowing someone&amp;rsquo;s country of origin? What difference does it make? If anything, it might be a knowledge we do not want to have. Knowing from where someone is from might spark stereotypical comments and behaviors that would jeopardize an otherwise perfect encounter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Braces</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/07/18/on-braces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/07/18/on-braces/</guid>
      <description>This is mainly for our records. Today Kent got his braces on, and thus it begins a few months of uncomfortable chewing, special diet, fastidious brushing and everything else that comes with braces.
Now I must go to sell some blood, and place one of my kidneys for sale on the black market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four-Way Stop</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/02/19/four-way-stop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/02/19/four-way-stop/</guid>
      <description>Drivers in Orlando do not seem to know what to do when they reach a four way stop. It really makes me wonder how were they able to obtain a drivers license without that knowledge, as it is part of Drivers Handbook (search for &amp;ldquo;Stop Signs&amp;rdquo; on that page), the test, and occasionally encountered while driving.
For the record, and in case you live in Orlando, and do not know what to do on a four-way stop (also known as all-way stop), these are the basics:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Winter Morning Small Talk</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/cold-winter-morning-small-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/cold-winter-morning-small-talk/</guid>
      <description>We have 36 Fahrenheit degrees this morning (2.2&amp;deg; Celsius). That is mighty cold for almost-always warm, sunny Florida. I stressed it to my child yesternight: he must wear warm clothes the next day. Reluctantly he said &amp;ldquo;OK&amp;rdquo;.
Then comes this morning, and the iMessages exchange look like this:
  Child :  &amp;ldquo;Mama is trying to make me wear an incredibly uncomfortable shirt and is yelling like a siren.&amp;rdquo;   Me :  &amp;ldquo;Why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specialization is for Insects</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/specialization-is-for-insects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/specialization-is-for-insects/</guid>
      <description>From Robert Heinlein&amp;rsquo;s science fiction book, Time Enough for Love:
 &amp;ldquo;A human being should be able to change a diaper, plan an invasion, butcher a hog, conn a ship, design a building, write a sonnet, balance accounts, build a wall, set a bone, comfort the dying, take orders, give orders, cooperate, act alone, solve equations, analyze a new problem, pitch manure, program a computer, cook a tasty meal, fight efficiently, die gallantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sands of Time</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/04/the-sands-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/04/the-sands-of-time/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It is said that some lives are linked across time connected by an ancient calling that echoes through the ages. Destiny.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;mdash; Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time
 I do not believe on such thing as destiny, but the line above from the movie is certainly touching. The movie itself is quite nice. Last night we watched it for the fourth time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy MMXIV everyone!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/01/happy-mmxiv-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/01/happy-mmxiv-everyone/</guid>
      <description>Now that we have gone around the Sun one more time, we simply start doing it again. We don&amp;rsquo;t fool ourselves, it is not by choice. And with this new elliptical orbit we walk into age, which will lead, ultimately, to our demise. It is a simple concept.
Leaving the obvious behind, what&amp;rsquo;s left is to enjoy what we have. To try being nice to others, to the best of our abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is All around Us</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/29/it-is-all-around-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/29/it-is-all-around-us/</guid>
      <description>Love. It really is.
 &amp;ldquo;Whenever I get gloomy with the state of the world, I think about the arrivals gate at Heathrow Airport. General opinion&amp;rsquo;s starting to make out that we live in a world of hatred and greed, but I don&amp;rsquo;t see that. It seems to me that love is everywhere. Often it&amp;rsquo;s not particularly dignified or newsworthy, but it&amp;rsquo;s always there &amp;mdash; fathers and sons, mothers and daughters, husbands and wives, boyfriends, girlfriends, old friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joy of Reading Hemingway</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/27/the-joy-of-reading-hemingway/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/27/the-joy-of-reading-hemingway/</guid>
      <description>Recently, Kent had the misfortune of picking &amp;ldquo;A Moveable Feast&amp;rdquo;, by Ernest Hemingway, for a school assignment. I know I am not the right person1 to judge anyone&amp;rsquo;s writing style, I am simply recollecting the comments Kent has made while reading the book.
So far, other than finding the book boring &amp;mdash; mind it, he is barely 13 &amp;mdash; he is puzzled at the use of French terms that he wonders how would the &amp;ldquo;everyday&amp;rdquo; American reader comprehend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/it-is-christmas-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/it-is-christmas-day/</guid>
      <description>One of the many things to look forward to each year is, of course, the end of year holidays. Christmas, Festivus, or whatever you call it, the end of December is always a special time. My only complain, and that might be yours too, is that it comes and goes so fast! Kent has finished opening his presents, and somehow it feels &amp;ldquo;it is all over.&amp;rdquo; But we waited the whole year for this!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies to Watch during Christmas</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/movies-to-watch-during-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/25/movies-to-watch-during-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Christmas is not the same without watching certain movies. The ones that are always a must for me are &amp;ldquo;National Lampoon&amp;rsquo;s European Vacation&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;National Lampoon&amp;rsquo;s Christmas Vacation&amp;rdquo;. As I type this I am getting ready to watch them both. Those are the ones to laugh to tears and have fun. The other favorite one &amp;ndash;please don&amp;rsquo;t hate me&amp;ndash; is &amp;ldquo;The Sound of Music.&amp;rdquo; There is something about it that just does it for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Mobile and the iPad</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/24/tmobile-and-the-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/24/tmobile-and-the-ipad/</guid>
      <description>I am not sure about the other mobile telephony providers, but this morning I went to T-Mobile with the intention of buying an iPad mini. They had only the dark colour in stock, and on 32GB capacity &amp;ndash; I was wanting a 16GB. The transaction was almost finished, when I was asked for a telephone number. After stating that I just wanted the iPad, no connection, I was told they could only sell it, if it was with a mobile data plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas Tree Small Story</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/23/a-christmas-tree-small-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/23/a-christmas-tree-small-story/</guid>
      <description>Last year we had a plastic Christmas tree. Wife was not happy. This year she wanted a real one, so this morning the child and I went on the quest of getting it. Most families in the States will get a Christmas tree right after Thanksgiving, but I am used to get it the day before Christmas. Of course, if I wait for that day there will be none left. So it is today, or never1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World, or Hello Again!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/21/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/21/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post. It seems I have started writing occasionally again. I still conserve the old posts, from the previous weblog. Not sure many of them were worth of keeping, but I might browse through them and pick one or two to bring back here.
This time I will keep this simple. Well, as simple as a person with slight OCD can keep it. I promise, I think. This little site is generated by Jekyll and hosted on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morale</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2012/10/31/morale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2012/10/31/morale/</guid>
      <description>Last week I wrote about Kent’s Spelling Bee, and how preparing for it was hard for him and I.
Well, the Bee came and went, and I forgot to come back to post the results. He misspelled &amp;ldquo;morale&amp;rdquo; (he spelled it as &amp;ldquo;moral&amp;rdquo;) and finished in 4th place&amp;mdash;for me, it doesn’t make sense, as I have always considered first, second and third place relevant, but fourth?&amp;mdash;, which still qualified him to go to the State competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spelling Bee</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2012/10/21/spelling-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2012/10/21/spelling-bee/</guid>
      <description>As a foreigner, trying to go over a Spelling Bee word list with my kid is nothing less than a challenge. For the both of us. First, there are the words I have never seeing; those I can&amp;rsquo;t pronounce. Second, there are the words I will mispronounce. And third, there are the ones I don&amp;rsquo;t know what they mean.
If you add to that the fact that the kid is learning them, hence bound to make many mistakes&amp;hellip; well, yes, a challenge, to put it mildly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mi Vieja</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/12/03/mi-vieja/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/12/03/mi-vieja/</guid>
      <description>She created me, all my flaws and gifts unintended. She nurtured and guided me through life the best she could, suffering for my mistakes &amp;mdash;but always hopeful&amp;mdash; and rejoicing on my victories. Always supportive she gave herself to me (and my siblings), selflessly.
After a lifetime mission, her time around here has expired. We knew it would come, but never fully prepared for it. And so we wept, sadness seeping through us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Social</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/08/03/non-social/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/08/03/non-social/</guid>
      <description>Almost over two years ago I left Facebook. A few months ago I left LinkedIn and Twitter. Two weeks ago I left Google+. I also left Groupon (I don&amp;rsquo;t even know why I ever sign up for that junk!). Next is to leave here. I guess this is my way to pursuit happiness.
As Mark weblog is gone1 &amp;mdash;perhaps step 9 was, &amp;ldquo;Get rid of the weblog&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash; I enumerate what he wrote:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ritual of Seduction</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/05/27/operation-seduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/05/27/operation-seduction/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The ritual &amp;mdash;considered old-fashioned nowadays by just about everyone under the age of 60&amp;mdash; was traditionally a ceremonial, sacred gesture; its history can be traced to ancient Greece and Rome. In the Middle Ages, a vassal paid homage to his lord by kissing his hand. By the 19th century, hand kissing had been reinvented to convey a man&amp;rsquo;s gallantry and politesse toward a woman. Those men who still practice it today know the rules: never kiss a gloved hand or the hand of a young girl; kiss the hand only of a married woman, and do so only indoors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I thought when my plane crashed</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/05/12/what-i-thought-when-my-plane-crashed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/05/12/what-i-thought-when-my-plane-crashed/</guid>
      <description>From CNN Opinion, this article, written by Ric Elias I liked. I liked it so much, I decided to keep it here, for when it is not longer available at CNN. As I did with a previous article I kept from the WSJ, if CNN does not likes what I have done, let me know and I will remove it, or adapt it to a compromise. Please do not sue me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawing a blank, again</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/04/11/drawing-a-blank-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/04/11/drawing-a-blank-again/</guid>
      <description>Drawing a blank.
 Lost in a search of identity, on a broader scale Consumed by the unknowns Overflowed by love; furious for not knowing why Feeling I am missing something Moving towards the end  Drawing a blank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find what you love</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/04/11/find-what-you-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/04/11/find-what-you-love/</guid>
      <description>Steve Jobs commencement address at Stanford University, in 2005:
 Remembering that I’ll be dead soon is the most important tool I’ve ever encountered to help me make the big choices in life. Because almost everything — all external expectations, all pride, all fear of embarrassment or failure — these things just fall away in the face of death, leaving only what is truly important. Remembering that you are going to die is the best way I know to avoid the trap of thinking you have something to lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Many changes coming soon</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/04/01/many-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/04/01/many-changes/</guid>
      <description>Just very recently I wrote about me moving to Jekyll from WordPress:
 After much thought, and tinkering, I decided to ditch my six year old or so WordPress and start blogging like a hacker with the awesome Jekyll.
 I also wrote —fairly recently— about living on a Linode:
 Moved to Linode. Love it, highly recommend it. They reward customers that bring referrals, but notice my links do not have any referral code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science Fair 1st Place</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/03/24/science-fair-1st-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/03/24/science-fair-1st-place/</guid>
      <description>Kent did it again (and we are so happy and proud of him!). The last time he brought home an award was for being on Principal’s list. This time he has gotten first place on Elementary School Science Fair. His project was “How is Electricity produced?”
Off topic, we need a new camera to replace our aged Powershot (Canon PowerShot A640). Any tips?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Augustine</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/03/12/st-augustine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/03/12/st-augustine/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I went with Kent and classmates to St. Augustine, the oldest continuously occupied European established city and port in the continental United States.
It was a great trip, we learned a lot, we saw a lot, it was cold, we came home tired. We will return&amp;hellip; one day. The end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday, Viejo!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/02/27/happy-birthday-viejo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/02/27/happy-birthday-viejo/</guid>
      <description>Not a day goes by without me thinking of my Dad. Today he would have being 92 years old.
I still remember him on his 90th birthday, doing push ups using only three fingers on each hand. I will forever remember the endless stories he used to tell, and his constant smile. He was the best father a son can ask for, an example for many. It hurts so very much not to have him around anymore&amp;hellip;!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A good day</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/20/a-good-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/20/a-good-day/</guid>
      <description>There is nothing sweeter than waking up and hear your kid say &amp;ldquo;Have a good day Pap&amp;aacute;. Good bye!&amp;rdquo; It made my day. Thank you, Super Duper!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Brotherhood</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/12/the-brotherhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/12/the-brotherhood/</guid>
      <description>Recently I got the PS3 game &amp;ldquo;Assassin Creed Brotherhood&amp;rdquo; for my birthday and it has being very fun. My dad got me the Harlequin code, and playing him is very fun as well. I have already gotten the armor of Brutus, the very best on the game. Needless is to say, I already finished the game, but am still &amp;ldquo;renovating&amp;rdquo; things.
&amp;mdash; Kent</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steal everything</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/04/steal-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/04/steal-everything/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Nothing is original. Steal from anywhere that resonates with inspiration or fuels your imagination. Devour old films, new films, music, books, paintings, photographs, poems, dreams, random conversations, architecture, bridges, street signs, trees, clouds, bodies of water, light and shadows. Select only things to steal from that speak directly to your soul. If you do this, your work (and theft) will be authentic. Authenticity is invaluable; originality is nonexistent. And don’t bother concealing your thievery—celebrate it if you feel like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas Tree</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/12/19/a-christmas-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/12/19/a-christmas-tree/</guid>
      <description>After a small, but heated battle, on whether or not to buy a real tree for Christmas (Kent and I said no, Kim said yes), Kent and Alyssa are now decorating a Fraser pine tree. I am sure you guessed who won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragons can be killed</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/10/08/dragons-can-be-killed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/10/08/dragons-can-be-killed/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fairy tales do not tell children the dragons exist. Children already know that dragons exist. Fairy tales tell children the dragons can be killed.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;mdash; G. K. Chesterton
 &amp;ldquo;By confining your child to blameless stories of child life in which nothing at all alarming ever happened, you would fail to banish the terrors, and would succeed in banishing all that can ennoble them or make them endurable. For in the fairy tales, side by side with the terrible figures, we find the immemorial comforters and protectors, the radiant ones; and the terrible figures are not merely terrible, but sublime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva Spain!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/07/11/viva-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/07/11/viva-spain/</guid>
      <description>Woohoo! Spain, Champions of Europe and now Champions of the World! What an amazing match! So excited! Now I can&amp;rsquo;t hardly wait until the next World Cup! :-) Viva Espa&amp;ntilde;a! Viva Espa&amp;ntilde;a!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Unthinkable</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/06/25/the-unthinkable/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/06/25/the-unthinkable/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I did the unthinkable. Something I have never done &amp;mdash; nor will I do again &amp;mdash; before. I went very early (03:15) to stand at the Millenia all, to be one of the first (or so I thought) to buy the iPhone 4.
I don&amp;rsquo;t want to write long about something I am more than half way ashamed of. Suffice it to say that I got an iPhone 4 after standing in line for 14 hours (17:15).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A month</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/06/23/a-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/06/23/a-month/</guid>
      <description>It has been a month since our Jean passed away. Times flies, yet it seems like it was yesterday. Nor a day has passed by without coming to mind, one way or another. We miss her like we did the first day. I truly dislike Warcraft, but I am keeping her toons alive, and advancing. Somehow playing something she dedicated so much time on, where she had so many good friends, gives me the feeling she still lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back from vacations</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/06/20/back-from-vacations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/06/20/back-from-vacations/</guid>
      <description>We are back from vacations. It was a great one, but at the end we agreed that there is no place like home, for many reasons. They are mostly minor things, to which we have grown accustom to, but that combined make the type of life we live. I might detail some of those little things later.
A few posts will be due, to narrate some relevant things from the trip: Iberia and our misplaced luggages (and their English/Spanish phones lines), Hertz and our lemon like rental car, speed limits, Aix-en-Provence hotel, and the high cost of everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kent on Principal&#39;s List</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/06/04/kent-principals-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2010 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/06/04/kent-principals-list/</guid>
      <description>Kent&amp;rsquo;s school Awards Ceremony was today. I did not take a picture there, but filmed a bit. The photo above was taken afterwards, at home. He was so happy &amp;ndash;and I so proud of him!&amp;ndash; to receive the trophy for being the whole third academic year on the Principal&amp;rsquo;s List (straight A in all subjects).
I am lucky I got him to smile too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R.I.P. Dixie J. McCoy</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/06/01/dixie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/06/01/dixie/</guid>
      <description>Our Dixie died in her sleep, on May 23rd, 2010. Her death brought sorrow, and she is greatly missed each day. We will never forget her sweetness, kindness, good advise&amp;hellip; Her gentle smile will live in our memories.
Rest in peace Maxie Bizzenscooter, Astlyr, Thorir, kitty, Dixie Jean McCoy. We loved you, we miss you, we will remember you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s decided</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/05/05/its-decided/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/05/05/its-decided/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s decided, my next machine will be an Apple computer. Most likely I will end up buying a Mac Mini, although an iMac is also being considered. Now, who wants a (still under warranty) DELL XPS 630i? It is a Q6600 (quad), with 4GB RAM, 500GB HD, and NVIDIA 9800GT. Comes with Windows 7 Ultimate. Nice machine!
Note: Someone contacted me, but the email went to spam, and got deleted. Try again please, I have whitelisted the contact form address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPad 3G status</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/29/ipad-3g-status/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/29/ipad-3g-status/</guid>
      <description>It seems that it will be here tomorrow before, or around 3:00PM after all. Just when I was starting to lose my faith&amp;hellip; So happy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The wheels of justice</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/26/the-wheels-of-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/26/the-wheels-of-justice/</guid>
      <description>I thought twice before coming here and write two or three sentences. But sometimes two or three sentences is all you have. I had to do it: Apple Inc., you rock!
If you want to be a &amp;ldquo;journalist&amp;rdquo;, act as one. As Powazek wrote in a tweet, &amp;ldquo;Real journalists don&amp;rsquo;t buy stolen property.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clan of the Cave Bear</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/24/clan-of-the-cave-bear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/24/clan-of-the-cave-bear/</guid>
      <description>Just saw the Clan of the Cave Bear movie, for the first time, on it&amp;rsquo;s entirety. Great movie. Touching; got me a knot on the throat in more than one occasion. I think it is a sad movie, and brought up many memories. Sometimes movies, like music, have that effect. Sometimes it is just us, and how our mind works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend starts</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/24/weekend-starts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/24/weekend-starts/</guid>
      <description>The weekend has started. It really started yesterday&amp;rsquo;s afternoon, but who is keeping tabs? The fact is, it is here and thus it brings a dilemma. If I do nothing&amp;mdash;which is impossible if you have a kid&amp;mdash;the weekend will fly by. On the other hand, if I get busy&amp;mdash;and I will&amp;mdash;it will fly by as well.
There are little things in life that keeps you, in a short term, looking forward to a near future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Host hunting</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/11/24/host-hunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/11/24/host-hunting/</guid>
      <description>I had had all my websites &amp;mdash;this one, and many other test ones, etc&amp;mdash;, plus my self-managed DNS on ServerBeach (now part of Peer1) for a very long time. They all reside on a dedicated server, which has, sadly, reached it&amp;rsquo;s end of life (EOL).
Although I can keep it as it is, doing so represents a liability problem, as I will be out of luck, should it decide to fail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selling iPhone</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/10/13/selling-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/10/13/selling-iphone/</guid>
      <description>In an effort to start saving money towards an Android based device (would love HTC Hero), I am selling my 2G 16GB iPhone. As the eBay listing reads, it is a very well kept, 2G 16GB iPhone, unlocked and jailbroken. No scratches, no blemishes. Bid starts at $1, no reserve. Yes, $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IP migration</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/09/09/ip-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/09/09/ip-migration/</guid>
      <description>I have a deadline to meet. I must migrate all my servers, and clients to a private IP space. Servers must be done &amp;mdash; if at all possible &amp;mdash; by September 30th. Clients by October 30th. That is, this year. Problem is, I have never done anything close to it, and there are so many things that need to be done at once, I don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start.
I have a Linux DNS/DHCP to change (Internet facing one).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world, again!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/09/02/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/09/02/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>I am starting over. I might &amp;ldquo;port&amp;rdquo; back some entries from the old weblog, but that&amp;rsquo;s pretty much it. Right now everything is in state of flux, running on a vanilla WordPress installation with a couple of plugins on. Work will progress as time permits.
There isn&amp;rsquo;t one single reason why I am starting over, but a few. Basically, the old weblog database was &amp;ldquo;dirty&amp;rdquo; with entries and rows, and tables from plugins&amp;hellip; and god knows what other things (I ran quite a few experiments on that one).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aion, the WoW killer</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/07/11/aion-the-wow-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/07/11/aion-the-wow-killer/</guid>
      <description>Aion isn&amp;rsquo;t out yet for North America or Europe, but has already caused long time WoW players to quit. That is what my household has done, ending the life of two, four years old, accounts.
Beta 4 is coming up, July 17th and we can hardly wait. Preorder will give you access to the beta, so go ahead! Simply Google Aion and follow the appropiated link.
While we wait, it feels good to be out of WoW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safari 4 Beta</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/02/24/safari-4-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/02/24/safari-4-beta/</guid>
      <description>Safari 4 Beta is out and it is rocking. Apple has adopted (copied) quite a bit from Chrome interface and I have to say the browser looks and behaves awesomely under Windows 7.
But, why bore you with senseless praise? Go download it, and see it for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email liturgy</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/01/07/email-liturgy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/01/07/email-liturgy/</guid>
      <description>I miss the days when emails were written with thought, and care. They were clear, and to the point. There was no HTML in them; replies were perfectly quoted, references were neatly annotated. Emoticons were kept to a minimum, if any.
No one does that anymore&amp;hellip; well, not many of us do. I haven&amp;rsquo;t give up, I insist. For me, sending and replying emails is a liturgy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NETBROS.COM for sale</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/12/02/netbros-com-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/12/02/netbros-com-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I am selling this domain, which I have have since, well, I already lost count. If you are interested on buying this domain, please contact me. I would rather sell it directly than going through a broker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yet another</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/11/12/yet-another/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/11/12/yet-another/</guid>
      <description>Yet another long downtime on World of Warcraft, just in the verge of the release of the second major expansion for the game. What a royal mess! You would think Blizzard has it figured out by now, down to a science, but&amp;hellip;
I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine how tomorrow, with the expansion release, will be. Not going to &amp;ldquo;tune in.&amp;rdquo; Instead will let others have the &amp;ldquo;fun.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not allowed to tell</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/10/10/not-allowed-to-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/10/10/not-allowed-to-tell/</guid>
      <description>A local bank in front of which I sit quite often has a locked metal box sitting outside the branch. Yesterday my curiosity got sparked when I saw one of the employees (which I greet daily) opening it and taking a canvas bag out of it. When I asked what was the box for, she stopped like frozen, and muttered &amp;ldquo;Company doesn&amp;rsquo;t allow me to tell.&amp;ldquo;
Now, won&amp;rsquo;t you agree with me that such answer was a very silly &amp;mdash;and dangerous!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MCITP - Enterprise Server Administrator</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/08/10/mcitp-enterprise-server-administrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/08/10/mcitp-enterprise-server-administrator/</guid>
      <description>The last two weeks were very busy ones. I went through a Boot Camp and obtained the Microsoft Certified Information Technology Professional certification, as an Enterprise Server 2008 Administrator. Much more to do with the product, but migration is on my close horizon.
As a side note, and totally unrelated, I will change the way this weblog look soon. I will probably start over as well, all the old content gone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration and comments disabled</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/07/02/registration-and-comments-disabled/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/07/02/registration-and-comments-disabled/</guid>
      <description>I have grown tired of deleting bogus accounts. They do not do anything, they do not cause harm; it is just tiresome to delete, each day, 20 or 30 of them. So enough&amp;hellip; for now. Those who had an account (which was created using OpenID), still can comment, but no new registrations anymore.
As a matter of fact&amp;hellip; I think I will change this site completely. Soon&amp;hellip; ish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Einstein on religion</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/15/einstein-on-religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/15/einstein-on-religion/</guid>
      <description>Einstein: Letter to Eric Gutkind
 &amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; The word God is for me nothing more than the expression and product of human weaknesses, the Bible a collection of honourable, but still primitive legends which are nevertheless pretty childish. No interpretation no matter how subtle can for me change this. These subtilized interpretations are highly manifold according to their nature and have almost nothing to do with the original text. For me the Jewish religion like all other religions is an incarnation of the most childish superstitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prepare to pay more</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/30/prepare-to-pay-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/30/prepare-to-pay-more/</guid>
      <description>It seems that within four years &amp;ndash;if nothing is done to prevent it (and nobody really knows what to do)&amp;ndash; we [americans] will be paying $7 for a gallon of gasoline.
A very interesting post over Wired explains some of the reasons. A brief summary of them:
 Oil companies getting tax breaks, and not passing those savings down, but pocketing them. The economic development in China and India, which increases the demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day of sadness</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/27/a-day-of-sadness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/27/a-day-of-sadness/</guid>
      <description>Today we realized that we have lost our camcorder, and with it, all the memories we had since KM was born: from birth until his last birthday, at least. And the pain we feel can&amp;rsquo;t be explained. How could we be so stupid?!
Although we have thoughts, accusing ourselves for lots of things&amp;hellip; what sense does it make at this point? Everything is gone, and discussing the why&amp;rsquo;s, what if&amp;rsquo;s and so on will not bring the tapes back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The day Santa died</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/02/21/the-day-santa-died/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/02/21/the-day-santa-died/</guid>
      <description>Kim and I have always told Kent Santa exists. Almost every kid is told the same, and get presents delivered by the fat, white bearded guy each year. He gets all the credits, but kids are happy.
With Kent getting into first grade, he has been hearing things from his peers. Things like, &amp;ldquo;Santa doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Santa isn&amp;rsquo;t real&amp;rdquo;, so he began asking about it. About a month ago I told him his peers weren&amp;rsquo;t right, when he commented about it, and that by not believing in Santa they might not get presents next time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t step in the lines</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/01/11/dont-step-in-the-lines/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/01/11/dont-step-in-the-lines/</guid>
      <description>The child inside of us lives, I am a living proof. That, or I have some autistic tendencies. Or both. Having a child, I unintentionally behave like a child when I am with him but, also, when I am alone.
I have found myself avoiding to step on cracks on the floor, or on lines. When challenged with floors with multiple lines together, which are difficult or impossible to avoid, I either find and alternative route, or simply enlarge my pattern of what I consider lined space, like lined areas of different colors become empty spaces &amp;ndash;without lines&amp;ndash;, for example, all the black mosaic, even though it has lines, becomes a &amp;ldquo;flat&amp;rdquo; and the lines not to be stepped on become those who divide the black mosaic space from a different colored space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy 2008!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/31/happy-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/31/happy-2008/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone out there! Please, love one another. Be safe. Happy New Year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas is gone, or is it?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/27/christmas-is-gone-or-is-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/27/christmas-is-gone-or-is-it/</guid>
      <description>The long whole year wait, for many, comes to an end quite fast. It seems it takes a long time until Christmas arrives, but when it does, it goes away very quickly. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s not fair&amp;rdquo;, Kim says. Well, I am that type of crazy individual that sings Christmas Carols, listen to Christmas music and lives the &amp;ldquo;Christmas spirit&amp;rdquo; pretty much all year round. I have my ups and downs like everyone else, but I refuse to let Christmas be a one day celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa gets the extra love</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/19/santa-gets-the-extra-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/19/santa-gets-the-extra-love/</guid>
      <description>KM believes in Santa. It is that childish fantasy we do not want to spoil quite yet. But the fat guy, with red cheeks, who pilots a sleigh pulled by reindeers, gets all the extra love &amp;ndash;and credits&amp;ndash; for the job we, as parents, do during Christmas time. I challenge Santa to come up with a Wii!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I had to have them</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/14/i-had-to-have-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/14/i-had-to-have-them/</guid>
      <description>I found this weblog, via Kottke, and in it, this post I like: So long Flight of the Conchords. And I loved it. I had to have the list of videos on that log here1, to show wife, to play them at a later time. Simply awesome. And here they come (links go to Youtube):
 The most beautiful girl in the room - “you could be a part-time model”. Humans are dead - the robot one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate school</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/09/i-hate-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/09/i-hate-school/</guid>
      <description>When your, almost seven years old, son tells you he hates going to school you worry. It is not the first time that KM tells me he doesn&amp;rsquo;t like going to school. He goes to a private, Christian school, and his main complain has always being that he doesn&amp;rsquo;t like to memorize the weekly versicle. I have noticed that this &amp;ldquo;disliking&amp;rdquo; normally comes after a weekend, holiday, or similar &amp;lsquo;time off school&amp;rsquo; occasion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, they sold it</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/07/yes-they-sold-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/07/yes-they-sold-it/</guid>
      <description>A while ago, I wrote about the closing of the C3 School, previously known as Parkway Preparatory School. As many other parents and staff, I was sad to see the school my kid attended to disappearing. And there were rumors, so I asked a senior Pastor (do not remember his name now) about them. I was told the Church wasn&amp;rsquo;t going anywhere, that the rumors about selling the Church were unfounded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farewell Maestro</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/09/06/farewell-maestro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/09/06/farewell-maestro/</guid>
      <description>Luciano Pavarotti has died. &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; One of the most popular contemporary vocal performers in the world of opera and across multiple musical genres..&amp;rdquo; The world grieves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First day at school</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/08/20/first-day-at-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/08/20/first-day-at-school/</guid>
      <description>Today is Kent&amp;rsquo;s first day at school, after the long &amp;ndash;although it did not seemed that long&amp;ndash; summer vacation. It is his first grade, on a new school and I have &amp;ldquo;the jitters.&amp;rdquo; I worry for my son, all the time. I enjoyed this summer with him more than anything in the world. You can&amp;rsquo;t stop them from growing up, you can&amp;rsquo;t be with them all the time. But it is so hard not to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>