<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>images on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/images/</link>
    <description>Recent content in images on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:34:10 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/images/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplicity</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/22/simplicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:34:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/22/simplicity/</guid>
      <description>That is a screenshot of my macOS desktop. It could be simpler, but as it is it does what I need, and want. When I need to use an app, I simply hit command (⌘) space and start typing the app name to launch it. That is, I use Spotlight.
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great that iOS could be customized like that too? Preferably it would be a setting, that would allow to turn off the visibility of all, or any app on the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Meltdown</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/another-meltdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 21:19:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/another-meltdown/</guid>
      <description>Someone is having another meltdown.
 The Mueller probe should never have been started in that there was no collusion and there was no crime. It was based on fraudulent activities and a Fake Dossier paid for by Crooked Hillary and the DNC, and improperly used in FISA COURT for surveillance of my campaign. WITCH HUNT!
 😂
Now, there is a background for his latest fit.
Yesterday, 16 March, Jeff Sessions fired Andrew McCabe, the FBI deputy director.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flowers Will Follow</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/flowers-will-follow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 18:17:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/flowers-will-follow/</guid>
      <description>To the untrained, this image will have little meaning. Who could imagine that those &amp;ldquo;ugly sticks,&amp;rdquo; as the child called them, will soon bloom into hundreds of beautiful yellow flowers? Yet, as it has happened each year, flowers will follow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching for The Car</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/searching-for-the-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 17:15:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/searching-for-the-car/</guid>
      <description>A year ago, Kent got his learner&amp;rsquo;s permit. With the help of John, and a little from me, he practiced driving for over 250 hours. A year later — more or less — on 9 March, he got his driver&amp;rsquo;s license, passing the practical test with a 96, out of 100 points, score. And so the asking for a car began.
What car should we get for a 17 year old?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adrian Lamo Has Died</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/16/adrian-lamo-has-died/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:53:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/16/adrian-lamo-has-died/</guid>
      <description>Adrian Lamo, mostly known as the hacker who broke into several major companies computer networks, and indirectly reported Chelsea Manning, has died — cause unknown thus far. The news was posted on Hacker News, of course, and I found one the comments — true or not — left there interesting.
 I had a car, while my friend did not, and Adrian had traveled via transit, so I spent the day with them hopping around town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Goes After Trump Org</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/15/mueller-goes-after-trump-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 19:50:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/15/mueller-goes-after-trump-org/</guid>
      <description>I have disliked other presidents in the past, for actions taken while they were in the office that I — and many others — considered stupid, crazy, or just plain wrong. My dislike for the current president eclipses any of my previous. I voted for Hillary, and wrongly predicted that she would win the presidency.
Today news, although perhaps inconsequential, brings joy to an otherwise political nightmare.
 The special counsel, Robert S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comey Sacking</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/05/11/comey-sacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 16:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/05/11/comey-sacking/</guid>
      <description>This is, at least for me, completely surreal. It is not only that Trump sacked the FBI director &amp;mdash; who arguably helped him getting elected President &amp;mdash; while he was conducting an investigation on Trump&amp;rsquo;s presidential campaign, but the way he wrote the sacking letter (I emphasised):
 Dear Director Comey:
I have received the attached letters from the Attorney General and Deputy Attorney General of the United States recommending your dismissal as the Director of the Federal Bureau of Investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enticement</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/10/enticement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/10/enticement/</guid>
      <description>Someone decided to entice us to fill out a survey, by sending us a &amp;ldquo;lucky&amp;rdquo; two dollars bill with it. Normally we do not fill out any type of surveys, unless proper remuneration is provided. Two dollars isn&amp;rsquo;t really worth the effort, and normally would not be accepted as a fee. Yet, since there is no way to send it back with assurances it will reach the original sender, we have a small dilemma on hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On a Rock</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/01/on-a-rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/01/on-a-rock/</guid>
      <description>From our last vacation&amp;mdash;which occurred four months ago&amp;mdash;to Colorado. This one was taken somewhere around Pikes Peak. Kent was daring, and Kim was afraid. I took the photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shogi</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/20/shogi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/20/shogi/</guid>
      <description>Kent&amp;rsquo;s latest hobby is to play Shogi. That makes me an obligatory player and fan as well since, just like chess, Shogi requires two players. We bought a cheap board from Amazon, but he has already stated that a better quality board and pieces is what he would want for Christmas (yes, he is already planning for it).
The game isn&amp;rsquo;t difficult to play, but I am having an excruciating hard time remembering each piece — labeled with kanji characters — and how they move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mi Vieja</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/12/03/mi-vieja/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/12/03/mi-vieja/</guid>
      <description>She created me, all my flaws and gifts unintended. She nurtured and guided me through life the best she could, suffering for my mistakes &amp;mdash;but always hopeful&amp;mdash; and rejoicing on my victories. Always supportive she gave herself to me (and my siblings), selflessly.
After a lifetime mission, her time around here has expired. We knew it would come, but never fully prepared for it. And so we wept, sadness seeping through us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve P. Jobs, 1955 - 2011</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/10/05/steve-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/10/05/steve-jobs/</guid>
      <description>A great man has passed away. While mourning, we celebrate all he brought to us&amp;hellip; his many accomplishments. He will not be forgotten.
February 24, 1955 &amp;ndash; October 5, 2011</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science Fair 1st Place</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/03/24/science-fair-1st-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/03/24/science-fair-1st-place/</guid>
      <description>Kent did it again (and we are so happy and proud of him!). The last time he brought home an award was for being on Principal’s list. This time he has gotten first place on Elementary School Science Fair. His project was “How is Electricity produced?”
Off topic, we need a new camera to replace our aged Powershot (Canon PowerShot A640). Any tips?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan Earthquake and Tsunami</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/03/14/japan-earthquake-tsunami-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/03/14/japan-earthquake-tsunami-2011/</guid>
      <description>Japan’s destruction due to the recent earthquake and tsunami is unbelievable. It is more than heartbreaking. Google has setup a page (Google’s Japan Earthquake Crisis Response) with informational links, one of them being one to donate through the Red Cross Japan. Around the clock information from the BBC is also available.
A small donation can go a long way. I have donated, and you can too. Please help by donating (Google’s Japan Earthquake Crisis Response) today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Augustine</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/03/12/st-augustine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/03/12/st-augustine/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I went with Kent and classmates to St. Augustine, the oldest continuously occupied European established city and port in the continental United States.
It was a great trip, we learned a lot, we saw a lot, it was cold, we came home tired. We will return&amp;hellip; one day. The end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday, Viejo!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/02/27/happy-birthday-viejo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/02/27/happy-birthday-viejo/</guid>
      <description>Not a day goes by without me thinking of my Dad. Today he would have being 92 years old.
I still remember him on his 90th birthday, doing push ups using only three fingers on each hand. I will forever remember the endless stories he used to tell, and his constant smile. He was the best father a son can ask for, an example for many. It hurts so very much not to have him around anymore&amp;hellip;!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insignificant</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/27/insignificant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/27/insignificant/</guid>
      <description>Do you see the pale dot on the dark image above? You don&amp;rsquo;t see it? Look carefully, it is there! That pale dot could be us, Earth; but you pick: Solar System, Milky Way, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. We are that insignificant because of the vastness of the universe we live in. And vastness is an understatement. After all, the universe is infinite.
We might try to explain what is at our noses, but that &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rdquo; will always be too insignificant to mean anything more than what is immediate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Brotherhood</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/12/the-brotherhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/12/the-brotherhood/</guid>
      <description>Recently I got the PS3 game &amp;ldquo;Assassin Creed Brotherhood&amp;rdquo; for my birthday and it has being very fun. My dad got me the Harlequin code, and playing him is very fun as well. I have already gotten the armor of Brutus, the very best on the game. Needless is to say, I already finished the game, but am still &amp;ldquo;renovating&amp;rdquo; things.
&amp;mdash; Kent</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mi viejo</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/11/26/mi-viejo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/11/26/mi-viejo/</guid>
      <description>A steady, yet gentle, rain was falling over Miami on the night of November 24th, 2010. Some say rain are tears from the sky. I was crying as well. On November 24th my father died.
Those who have lost an infinitely dear one will understand how I feel. Not only did I lose the best father a son could have, I lost a lifetime friend, a restless protector, a confidant. The many memories that I have of him continue to bring tears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva Spain!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/07/11/viva-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/07/11/viva-spain/</guid>
      <description>Woohoo! Spain, Champions of Europe and now Champions of the World! What an amazing match! So excited! Now I can&amp;rsquo;t hardly wait until the next World Cup! :-) Viva Espa&amp;ntilde;a! Viva Espa&amp;ntilde;a!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Unthinkable</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/06/25/the-unthinkable/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/06/25/the-unthinkable/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I did the unthinkable. Something I have never done &amp;mdash; nor will I do again &amp;mdash; before. I went very early (03:15) to stand at the Millenia all, to be one of the first (or so I thought) to buy the iPhone 4.
I don&amp;rsquo;t want to write long about something I am more than half way ashamed of. Suffice it to say that I got an iPhone 4 after standing in line for 14 hours (17:15).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A month</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/06/23/a-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/06/23/a-month/</guid>
      <description>It has been a month since our Jean passed away. Times flies, yet it seems like it was yesterday. Nor a day has passed by without coming to mind, one way or another. We miss her like we did the first day. I truly dislike Warcraft, but I am keeping her toons alive, and advancing. Somehow playing something she dedicated so much time on, where she had so many good friends, gives me the feeling she still lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kent on Principal&#39;s List</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/06/04/kent-principals-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2010 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/06/04/kent-principals-list/</guid>
      <description>Kent&amp;rsquo;s school Awards Ceremony was today. I did not take a picture there, but filmed a bit. The photo above was taken afterwards, at home. He was so happy &amp;ndash;and I so proud of him!&amp;ndash; to receive the trophy for being the whole third academic year on the Principal&amp;rsquo;s List (straight A in all subjects).
I am lucky I got him to smile too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R.I.P. Dixie J. McCoy</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/06/01/dixie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/06/01/dixie/</guid>
      <description>Our Dixie died in her sleep, on May 23rd, 2010. Her death brought sorrow, and she is greatly missed each day. We will never forget her sweetness, kindness, good advise&amp;hellip; Her gentle smile will live in our memories.
Rest in peace Maxie Bizzenscooter, Astlyr, Thorir, kitty, Dixie Jean McCoy. We loved you, we miss you, we will remember you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 11th</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/09/11/september-11th/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/09/11/september-11th/</guid>
      <description>We will never forget.
Today, eight years ago, a group of humans, guided by a political agenda, a deep hatred towards the United States, and a mad religious fanaticism slammed airplanes into the World Trade Center, destroying the Twin Towers, damaging other buildings, and killing almost 3,000 people. A second airplane hit The Pentagon, and a third crashed near Pennsylvania after some of its passengers and flight crew attempted to retake control of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We remember: Six years ago</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/09/11/we-remember-six-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/09/11/we-remember-six-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>Today, six years ago, a group of animals belonging to the human race decided to take away thousands of innocent lives by destroying the Twin Towers (see World Trade Center). Let us not to forget how stupid they were, how criminal they were, how inhuman they were. Let us remember our brothers and sisters who died that day. For me The Towers stand tall. They always will.
September 11th, 2001: We will never forget!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canon PowerShot A640</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/12/canon-powershot-a640/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/12/canon-powershot-a640/</guid>
      <description>Recently we decided to replace our old Sony little camera, since quite a few photos are going to be taken in the near future, and the poor Cyber-Shot we had really wasn&amp;rsquo;t up to the task. With an under $400 budget, I picked the Canon PowerShot A640, and the picture below is the first one I took, on total automatic mode.
More will come in the near future, as we will have our first real vacation in six years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembrance</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/09/11/remembrance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/09/11/remembrance/</guid>
      <description>Today, three years ago, a group of animals belonging to the human race decided to take away thousands of innocent lives by destroying the Twin Towers (see World TradeCenter). Let us not to forget how stupid they were, how criminal they were, how non human they were. Let us remember our brothers and sisters who died that day. For me The Towers stand tall. They always will.
September 11th, 2001: We will never forget!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shredder and Eggroll</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/18/shredder-and-eggroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/18/shredder-and-eggroll/</guid>
      <description>Kent assumes the personality of a different cartoon character &amp;mdash; or hero &amp;mdash; every day. He seems to shuffle between Ninja Turtles, Batman, Danny Phantom, Robin (from &amp;ldquo;Teen Titans&amp;rdquo;), Jackie Chang and others. He has even been Spongebob Squarepants! Needless is to say we &amp;mdash; Kim and I &amp;mdash; are always the bad guys.
Today he decided he was a Ninja Turtle (purple and blue at times) and that Kim and I were Shredders (of different colours, of course).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sun and salty water</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/04/11/sun-and-salty-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/04/11/sun-and-salty-water/</guid>
      <description>After almost a year, we returned to the beach yesterday. Jetty Park, by Port Cañaveral is around 45 miles from where we live, but still closer than Daytona. It is quite a nice park, with a decently clean beach. For those of you living constantly under the cold weather, sun and salty water is as good as it gets, right? :-)
Almost a year ago we took KM to Cocoa beach and at the time he was afraid to even touch the water.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>