<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gates on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/gates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gates on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/gates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets us make sure</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/28/lets-make-sure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/28/lets-make-sure/</guid>
      <description>Comes v. Microsoft &amp;ndash; Plaintiff&amp;rsquo;s Exhibit 2991 &amp;ndash; (PDF)
  From: Bill Gates Sent: Saturday, December 05, 1998 9:44 AM To: Bob Muglia; Jon DeVaan; Steven Sinofsky Cc: Paul Maritz Subject: Office rendering  One thing we have got to change in our strategy - allowing Office documents to be rendered very well by other peoples browsers is one of the most destructive things we could do to the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programmers != Antisocials</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/14/programmers-antisocials/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/14/programmers-antisocials/</guid>
      <description>BBC NEWS: Business: Bill Gates: The skills you need to succeed
 A lot of people assume that creating software is purely a solitary activity where you sit in an office with the door closed all day and write lots of code.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t true at all.
Software innovation, like almost every other kind of innovation, requires the ability to collaborate and share ideas with other people, and to sit down and talk with customers and get their feedback and understand their needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Bill Gates, with love</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/01/24/from-bill-gates-with-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/01/24/from-bill-gates-with-love/</guid>
      <description>I received an email today. While it is true that I receive 60 to 70 emails daily, this one was not trivial. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t the expected porno offer, nor a letter from Nigeria or Lagos promising riches. Is wasn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;reputable&amp;rdquo; diplomas or innocent spam passed along by a lack-of-knowledge friend neither. If was an email from Bill Gates itself. Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s right, an email from the billionaire Gates.
I have to admit that my first thought was, &amp;ldquo;It is another spam&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>