<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rants on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/rants/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rants on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 11:53:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/rants/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Uber Affair</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/06/06/the-uber-affair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 11:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/06/06/the-uber-affair/</guid>
      <description>Using Uber for the first time, in France, was a delightful experience. We were able to summon a relatively cheap minivan within minutes, the drivers were nice, nothing found to complain. Then, once back home, I decided that I might want to occasionally drive for Uber, for fun. That is when the real affair started.
To begin with, the rider photo I had on my profile no longer met their requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake Email Clients</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/11/fake-email-clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 21:06:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/11/fake-email-clients/</guid>
      <description>For a few (years?) now, there has been an increase of so called email clients that are not so. I am talking about the &amp;ldquo;value added email clients&amp;rdquo; that require a third party server/service to work. Within that category there is Nylas, Polymail, and Sparkmail, to mention a few. Although they bring an array of features not normally found on an email client, they are worthless if the third party company server(s) goes down, or have problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Cloud Drive Feedback</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/11/12/amazon-cloud-drive-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/11/12/amazon-cloud-drive-feedback/</guid>
      <description>This is not merely a technical problem, but I did not have the choice for multiple selections. Anytime I use the word &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; down below, I mean Amazon.
First the good. I love you, I have used AWS S3 for a long time, no complains. I do much of my online purchases on you, although I am not a fervent shopper. I rent my movies on Amazon Video. I am signed up for Flex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumping Dollars Left and Right</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/11/02/dumping-dollars-left-and-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/11/02/dumping-dollars-left-and-right/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;DOD charged the American taxpayer $43 million for what is likely the world&amp;rsquo;s most expensive gas station.&amp;rdquo;
That&amp;rsquo;s what Special Inspector General John F. Sopko found when he looked at the construction of a natural gas station in Sheberghan, Afghanistan.
According to the report, at most that station should have cost about $500,000. But in this case, the Department of Defense&amp;rsquo;s Task Force for Stability and Business Operations awarded Central Asian Engineering a contract to build the station for a little under $3 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard and Daylight Savings Time</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/11/01/standard-and-daylight-savings-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/11/01/standard-and-daylight-savings-time/</guid>
      <description>Standard Time. When I was a child, an old lady I loved as my own grandmother used to tell me this time was &amp;ldquo;God&amp;rsquo;s time,&amp;rdquo; and that she never changed clocks when everyone else switched to &amp;ldquo;Daylight Savings Time.&amp;rdquo; I wish I could do the same, unfortunately I am not old enough not to care.
I am part of the growing group that believes DST (or time changing of any kind) is worthless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Red Bus</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/22/big-red-bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/22/big-red-bus/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Hi guys, don&amp;rsquo;t forget to donate today!&amp;rdquo; says the lady with the oneblood.org t-shirt. The Big Red Bus parks on campus often, sometimes they seem to be here every day. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ll give you a t-shirt and a cookie!&amp;rdquo; She says. That&amp;rsquo;s the price of your donation, but is it?
A typical pint of blood costs $130-150, and sometimes even more. A lucrative business, don&amp;rsquo;t you agree? Yet, oneblood.org is non-profit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking and using the Phone</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/21/walking-and-using-the-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/21/walking-and-using-the-phone/</guid>
      <description>Walking around with your head stuck on the phone is like playing the chicken game. The fully aware pedestrian walking in your opposite direction&amp;mdash;and on the same path&amp;mdash;is forced to play the game. Not as dangerous as driving but still very annoying. When you walk, please pay attention, look where you are walking, and leave the phone in your pocket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disappointing</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/30/disappointing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/30/disappointing/</guid>
      <description>Pope Francis &amp;ldquo;thanked her for her courage&amp;rdquo; and told her to &amp;ldquo;stay strong&amp;rdquo;, Mr. Stavers said.
&amp;mdash; BBC News
 If this truly happened, it is disappointing. A person as charismatic as Pope Francis, who has been so politically careful, should have known better. She is a government employee, fulfilling an official task. She must abide the law, or simply leave her job, if she can&amp;rsquo;t perform as expected. What would we do if our troops, due to their religious beliefs, decide to put down their weapons?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Loathe Emoji</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/18/i-loathe-emoji/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/18/i-loathe-emoji/</guid>
      <description>I despise Emoji and emoticons, specially graphical emoji, or people who continuously abuse them, and interject them in every single sentence they type, sometimes even more than once. I thought that I hated &amp;ldquo;LOL,&amp;rdquo; which I do, but I would rather see LOL &amp;mdash; when justified, not the moronic &amp;ldquo;LOL&amp;rdquo; without reason you see often &amp;mdash; than see the utter idiotic smiles, winks, etc., continuously, all the time. &amp;ldquo;I am an elitist asshole, but here, have an Emoji!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding little to talk about</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/03/30/little-to-talk-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/03/30/little-to-talk-about/</guid>
      <description>The main problem with Jekyll is that is out of the way. Unlike other weblog engines, which are managed via the web, I come to the shell to type and process this. Perhaps I need to research a better workflow?
 I am finding little to talk about lately, and that is keeping things here rather quiet. It is not only that I do not have much to write, but that when the desire arrives it gets lost in translation, mostly because of the way I have decided to handle this little space of mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four-Way Stop</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/02/19/four-way-stop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/02/19/four-way-stop/</guid>
      <description>Drivers in Orlando do not seem to know what to do when they reach a four way stop. It really makes me wonder how were they able to obtain a drivers license without that knowledge, as it is part of Drivers Handbook (search for &amp;ldquo;Stop Signs&amp;rdquo; on that page), the test, and occasionally encountered while driving.
For the record, and in case you live in Orlando, and do not know what to do on a four-way stop (also known as all-way stop), these are the basics:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint crookery</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2012/11/19/sprint-crookery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2012/11/19/sprint-crookery/</guid>
      <description>I am not happy with Sprint, I think it is a bad company. That, of course, is my opinion.
I left them and took the hit of the early termination fee (ETF) because their service in my area was, and is, not usable. Even though I had documented the many times I called for not having reception, not able to make calls, and their “unlimited” data plan been unusable, I paid the ETF and decided to move on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insignificant</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/27/insignificant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/27/insignificant/</guid>
      <description>Do you see the pale dot on the dark image above? You don&amp;rsquo;t see it? Look carefully, it is there! That pale dot could be us, Earth; but you pick: Solar System, Milky Way, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. We are that insignificant because of the vastness of the universe we live in. And vastness is an understatement. After all, the universe is infinite.
We might try to explain what is at our noses, but that &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rdquo; will always be too insignificant to mean anything more than what is immediate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bright House saga</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/05/02/bright-house-saga/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/05/02/bright-house-saga/</guid>
      <description>In two occasions I have written about Bright House service, or the lack of. Ever since my last entry, many issues aroused, but I never came here to document them.
What where those issues? They vary, and cover a wide range. So many Bright House technicians has passed by my house, I lost count. The proverbial &amp;ldquo;how many technicians do Bright House needs&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; comes to mind. Issues:
 Black out screens, with &amp;ldquo;Please wait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t talk to aliens</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/28/dont-talk-to-aliens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/28/dont-talk-to-aliens/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;We only have to look at ourselves to see how intelligent life might develop into something we wouldn’t want to meet. I imagine they might exist in massive ships, having used up all the resources from their home planet. Such advanced aliens would perhaps become nomads, looking to conquer and colonise whatever planets they can reach.&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;If aliens ever visit us, I think the outcome would be much as when Christopher Columbus first landed in America, which didn’t turn out very well for the Native Americans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The wheels of justice</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/26/the-wheels-of-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/26/the-wheels-of-justice/</guid>
      <description>I thought twice before coming here and write two or three sentences. But sometimes two or three sentences is all you have. I had to do it: Apple Inc., you rock!
If you want to be a &amp;ldquo;journalist&amp;rdquo;, act as one. As Powazek wrote in a tweet, &amp;ldquo;Real journalists don&amp;rsquo;t buy stolen property.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bright House Follow Up</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/10/09/bright-house-follow-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/10/09/bright-house-follow-up/</guid>
      <description>You will remember my previous Bright House post. The same day I wrote that, I got a call from a Bright House customer service representative. Since there is no need to know names, let&amp;rsquo;s call her Christine. I like that name.
Christine told me Bright House was aware I had publicly written about my displeasure with their services, and that her job was to make sure I was completely satisfied. Fair enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avoid Bright House if You Can</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/10/05/avoid-brighthouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/10/05/avoid-brighthouse/</guid>
      <description>I live in Central Florida. In my area, if I want cable TV and Internet, I have no choice but to use Bright House services. The competition is satellite TV/Internet and/or DSL (for Internet). Why am I recommending to avoid Bright House, if you can? It is simple: their service is far from being of a good quality and/or reliable. I will elaborate a little.
On cable TV, you get black screens (no video or audio), or &amp;ldquo;Please wait&amp;rdquo; screens, constantly and randomly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email liturgy</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/01/07/email-liturgy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/01/07/email-liturgy/</guid>
      <description>I miss the days when emails were written with thought, and care. They were clear, and to the point. There was no HTML in them; replies were perfectly quoted, references were neatly annotated. Emoticons were kept to a minimum, if any.
No one does that anymore&amp;hellip; well, not many of us do. I haven&amp;rsquo;t give up, I insist. For me, sending and replying emails is a liturgy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yet another</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/11/12/yet-another/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/11/12/yet-another/</guid>
      <description>Yet another long downtime on World of Warcraft, just in the verge of the release of the second major expansion for the game. What a royal mess! You would think Blizzard has it figured out by now, down to a science, but&amp;hellip;
I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine how tomorrow, with the expansion release, will be. Not going to &amp;ldquo;tune in.&amp;rdquo; Instead will let others have the &amp;ldquo;fun.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not allowed to tell</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/10/10/not-allowed-to-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/10/10/not-allowed-to-tell/</guid>
      <description>A local bank in front of which I sit quite often has a locked metal box sitting outside the branch. Yesterday my curiosity got sparked when I saw one of the employees (which I greet daily) opening it and taking a canvas bag out of it. When I asked what was the box for, she stopped like frozen, and muttered &amp;ldquo;Company doesn&amp;rsquo;t allow me to tell.&amp;ldquo;
Now, won&amp;rsquo;t you agree with me that such answer was a very silly &amp;mdash;and dangerous!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prepare to pay more</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/30/prepare-to-pay-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/30/prepare-to-pay-more/</guid>
      <description>It seems that within four years &amp;ndash;if nothing is done to prevent it (and nobody really knows what to do)&amp;ndash; we [americans] will be paying $7 for a gallon of gasoline.
A very interesting post over Wired explains some of the reasons. A brief summary of them:
 Oil companies getting tax breaks, and not passing those savings down, but pocketing them. The economic development in China and India, which increases the demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primary elections</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/13/primary-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/13/primary-elections/</guid>
      <description>It is my desire that the U.S. primary elections were available to everyone, to vote for anyone, regardless of the political part affiliation 1. In fact, I would not make a requirement to affiliate to a specific party at all.
Why? If I am registered, for example, democrat, but I see that the choices of the Democratic Party are not &amp;ldquo;presidential&amp;rdquo; material, then I would like to be able to vote (even at the primaries) for the best of the other party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft is a crying baby</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/16/microsoft-is-a-crying-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/16/microsoft-is-a-crying-baby/</guid>
      <description>What does Microsoft do when they don&amp;rsquo;t get it their way? They cry like babies, they snitch and they try to use their mu$cle to get things their way.
 Microsoft Urges Review of Google-DoubleClick Deal &amp;ndash; Microsoft, a veteran defendant of epic antitrust battles in the United States and Europe, is urging regulators to consider scuttling Google&amp;rsquo;s plan to buy DoubleClick, an online advertising company.
Microsoft contends that the $3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thought of the day</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/09/thought-of-the-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/09/thought-of-the-day/</guid>
      <description>If your weblog or site &amp;ndash;in general&amp;ndash; advertising is slowing down the load of pages to an almost complete halt, it is time to re-think and take a different marketing approach. Your writings and your advertising are been missing. You may as well cancel your hosting and print what you want to say, along with the advertisings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoDaddy and MediaTemple</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/07/godaddy-and-mediatemple/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/07/godaddy-and-mediatemple/</guid>
      <description>Not long ago I was looking for a new collocation provider. I was with ServerBeach, as I am right now, but the friend I was teaming up with to share the expenses wanted to move from Linux to a Windows server, and I have nothing to do with one &amp;ndash;Windows server, that is. Since I couldn&amp;rsquo;t afford to pay the fees on my own, I was off to find a new provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is there any difference?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/03/21/is-there-any-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/03/21/is-there-any-difference/</guid>
      <description>Is has always amazed me how people or groups of people self segregate, while voicing their concerns about discrimination and inequality.
Some websites have come across lately that really puzzle me. To show a couple, Black Engineer and The Black Collegian. Why? It doesn&amp;rsquo;t make any sense to me. Are engineers different because of their ethnic background, or because of their field of knowledge? Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t all Colleges teach the same, regardless of the ethnicity of their students?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Katrina crime increase</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/01/08/post-katrina-crime-increase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/01/08/post-katrina-crime-increase/</guid>
      <description>Ever since after Katrina we have seeing crime increase to levels never saw before in Orlando. Crime has been so high, that it has placed our city on the top most 25 dangerous cities in the States. Orlando, City Beautiful, rated higher than Miami on crime. Every single day more than 4-5 people die victim of a violent crime. Others get injured. It seems other cities/states are experiencing similar problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electoral signs: my approach</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/11/06/electoral-signs-my-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/11/06/electoral-signs-my-approach/</guid>
      <description>On every single election &amp;ldquo;season&amp;rdquo; I can see a multitude of signs and advertising that often remains until &amp;ldquo;natural decay&amp;rdquo; or the city gets them removed, 6 months &amp;ndash;or more&amp;ndash; after the elections are over. That really makes me mad. I would make it part of the process of being elected: if you win, you cannot take over office until you clean up all your garbage. And if they don&amp;rsquo;t, a hefty fine gets applied, they get ridiculed and their seat is up for claiming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three years ago</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/10/18/three-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/10/18/three-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>In light of everything happening in Asia, specifically on the Korean peninsula, I remembered what I wrote three years ago, more or less. It took them three years to develop something that can be tested (a bomb), or were they working already on it for a long time and our intelligence was &amp;lsquo;asleep&amp;rsquo;? If it was the first, they could already have a way to deliver it overseas, and if it is the second, we may not even know it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too busy, too much money or...</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/10/18/too-busy-too-much-money-or-just-uneducated/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/10/18/too-busy-too-much-money-or-just-uneducated/</guid>
      <description>Our College is trying to re-design. Our web manager has been assigned to some other project of more importance (Dean&amp;rsquo;s order), so he can&amp;rsquo;t tackle the conversion of the existing website to a full blown CMS driven one. Other than the locals we have seeing and sit through presentations and proposals, I sent emails &amp;ndash;very brief ones, but to the point&amp;ndash; to Dan Cederholm, Dan Bejamin (we live in the same town), and David Shea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do not phone and drive</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/05/16/do-not-phone-and-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/05/16/do-not-phone-and-drive/</guid>
      <description>It infuriates me the idiots who think (and insist) that driving a car while talking on their mobile phones represents no problem for them or those around. Well, it does, fools! I have done it, I confess &amp;ndash;although I have stopped doing so for a while, unless it is a real emergency&amp;ndash; and I know what I am talking about. A driver handling a phone conversation while driving is impaired. It is!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musical batons and other memes</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/01/musical-batons-and-other-memes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/01/musical-batons-and-other-memes/</guid>
      <description>I hate the &amp;ldquo;Musical Baton&amp;rdquo; and any other type of Memes (Friday&amp;rsquo;s craps, &amp;ldquo;This or That&amp;rdquo; imbecile lists, etc). Just do a quick search at Google and you will know what I am talking about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PGP Corporation Decadence</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/05/28/pgp-corporation-decadence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/05/28/pgp-corporation-decadence/</guid>
      <description>Recently PGP Corporation released their latest version of the PGP software created by Phil Zimmerman and made famous by millions of users around the world (me included). I wish I could say such latest release is great, but I can&amp;rsquo;t.
The new PGP Desktop 9.0 (or 9.0.1 beta as of this writting) come with a few new &amp;ldquo;features&amp;rdquo; and lacks of a few others that any old school PGP user might notice right away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shameful website</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/05/28/shameful-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/05/28/shameful-website/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever tried going to the U.S. website for Kenwood? Kenwood, you know, that audio equipment, transceivers maker, etc? Go look! They ought to be ashamed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Privacy at stake</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/03/31/your-privacy-at-stake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/03/31/your-privacy-at-stake/</guid>
      <description>Something very infortunated has happened and I want to encourage you, and the people you know, to help amend this by signing the petition and emailing your elected officials as soon as possible.
The NTIA, which is the telecommunications and Internet arm of the Department of Commerce, has disallowed private registrations for .US domain names. This unfortunate decision was made by the NTIA, without a hearing or an opportunity for a response by those affected &amp;ndash; in fact; there was no due process of any kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex is everything</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/01/12/sex-is-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/01/12/sex-is-everything/</guid>
      <description>For spammers &amp;ndash;and others&amp;ndash;, that is. Other than the trackback attack that a good group of people including me received recently, sex related spam seems to have doubled as the year increased by one. And all comes down to this: human beings are a bunch of sex driven machines. Take it or leave it. We all like it, enjoy it and are driven to it in a multifaceted spectrum. It goes beyond the Mother Nature purpose of procreation (continuity).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am a virus, open me!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/08/09/i-am-a-virus-open-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/08/09/i-am-a-virus-open-me/</guid>
      <description>The history repeats itself. No matter how many viruses get to their inboxes, no matter how many times you tell them not to open those attachments, when all logic and common sense are just yelling &amp;ldquo;delete!&amp;rdquo;, they will open it.
Virus and trojan makers/scripters will always succeed. Antivirus companies will always be behind (even for a few hours/minutes) and make tons of money. As long as my type of user exists there will be a future of revenues on that field and a headache for the rest of us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The worse Web Browser</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/14/the-worse-web-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/14/the-worse-web-browser/</guid>
      <description>Not too long ago I was an Internet Explorer fan. The pages I went to looked fine under it, the experience seemed rich. There were no complains. Then I started fiddling with CSS and moving away from tables. I experienced the advantages of the PNG format and I loved it. I experienced functionability I never saw before. I got tired of hearing about major problems and running security updates. I got my eyes opened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screw SPEWS</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/06/20/screw-spews/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/06/20/screw-spews/</guid>
      <description>Note: I still have Gmail invitations. A lot. Ask and you shall receive.
Recently I found out that my existing server IP &amp;ndash;the server I am moving away from&amp;ndash; is banned on SPEWS (I am not linking them, Google it and you shall know), because it is assigned to UUnet, which is blamed of harboring spammers. Following the recommendation of the bounced email I posted on Usenet, asking to be removed, without knowing at that time that it was something out of my hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why do they even bother?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/03/19/why-do-they-even-bother/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/03/19/why-do-they-even-bother/</guid>
      <description>State institutions have a different way of doing things. Different from Corporate America, that is. For example let&amp;rsquo;s say, hypothetically, that a position opens on certain department on a state institution. A person already working for the department, a person which everyone is happy with about the job being done &amp;ndash; by the person, that is &amp;ndash; applies for the position. Odds of that person getting the job are very high, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobility 20-20</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/10/07/mobility-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/10/07/mobility-2020/</guid>
      <description>If you do not live in Orlando you will not know what I am talking about here. Today was also voting day here, in Orlando, FL, but for a different reason than the Californians. Let me explain.
As you may or may not know every city has its budget. I bet that even every county has its own as well. Talking about a city budget, some people, perhaps even a bunch of people, get paid big money to come up with the numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The lack of evidence</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/06/06/the-lack-of-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/06/06/the-lack-of-evidence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am proudly a republican. I did not vote on the last presidential election for a technicality: I moved from one county to another a week before elections and I lost my right to vote, just because of bad timing. But I would have voted for Mr. Bush.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also supported the war against Saddam Hussein and his army, because I think the world is better off without a man like him on power. I did not care whether or not he had &amp;ldquo;weapons of mass destruction&amp;rdquo;, I knew the guy history and that was enough justification for me. But, if I remember well, the war was sold, &lt;b&gt;mainly&lt;/b&gt;, on the existence of WMD, whilst it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t. We had thousands of other reasons to go to war against that mad man. Why WMD were made the &amp;ldquo;key&amp;rdquo; reason I do not know. And now we have a problem in our hands.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>