<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>david on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/david/</link>
    <description>Recent content in david on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 11:04:35 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/david/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning the plate</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/12/cleaning-the-plate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 11:04:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/12/cleaning-the-plate/</guid>
      <description>My wife has always told me, &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t eat everything in your plate, leave something!&amp;rdquo; It is her believe, and her culture&amp;rsquo;s, that only poor people eats everything, and that if I do so, it will show I am dying of hunger, and thus, poor. If it were so, what&amp;rsquo;s wrong with being poor? Why will I leave food on the plate, food that I really like, to pretend what I am not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small catching up</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/08/07/small-catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/08/07/small-catching-up/</guid>
      <description>Last week was a busy week. The Exchange serverwent into 3/4 full production and, yes, it crashed. For the first time I had to recover the PRIV and PUB databases and the server wasn&amp;rsquo;t been on production not even a week! Oh boy&amp;hellip;
I got the Lingogateway (VoIP gateway, that is) and the quality is excellent, while reaching their technical support is close to impossible. When I finally got a techie I told him I was starting to think Lingotechnical support was a myth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The three of us</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/05/the-three-of-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/05/the-three-of-us/</guid>
      <description>For one reason or another, we have very few pictures on which the three of us are present. Even today, went I tried to snap one I failed. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, photos we have, but none of them pleases us &amp;ndash;Kim&amp;ndash; to put online for the viewing audience (the very small one we have here).
A couple of days ago I took one photo that I decided to put online, because I like they way KM eyes look and because it represents the priority level in our family: kid goes first, then us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One year older</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/08/06/one-year-older/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/08/06/one-year-older/</guid>
      <description>Well, I thought it will never come. We &amp;mdash; adults &amp;mdash;, sometimes pursuing our dreams of Peterpan&amp;hellip; we think we&amp;rsquo;ll never age. Slowly our skin becomes saggy and wrinkled; we can not see as sharp as before, hence we wear glasses; our hair turn white (for the lucky ones) and falls down (for those unlucky, like me). The rhythm of live goes at a different beat then. You start getting tired easily, things that previously attracted you do not longer do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>