<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lingo on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/lingo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lingo on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2005 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/lingo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>More on VoIP</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/01/06/more-on-voip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/01/06/more-on-voip/</guid>
      <description>Last year I wrote about Lingo and recommended their VoIP service. While I was not that off on that &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;, I have changed my mind long ago and decided not to keep the service. I got a lot of emails from people wanting to try and/or get the service and they used my email for referral. As a result, I got a lot of free Lingo service, but I called them at the end of December to cancel for good (something they told me they did, but I still have the service, I am not sure why.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More on Lingo</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/08/21/more-on-lingo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/08/21/more-on-lingo/</guid>
      <description>A while ago I wrote about my plans of dropping BellSouth for a VoIP provider called Lingo. At that time I also wrote that I would come back and write a review about it. Well, this is not a real review &amp;ndash;I really do not know how to write one&amp;ndash; but it contains my experiences with Lingo voice over IP (VoIP) service, so far.
When something works fine there is very little to tell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropping BellSouth</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/31/dropping-bellsouth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/31/dropping-bellsouth/</guid>
      <description>Our VoIP gateway shipped yesterday and it should reach us around August 3rd (Tuesday). We are going to try Voice over IP technology and service, from Lingo. The reason why? Save money. Lingo VoIP service is $20 for unlimited long distance for US, Canada and Western Europe. Very &amp;ndash;very&amp;ndash; competitive fees to the rest of the world. And you get all the other goodies (caller ID, call waiting, return call, *69, voicemail, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>