<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>trump on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/trump/</link>
    <description>Recent content in trump on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 21:19:21 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/trump/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Meltdown</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/another-meltdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 21:19:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/another-meltdown/</guid>
      <description>Someone is having another meltdown.
 The Mueller probe should never have been started in that there was no collusion and there was no crime. It was based on fraudulent activities and a Fake Dossier paid for by Crooked Hillary and the DNC, and improperly used in FISA COURT for surveillance of my campaign. WITCH HUNT!
 😂
Now, there is a background for his latest fit.
Yesterday, 16 March, Jeff Sessions fired Andrew McCabe, the FBI deputy director.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Goes After Trump Org</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/15/mueller-goes-after-trump-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 19:50:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/15/mueller-goes-after-trump-org/</guid>
      <description>I have disliked other presidents in the past, for actions taken while they were in the office that I — and many others — considered stupid, crazy, or just plain wrong. My dislike for the current president eclipses any of my previous. I voted for Hillary, and wrongly predicted that she would win the presidency.
Today news, although perhaps inconsequential, brings joy to an otherwise political nightmare.
 The special counsel, Robert S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A downright moron</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/10/05/a-downright-moron/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 05:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/10/05/a-downright-moron/</guid>
      <description>Henry Louis Mencken wrote an article on the Baltimore Sun, on 26 July, 1920, that amongst other things read:
 As democracy is perfected, the office represents, more and more closely, the inner soul of the people. We move toward a lofty ideal. On some great and glorious day the plain folks of the land will reach their heart&amp;rsquo;s desire at last, and the White House will be adorned by a downright moron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comey Sacking</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/05/11/comey-sacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 16:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/05/11/comey-sacking/</guid>
      <description>This is, at least for me, completely surreal. It is not only that Trump sacked the FBI director &amp;mdash; who arguably helped him getting elected President &amp;mdash; while he was conducting an investigation on Trump&amp;rsquo;s presidential campaign, but the way he wrote the sacking letter (I emphasised):
 Dear Director Comey:
I have received the attached letters from the Attorney General and Deputy Attorney General of the United States recommending your dismissal as the Director of the Federal Bureau of Investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Intelligent Person</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/27/an-intelligent-person/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 19:59:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/27/an-intelligent-person/</guid>
      <description>From Twitter:
 The most amazing thing about the Trump presidency is that it’s made GWB look like a reasonably intelligent person.
&amp;mdash; Derek Powazek (@fraying) February 27, 2017
 And from The New York Times:
 Former President George W. Bush said Monday &amp;ldquo;we all need answers&amp;rdquo; on the extent of contact between President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s team and the Russian government, and didn&amp;rsquo;t rule out the idea that a special prosecutor could be necessary to lead an investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Silence of the Hacks</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/18/the-silence-of-the-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 21:32:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/18/the-silence-of-the-hacks/</guid>
      <description>There is a reason why I subscribed to the digital edition of The New York Times. Its journalists are superb; it is a paper I trust, and have found to be veridical after cross referencing the news they post with other major, equally trusted, news sources.
From yesterday&amp;rsquo;s edition (some emphasis mine):
 The story so far: A foreign dictator intervened on behalf of a U.S. presidential candidate — and that candidate won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incapable of Serving</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/14/incapable-of-serving/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 05:49:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/14/incapable-of-serving/</guid>
      <description>From the opinion pages of The New York Times yesterday, 13 of February, 2017, also appearing in print today. Some emphasis mine.
 Mr. Trump’s speech and actions demonstrate an inability to tolerate views different from his own, leading to rage reactions. His words and behavior suggest a profound inability to empathize. Individuals with these traits distort reality to suit their psychological state, attacking facts and those who convey them (journalists, scientists).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard to Believe</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/09/hard-to-believe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 14:30:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/09/hard-to-believe/</guid>
      <description>If you hear or read this somewhere else &amp;mdash; whether on social media, or via your clueless uncle Olaf &amp;mdash; you will find it hard, if not impossible, to believe. Now, finding it on Reuters is a different story.
 In his first call as president with Russian leader Vladimir Putin, Donald Trump denounced a treaty that caps U.S. and Russian deployment of nuclear warheads as a bad deal for the United States, according to two U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unpresidential</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/01/12/unpresidential/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 20:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/01/12/unpresidential/</guid>
      <description>Not presidential at all.
 “President-elect Donald J. Trump’s aides often cite his appearances at professional wrestling matches as an inspiration for his outsize political speaking style, and his buoyantly belligerent news conference in New York on Wednesday proved he has no plans to betray his brawler’s roots in the service of seeming more presidential.”
&amp;mdash; New York Times
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I was wrong</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/11/09/i-was-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/11/09/i-was-wrong/</guid>
      <description>Back in October 5th, 2015, I wrote a prediction, which I saved in a file for which I posted a hash. I predicted that Hillary Clinton would win the United States presidential elections. Sadly, I was wrong.
I really do not have much else to say. I am sorry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/prediction/</guid>
      <description>Next year we will have our Presidential Elections. Everyone knows that, of course, because the politicians have been campaining for almost a year now.
Below is the name of a file with my winner&amp;rsquo;s prediction on the United States 2016 Presidential Elections written on it. It is a hash algorithm of a file containing a sentence with my prediction. I will refer to this post the day after elections, as the results are known.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presidential Elections 2016</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/27/presidential-elections-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/27/presidential-elections-2016/</guid>
      <description>Back in 2011 was the last time I wrote about Presidential Elections (2012). I can&amp;rsquo;t believe we are about to get into them again. In 2012 I knew exactly who to vote for, but in 2016, with the selection we have thus far, I really have no idea about who is the most viable&amp;mdash;if there is one. Certainly not this one:
 Question: &amp;ldquo;How will you bring back the American Dream?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>