<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>economy on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/categories/economy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in economy on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/categories/economy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan Earthquake and Tsunami</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/03/14/japan-earthquake-tsunami-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/03/14/japan-earthquake-tsunami-2011/</guid>
      <description>Japan’s destruction due to the recent earthquake and tsunami is unbelievable. It is more than heartbreaking. Google has setup a page (Google’s Japan Earthquake Crisis Response) with informational links, one of them being one to donate through the Red Cross Japan. Around the clock information from the BBC is also available.
A small donation can go a long way. I have donated, and you can too. Please help by donating (Google’s Japan Earthquake Crisis Response) today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese products are cheap</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/09/chinese-products-are-cheap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/09/chinese-products-are-cheap/</guid>
      <description>Not anymore.
 The era of cheap Chinese consumer goods may finally be ending, thanks to irrepressible inflation. Now when the Chinese present their lists, some American importers are conceding higher prices, meaning that American shoppers, for the first time in years, are starting to pick up the tab for rising costs in China. Some Chinese factories are now asking their American customers for price increases of as much as 20 percent to 30 percent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Made in China</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/30/made-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/30/made-in-china/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t have a particular problem with China. I admire its very old culture, its people resourcefulness and their resilience, among other things. But when I see everything I buy here in the U.S. made in China, I feel uncomfortable. It tells me something is wrong with the way we are doing business.
It isn&amp;rsquo;t the &amp;ldquo;Made in China&amp;rdquo; the thing that bugs me. It&amp;rsquo;s the everything &amp;ldquo;Made in China&amp;rdquo; that does.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>