<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>russia on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/russia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in russia on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 19:50:42 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/russia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Goes After Trump Org</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/15/mueller-goes-after-trump-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 19:50:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/15/mueller-goes-after-trump-org/</guid>
      <description>I have disliked other presidents in the past, for actions taken while they were in the office that I — and many others — considered stupid, crazy, or just plain wrong. My dislike for the current president eclipses any of my previous. I voted for Hillary, and wrongly predicted that she would win the presidency.
Today news, although perhaps inconsequential, brings joy to an otherwise political nightmare.
 The special counsel, Robert S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard to Believe</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/09/hard-to-believe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 14:30:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/09/hard-to-believe/</guid>
      <description>If you hear or read this somewhere else &amp;mdash; whether on social media, or via your clueless uncle Olaf &amp;mdash; you will find it hard, if not impossible, to believe. Now, finding it on Reuters is a different story.
 In his first call as president with Russian leader Vladimir Putin, Donald Trump denounced a treaty that caps U.S. and Russian deployment of nuclear warheads as a bad deal for the United States, according to two U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russians and Syria</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/08/russians-and-syria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/08/russians-and-syria/</guid>
      <description>We bomb. From the air, from the ground, from afar, from ships. And so do the Russians now. We target what we believe are terrorists, sometimes we miss. Russians are doing the same now.
We removed Saddam, and the Taliban, just to mention two, and that created&amp;mdash;or increased&amp;mdash;a mess that continues until today. The Russian&amp;rsquo;s tactic is different, they are targeting both, the terrorists fighting against the &amp;ldquo;official&amp;rdquo; regime, and those which we are targeting as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia warned over Georgia move</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/30/nato-warns-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/30/nato-warns-russia/</guid>
      <description>Russia warned over Georgia move
 Nato has warned Russia that its recent troop build-up in Georgia&amp;rsquo;s two breakaway regions undermines its neighbour&amp;rsquo;s territorial integrity.
 Would everyone chill out, please? This time Russians, specially. I think a &amp;ldquo;Back off, and chill&amp;rdquo; behavior is mandatory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only in Russia</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/17/only-in-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/17/only-in-russia/</guid>
      <description>Drunk Russian sleeps off knifing &amp;ndash; A Russian man trying to sleep off a night of after-work drinking failed to notice a six inch (15 cm) knife in his back - until his wife woke him up.
Yuri Lyalin, 53, took a bus home, ate breakfast and apparently slept like a baby before his spouse noticed a handle sticking out of his back.
He was rushed to casualty but doctors found no vital organs damaged.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>