<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kent on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/kent/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kent on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 18:38:42 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/kent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Sorry I Was Late</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2019/04/25/i-am-sorry-i-was-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 18:38:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2019/04/25/i-am-sorry-i-was-late/</guid>
      <description>I can explain why I was so late, I swear.
I woke up this morning after a brilliant two hours of sleep and went to milk the cow. She did not really have much, so the cereal kinda blew. Anyways, as I turned on my red 1993 Chevy Malibu I realised the garage was not opening. Great, the power was down! I went upstairs with a broom and woke up the hamster, which must have fallen asleep on the job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching for The Car</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/searching-for-the-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 17:15:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/03/17/searching-for-the-car/</guid>
      <description>A year ago, Kent got his learner&amp;rsquo;s permit. With the help of John, and a little from me, he practiced driving for over 250 hours. A year later — more or less — on 9 March, he got his driver&amp;rsquo;s license, passing the practical test with a 96, out of 100 points, score. And so the asking for a car began.
What car should we get for a 17 year old?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What have you taught me?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/10/29/what-have-you-taught-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/10/29/what-have-you-taught-me/</guid>
      <description>His father was only giving him a small advise, worried for him. Parents worry too much, sometimes. It was not taken well.
“You suffocate me, don’t worry so much about me! Enough advise, what have you taught me, until now?” He asks. Perhaps no much, the father thinks in retrospect. Brushing the teeth, maybe? Lacing the shoes? How to clean the arse? How to respect others, and do good? To be happy, love, study hard, work hard?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Violin Lessons</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/04/29/violin-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/04/29/violin-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Just as they started, randomly, on a whim, as a child desire to learn to play the violin, the lessons that Kent has been taking for almost two years came to an end two weeks ago. It was hard to tell Julie &amp;mdash; his teacher &amp;mdash; that he was not to continue, but it was what he wanted.
Kent never intended to play violin professionally, it was no more than an artistic hobby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Alone</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/12/17/home-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/12/17/home-alone/</guid>
      <description>Just like I did on July 18, 2014, this one is mostly for keeping a record of a first time activity or occasion. This time it was Kent&amp;rsquo;s first home alone day. He is almost 15 years old, and for the first time he spent eight hours home alone, while Kim and I were at work.
Happy &amp;ldquo;graduation&amp;rdquo; step, Kent!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reminders</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/19/reminders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/19/reminders/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;What did you have for lunch?,&amp;rdquo; the father asks while driving home. &amp;ldquo;Same as usual,&amp;rdquo; he replies. &amp;ldquo;And that is?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I just eat random sandwiches of what comes to whim.&amp;rdquo; The father processes that for a bit. &amp;ldquo;I see.&amp;rdquo; Later, at home, &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s there for homework today?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;No much,&amp;rdquo; he says. &amp;ldquo;Brush your teeth,&amp;rdquo; he is reminded. Later, in the evening. &amp;ldquo;Take a shower.&amp;rdquo; A few times.
Just before the father goes to sleep, and sees his bedroom lights on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP Classes</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/16/ap-classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/16/ap-classes/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday (15 October) Kent told me he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to take AP (Advanced Placement) classes next year. He also told me he might not want to be a neurological surgeon after all, and that he really doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what he will want to be, professionally. We talked more, but the rest of it has no place in here.
Amongst the many feelings I am experiencing, regret is one of them. If only my parents were alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On a Rock</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/01/on-a-rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/01/on-a-rock/</guid>
      <description>From our last vacation&amp;mdash;which occurred four months ago&amp;mdash;to Colorado. This one was taken somewhere around Pikes Peak. Kent was daring, and Kim was afraid. I took the photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shogi</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/20/shogi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/20/shogi/</guid>
      <description>Kent&amp;rsquo;s latest hobby is to play Shogi. That makes me an obligatory player and fan as well since, just like chess, Shogi requires two players. We bought a cheap board from Amazon, but he has already stated that a better quality board and pieces is what he would want for Christmas (yes, he is already planning for it).
The game isn&amp;rsquo;t difficult to play, but I am having an excruciating hard time remembering each piece — labeled with kanji characters — and how they move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never-ending Homework</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/14/neverending-homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/14/neverending-homework/</guid>
      <description>Ever since Kent started the 9th grade he has been having to do an unusual amount, and I mean really unusual, of homework. I might be getting too old, but I do not recall having to do that much, so early into high school. It is really messing up his sleeping schedule, and&amp;ndash;kind of&amp;ndash;mine.
Going to sleep really late each day, and waking up when sun still sleeps is wearing me out too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Braces</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/07/18/on-braces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/07/18/on-braces/</guid>
      <description>This is mainly for our records. Today Kent got his braces on, and thus it begins a few months of uncomfortable chewing, special diet, fastidious brushing and everything else that comes with braces.
Now I must go to sell some blood, and place one of my kidneys for sale on the black market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Winter Morning Small Talk</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/cold-winter-morning-small-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/cold-winter-morning-small-talk/</guid>
      <description>We have 36 Fahrenheit degrees this morning (2.2° Celsius). That is mighty cold for almost-always warm, sunny Florida. I stressed it to my child yesternight: he must wear warm clothes the next day. Reluctantly he said &amp;ldquo;OK&amp;rdquo;.
Then comes this morning, and the iMessages exchange look like this:
  Child :  &amp;ldquo;Mama is trying to make me wear an incredibly uncomfortable shirt and is yelling like a siren.&amp;rdquo;   Me :  &amp;ldquo;Why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joy of Reading Hemingway</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/27/the-joy-of-reading-hemingway/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/27/the-joy-of-reading-hemingway/</guid>
      <description>Recently, Kent had the misfortune of picking &amp;ldquo;A Moveable Feast&amp;quot;, by Ernest Hemingway, for a school assignment. I know I am not the right person1 to judge anyone&amp;rsquo;s writing style, I am simply recollecting the comments Kent has made while reading the book.
So far, other than finding the book boring &amp;mdash; mind it, he is barely 13 &amp;mdash; he is puzzled at the use of French terms that he wonders how would the &amp;ldquo;everyday&amp;rdquo; American reader comprehend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morale</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2012/10/31/morale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2012/10/31/morale/</guid>
      <description>Last week I wrote about Kent’s Spelling Bee, and how preparing for it was hard for him and I.
Well, the Bee came and went, and I forgot to come back to post the results. He misspelled &amp;ldquo;morale&amp;rdquo; (he spelled it as &amp;ldquo;moral&amp;quot;) and finished in 4th place&amp;mdash;for me, it doesn’t make sense, as I have always considered first, second and third place relevant, but fourth?&amp;mdash;, which still qualified him to go to the State competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spelling Bee</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2012/10/21/spelling-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2012/10/21/spelling-bee/</guid>
      <description>As a foreigner, trying to go over a Spelling Bee word list with my kid is nothing less than a challenge. For the both of us. First, there are the words I have never seeing; those I can&amp;rsquo;t pronounce. Second, there are the words I will mispronounce. And third, there are the ones I don&amp;rsquo;t know what they mean.
If you add to that the fact that the kid is learning them, hence bound to make many mistakes&amp;hellip; well, yes, a challenge, to put it mildly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science Fair 1st Place</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/03/24/science-fair-1st-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/03/24/science-fair-1st-place/</guid>
      <description>Kent did it again (and we are so happy and proud of him!). The last time he brought home an award was for being on Principal’s list. This time he has gotten first place on Elementary School Science Fair. His project was “How is Electricity produced?”
Off topic, we need a new camera to replace our aged Powershot (Canon PowerShot A640). Any tips?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Augustine</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/03/12/st-augustine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/03/12/st-augustine/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I went with Kent and classmates to St. Augustine, the oldest continuously occupied European established city and port in the continental United States.
It was a great trip, we learned a lot, we saw a lot, it was cold, we came home tired. We will return&amp;hellip; one day. The end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A good day</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/20/a-good-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/20/a-good-day/</guid>
      <description>There is nothing sweeter than waking up and hear your kid say &amp;ldquo;Have a good day Papá. Good bye!&amp;rdquo; It made my day. Thank you, Super Duper!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Brotherhood</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/12/the-brotherhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/12/the-brotherhood/</guid>
      <description>Recently I got the PS3 game &amp;ldquo;Assassin Creed Brotherhood&amp;rdquo; for my birthday and it has being very fun. My dad got me the Harlequincode, and playing him is very fun as well. I have already gotten the armor of Brutus, the very best on the game. Needless is to say, I already finished the game, but am still &amp;ldquo;renovating&amp;rdquo; things.
&amp;mdash; Kent</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas Tree</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/12/19/a-christmas-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/12/19/a-christmas-tree/</guid>
      <description>After a small, but heated battle, on whether or not to buy a real tree for Christmas (Kent and I said no, Kim said yes), Kent and Alyssa are now decorating a Fraser pine tree. I am sure you guessed who won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kent on Principal&#39;s List</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/06/04/kent-principals-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2010 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/06/04/kent-principals-list/</guid>
      <description>Kent&amp;rsquo;s school Awards Ceremony was today. I did not take a picture there, but filmed a bit. The photo above was taken afterwards, at home. He was so happy &amp;ndash;and I so proud of him!&amp;ndash; to receive the trophy for being the whole third academic year on the Principal&amp;rsquo;s List (straight A in all subjects).
I am lucky I got him to smile too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day of sadness</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/04/27/a-day-of-sadness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/04/27/a-day-of-sadness/</guid>
      <description>Today we realized that we have lost our camcorder, and with it, all the memories we had since KM was born: from birth until his last birthday, at least. And the pain we feel can&amp;rsquo;t be explained. How could we be so stupid?!
Although we have thoughts, accusing ourselves for lots of things&amp;hellip; what sense does it make at this point? Everything is gone, and discussing the why&amp;rsquo;s, what if&amp;rsquo;s and so on will not bring the tapes back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The day Santa died</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/02/21/the-day-santa-died/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/02/21/the-day-santa-died/</guid>
      <description>Kim and I have always told Kent Santa exists. Almost every kid is told the same, and get presents delivered by the fat, white bearded guy each year. He gets all the credits, but kids are happy.
With Kent getting into first grade, he has been hearing things from his peers. Things like, &amp;ldquo;Santa doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Santa isn&amp;rsquo;t real&amp;rdquo;, so he began asking about it. About a month ago I told him his peers weren&amp;rsquo;t right, when he commented about it, and that by not believing in Santa they might not get presents next time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa gets the extra love</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/19/santa-gets-the-extra-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/19/santa-gets-the-extra-love/</guid>
      <description>KM believes in Santa. It is that childish fantasy we do not want to spoil quite yet. But the fat guy, with red cheeks, who pilots a sleigh pulled by reindeers, gets all the extra love &amp;ndash;and credits&amp;ndash; for the job we, as parents, do during Christmas time. I challenge Santa to come up with a Wii!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate school</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/09/i-hate-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/09/i-hate-school/</guid>
      <description>When your, almost seven years old, son tells you he hates going to school you worry. It is not the first time that KM tells me he doesn&amp;rsquo;t like going to school. He goes to a private, Christian school, and his main complain has always being that he doesn&amp;rsquo;t like to memorize the weekly versicle. I have noticed that this &amp;ldquo;disliking&amp;rdquo; normally comes after a weekend, holiday, or similar &amp;lsquo;time off school&amp;rsquo; occasion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, they sold it</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/07/yes-they-sold-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/07/yes-they-sold-it/</guid>
      <description>A while ago, I wrote about the closing of the C3 School, previously known as Parkway Preparatory School. As many other parents and staff, I was sad to see the school my kid attended to disappearing. And there were rumors, so I asked a senior Pastor (do not remember his name now) about them. I was told the Church wasn&amp;rsquo;t going anywhere, that the rumors about selling the Church were unfounded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First day at school</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/08/20/first-day-at-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/08/20/first-day-at-school/</guid>
      <description>Today is Kent&amp;rsquo;s first day at school, after the long &amp;ndash;although it did not seemed that long&amp;ndash; summer vacation. It is his first grade, on a new school and I have &amp;ldquo;the jitters.&amp;rdquo; I worry for my son, all the time. I enjoyed this summer with him more than anything in the world. You can&amp;rsquo;t stop them from growing up, you can&amp;rsquo;t be with them all the time. But it is so hard not to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kent on elderly and fitness</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/06/09/kent-on-elderly-and-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/06/09/kent-on-elderly-and-fitness/</guid>
      <description>Having seeing an elder man jogging, Kent asked me why was he running. I told him that he probably wanted to be fit, to keep healthy to which he, in a very surprised voice, replied:
&amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s the fun on being healthy, when you are about to die?!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; kids, they say the &amp;lsquo;darnest&amp;rsquo; things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C3 is no more</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/05/01/c3-is-no-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/05/01/c3-is-no-more/</guid>
      <description>I am sad, I am mad and I am pissed. We got a letter today from Kent&amp;rsquo;s school &amp;ndash;was Parkway Preparatory School, later changed to C3 School&amp;ndash; stating that the school is closing its doors.
 Unfortunately, our continuing analysis and review of the Church&amp;rsquo;s financial obligations has led us to the conclusion that continued operation of the school is not the best use of Church resources. Our decision is also based in part on the projected enrollment for next school year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canon PowerShot A640</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/12/canon-powershot-a640/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/12/canon-powershot-a640/</guid>
      <description>Recently we decided to replace our old Sony little camera, since quite a few photos are going to be taken in the near future, and the poor Cyber-Shot we had really wasn&amp;rsquo;t up to the task. With an under $400 budget, I picked the Canon PowerShot A640, and the picture below is the first one I took, on total automatic mode.
More will come in the near future, as we will have our first real vacation in six years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God is bad</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/08/17/god-is-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/08/17/god-is-bad/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Papá, if you get close to a shark, what would he do to you?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash;Kent asks one day. &amp;ldquo;Well &amp;ndash;I replied&amp;ndash;, if it is hungry he will most likely attack you, try to eat you. If not, he will be scared and swim away. Sharks are by nature afraid of humans and will only come close to them if they are very hungry.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;God is bad. Why would he make sharks, if they could hurt us?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/16/happy-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/16/happy-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Today, a few years ago, a wonderful person &amp;ndash;at least very wonderful to me&amp;ndash; was born. A few years later I was lucky enough to meet her and become her husband.
Today Kim reaches a new milestone and it is with love that Kent I have to say: HAPPY BIRTHDAY MOM!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shredder and Eggroll</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/18/shredder-and-eggroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/18/shredder-and-eggroll/</guid>
      <description>Kent assumes the personality of a different cartoon character &amp;mdash; or hero &amp;mdash; every day. He seems to shuffle between Ninja Turtles, Batman, Danny Phantom, Robin (from &amp;ldquo;Teen Titans&amp;rdquo;), Jackie Chang and others. He has even been Spongebob Squarepants! Needless is to say we &amp;mdash; Kim and I &amp;mdash; are always the bad guys.
Today he decided he was a Ninja Turtle (purple and blue at times) and that Kim and I were Shredders (of different colours, of course).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The three of us</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/05/the-three-of-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/05/the-three-of-us/</guid>
      <description>For one reason or another, we have very few pictures on which the three of us are present. Even today, went I tried to snap one I failed. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, photos we have, but none of them pleases us &amp;ndash;Kim&amp;ndash; to put online for the viewing audience (the very small one we have here).
A couple of days ago I took one photo that I decided to put online, because I like they way KM eyes look and because it represents the priority level in our family: kid goes first, then us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sun and salty water</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/04/11/sun-and-salty-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/04/11/sun-and-salty-water/</guid>
      <description>After almost a year, we returned to the beach yesterday. Jetty Park, by Port Cañaveral is around 45 miles from where we live, but still closer than Daytona. It is quite a nice park, with a decently clean beach. For those of you living constantly under the cold weather, sun and salty water is as good as it gets, right? :-)
Almost a year ago we took KM to Cocoa beach and at the time he was afraid to even touch the water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday Kent Martin!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/01/03/happy-birthday-kent-martin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/01/03/happy-birthday-kent-martin/</guid>
      <description>Today is Kent Martin&amp;rsquo;s third birthday. Happy Birthday Kent! It is amazing how fast the time passes, it seems it was just yesterday when he was born. In this short three years we have managed to spoil him, but no more than the normal, when we are talking about the only child of mid-thirdties aged parents. The day before yesterday was mom birthday as well, 77 years old. Happy Birthday mama!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year 2004!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/12/31/happy-new-year-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/12/31/happy-new-year-2004/</guid>
      <description>As we get closer to changing years &amp;mdash;in some parts of the world it is already 2004&amp;mdash; I feel like going over the things that happened to us (the Collantes&amp;rsquo; family) during 2003. I may not have enough to write about to make this a serious entry, but here I go.
This year we are leaving behind brought very few things, but some made a deep impact in our lives at this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Definitely, humans are born violent</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/04/12/definitely-humans-are-born-violent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/04/12/definitely-humans-are-born-violent/</guid>
      <description>War topics are prime news. From the time we wake up to the hour we go to sleep, war news are the focus of people&amp;rsquo;s attention. We are a violent race, it is not a stereotype: humans are born violent.
My son is barely two years old. He hasn&amp;rsquo;t seen violent television programs, our home is a stable one, no fights, no yelling. Still, when he is around his little cousin, and more often that we would like, he constantly hits her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parents at home</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2002/12/22/parents-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2002 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2002/12/22/parents-at-home/</guid>
      <description>We have my parents visiting for Christmas and New Year. Kent Martin is already showing his happiness and he remembered my dad. I am glad it is not too cold &amp;mdash; at least for now &amp;mdash; so my parents time is more enjoyable (meaning they will be able to go out with us and such). I have miss them a lot and I am really happy to have them with us for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to better protect Kent Martin?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2002/11/18/how-to-better-protect-kent-martin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2002 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2002/11/18/how-to-better-protect-kent-martin/</guid>
      <description>Today was a sad day. I had good times, but my kid felt and badly bruised his lips and that shattered any happy moment I had. I feel like my hands are tied up, because I can not be with him 100% of the time to protect him. I know that even thought I could be with him all the time, I would not be able to protect him against everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent weekend</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2002/10/28/excellent-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2002 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2002/10/28/excellent-weekend/</guid>
      <description>The weekend was excellent and&amp;hellip; pretty tiresome. So tired I was that did not have the energy to come by and tell. It will happen tonight, I just wanted to create some anticipation.
Till tonight, good day!
All right! This is a continuation of what I started. The weekend was excellent, we (Gee, Jessica, Kim, Kent Martin and I) went to two Disney Parks, Disney MGM and Epcot. I had a good time although Kent Martin was the one who had a blast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And on the seventh day he rested</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2002/09/28/and-on-the-seventh-day-he-rested/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2002 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2002/09/28/and-on-the-seventh-day-he-rested/</guid>
      <description>Saturday is about over, at least for me. There is not much to tell about it, it just passed away silently, without much ado.
We went to the mall today, just to walk the kids around. The kids, you may ask? Well, we took Kent Martin and cousin Alyssa (six months younger) with us today. It was pretty tiresome to handle both of them, but it helped us to realize that we have enought with Kent Martin&amp;hellip; for now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>