<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:54:11 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Happiness?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2018/08/24/what-is-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:54:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2018/08/24/what-is-happiness/</guid>
      <description>After questioning myself on the meaning of life &amp;mdash; something I still do, by the way &amp;mdash; I long settled that, regardless of what it might be, living a happy life and aiming to be happy is what life is all about. Happiness, though, isn&amp;rsquo;t a fixed thing. Just like the many avatars of gods, their many incarnations, happiness comes from many sources, and is often found in subtle contexts throughout life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of no Use</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/of-no-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/05/of-no-use/</guid>
      <description>A farmer got so old that he couldn&amp;rsquo;t work the fields anymore. So he would spend the day just sitting on the porch. His son, still working the farm, would look up from time to time and see his father sitting there.
&amp;ldquo;He&amp;rsquo;s of no use any more,&amp;rdquo; the son thought to himself, &amp;ldquo;he doesn&amp;rsquo;t do anything!&amp;rdquo;
One day the son got so frustrated by this, that he built a wood coffin, dragged it over to the porch, and told his father to get in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Living to 200 Years Old</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/16/secrets-of-living-to-200-years-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/16/secrets-of-living-to-200-years-old/</guid>
      <description>This article refers to aging as not being an inevitable fact of life. It goes to describe the marvelous capabilities that some animals have to live, seemingly, forever. Yet, do we really want to? With all the problems we are having with over population, do we want to pursue the holy grail, and extend life to last hundreds?
We have already &amp;ldquo;extended&amp;rdquo; our lives considerably, taking into account that in 1950 the world average on life expectancy was 48 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The very last of Something</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/14/the-very-last-of-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/14/the-very-last-of-something/</guid>
      <description>There hasn&amp;rsquo;t been an article like this for a while, that fills me with such feeling of sadness, and emptiness. For as long as I can remember, a cartoon I saw as a child started my attraction for rhinoceros. Such lovely animals!
And now, the one pictured above (CB2/ZOB/Brent Stirton/National Geographic) is the last of his kind. Who do we have to thank for that? Us. On a comment to the article, a poster under a &amp;ldquo;Gordo Granudo&amp;rdquo; pseudonym writes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where are you from?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/07/30/where-are-you-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/07/30/where-are-you-from/</guid>
      <description>In the States, looking different and/or having an accent will get you asked &amp;ldquo;Where are you from?&amp;rdquo; It doesn&amp;rsquo;t fail, it happens all the time.
Why are we so concerned about knowing someone&amp;rsquo;s country of origin? What difference does it make? If anything, it might be a knowledge we do not want to have. Knowing from where someone is from might spark stereotypical comments and behaviors that would jeopardize an otherwise perfect encounter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specialization is for Insects</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/specialization-is-for-insects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/01/07/specialization-is-for-insects/</guid>
      <description>From Robert Heinlein&amp;rsquo;s science fiction book, Time Enough for Love:
 &amp;ldquo;A human being should be able to change a diaper, plan an invasion, butcher a hog, conn a ship, design a building, write a sonnet, balance accounts, build a wall, set a bone, comfort the dying, take orders, give orders, cooperate, act alone, solve equations, analyze a new problem, pitch manure, program a computer, cook a tasty meal, fight efficiently, die gallantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Lorre Productions, 373</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/23/the-prophet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/23/the-prophet/</guid>
      <description>At the end of each episode of &amp;ldquo;The Big Bang Theory&amp;rdquo; there is always something witty printed, that passes by so fast you can not read it. Today I saw, and remembered, &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; the prophet did not answer right away &amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo; I looked it up, and this came up.
The Prophet  A young woman stepped forward from the throng and asked, &amp;ldquo;0&amp;rsquo; great prophet, tell us how we might find love that is unconditional, unwavering and unending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Meaning of Life</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2012/02/02/the-meaning-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2012/02/02/the-meaning-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Will Durant sent a letter to a few notable figures, asking them for the meaning of life.
 Spare me a moment to tell me what meaning life has for you, what keeps you going, what help—if any—religion gives you, what are the sources of your inspiration and your energy, what is the goal or motive-force of your toil, where you find your consolations and your happiness, where, in the last resort, your treasure lies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Fry on Steve Jobs</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/10/26/steve-jobs-by-stephen-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/10/26/steve-jobs-by-stephen-fry/</guid>
      <description>Stephen Fry is an English actor, screenwriter, author, playwright, journalist, poet, comedian, television presenter, film director and a director of Norwich City Football Club. He is also an awesome human being.
 As always there are those who reveal their asininity (as they did throughout his career) with ascriptions like &amp;ldquo;salesman&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;showman&amp;rdquo; or the giveaway blunder &amp;ldquo;triumph of style over substance&amp;rdquo;. The use of that last phrase, &amp;ldquo;style over substance&amp;rdquo; has always been, as Oscar Wilde observed, a marvellous and instant indicator of a fool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve P. Jobs, 1955 - 2011</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/10/05/steve-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/10/05/steve-jobs/</guid>
      <description>A great man has passed away. While mourning, we celebrate all he brought to us&amp;hellip; his many accomplishments. He will not be forgotten.
February 24, 1955 &amp;ndash; October 5, 2011</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Social</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/08/03/non-social/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/08/03/non-social/</guid>
      <description>Almost over two years ago I left Facebook. A few months ago I left LinkedIn and Twitter. Two weeks ago I left Google+. I also left Groupon (I don&amp;rsquo;t even know why I ever sign up for that junk!). Next is to leave here. I guess this is my way to pursuit happiness.
As Mark weblog is gone1 &amp;mdash;perhaps step 9 was, &amp;ldquo;Get rid of the weblog&amp;quot;&amp;mdash; I enumerate what he wrote:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I thought when my plane crashed</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/05/12/what-i-thought-when-my-plane-crashed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/05/12/what-i-thought-when-my-plane-crashed/</guid>
      <description>From CNN Opinion, this article, written by Ric Elias I liked. I liked it so much, I decided to keep it here, for when it is not longer available at CNN. As I did with a previous article I kept from the WSJ, if CNN does not likes what I have done, let me know and I will remove it, or adapt it to a compromise. Please do not sue me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan Earthquake and Tsunami</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/03/14/japan-earthquake-tsunami-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/03/14/japan-earthquake-tsunami-2011/</guid>
      <description>Japan’s destruction due to the recent earthquake and tsunami is unbelievable. It is more than heartbreaking. Google has setup a page (Google’s Japan Earthquake Crisis Response) with informational links, one of them being one to donate through the Red Cross Japan. Around the clock information from the BBC is also available.
A small donation can go a long way. I have donated, and you can too. Please help by donating (Google’s Japan Earthquake Crisis Response) today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unknown Unknowns</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/01/12/unknown-unknowns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/01/12/unknown-unknowns/</guid>
      <description>It is all about the unknown unknowns, of course!
 &amp;ldquo;There are known knowns; there are things we know we know. We also know there are known unknowns; that is to say we know there are some things we do not know. But there are also unknown unknowns &amp;mdash; the ones we don&amp;rsquo;t know we don&amp;rsquo;t know.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;mdash; Donald Rumsfeld, DoD News briefing.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragons can be killed</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/10/08/dragons-can-be-killed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/10/08/dragons-can-be-killed/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fairy tales do not tell children the dragons exist. Children already know that dragons exist. Fairy tales tell children the dragons can be killed.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;mdash; G. K. Chesterton
 &amp;ldquo;By confining your child to blameless stories of child life in which nothing at all alarming ever happened, you would fail to banish the terrors, and would succeed in banishing all that can ennoble them or make them endurable. For in the fairy tales, side by side with the terrible figures, we find the immemorial comforters and protectors, the radiant ones; and the terrible figures are not merely terrible, but sublime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend starts</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/24/weekend-starts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/24/weekend-starts/</guid>
      <description>The weekend has started. It really started yesterday&amp;rsquo;s afternoon, but who is keeping tabs? The fact is, it is here and thus it brings a dilemma. If I do nothing&amp;mdash;which is impossible if you have a kid&amp;mdash;the weekend will fly by. On the other hand, if I get busy&amp;mdash;and I will&amp;mdash;it will fly by as well.
There are little things in life that keeps you, in a short term, looking forward to a near future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 11th</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/09/11/september-11th/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/09/11/september-11th/</guid>
      <description>We will never forget.
Today, eight years ago, a group of humans, guided by a political agenda, a deep hatred towards the United States, and a mad religious fanaticism slammed airplanes into the World Trade Center, destroying the Twin Towers, damaging other buildings, and killing almost 3,000 people. A second airplane hit The Pentagon, and a third crashed near Pennsylvania after some of its passengers and flight crew attempted to retake control of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China earthquake help</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/15/china-earthquake-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/15/china-earthquake-help/</guid>
      <description>Cities completely wipe out, thousands dead, thousands missing, thousands without anything left. China needs our help, and every little thing would help. Ten dollars might not be much for you, but when many donate we can make a difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesbos islanders dispute gay name</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/01/lesbian-islanders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/01/lesbian-islanders/</guid>
      <description>Who has the right to be called Lesbian? Campaigners on the Greek island of Lesbos are to go to court in an attempt to stop a gay rights organisation from using the term &amp;ldquo;lesbian&amp;rdquo;.
The islanders say that if they are successful they may then start to fight the word lesbian internationally.
The issue boils down to who has the right to call themselves Lesbians.
Is it gay women, or the 100,000 people living on Greece&amp;rsquo;s third biggest island &amp;mdash;plus another 250,000 expatriates who originate from Lesbos?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We remember: Six years ago</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/09/11/we-remember-six-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/09/11/we-remember-six-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>Today, six years ago, a group of animals belonging to the human race decided to take away thousands of innocent lives by destroying the Twin Towers (see World Trade Center). Let us not to forget how stupid they were, how criminal they were, how inhuman they were. Let us remember our brothers and sisters who died that day. For me The Towers stand tall. They always will.
September 11th, 2001: We will never forget!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Craigslist founder will not sell</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/11/07/craigslist-founder-has-no-desire-to-sell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/11/07/craigslist-founder-has-no-desire-to-sell/</guid>
      <description>The founder of craigslist, the free social-networking and classifieds Web site, said on Thursday he is not interested in selling out, just hours after MySpace.com was valued at $15 billion.
&amp;ldquo;Who needs the money? We don&amp;rsquo;t really care,&amp;rdquo; Craig Newmark said in an interview at the Picnic &amp;lsquo;06 Cross Media Week conference in Amsterdam.
&amp;ldquo;If you&amp;rsquo;re living comfortably, what&amp;rsquo;s the point of having more?&amp;rdquo; Newmark said.
[&amp;hellip;]
Newmark said raising the money to subsequently give it away to good causes also did not interest him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/05/23/why/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/05/23/why/</guid>
      <description>While visiting Southtoday I found, once again, this quote that I like so much:
 The first question which you will ask and which I must try to answer is this, &amp;lsquo;What is the use of climbing Mount Everest?&amp;rsquo; and my answer must at once be, &amp;lsquo;It is no use.&amp;rsquo; We shall not bring back a single bit of gold or silver, not a gem, nor any coal or iron. We shall not find a single foot of earth that can be planted with crops to raise food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nazi crimes archives set to open</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/05/16/nazi-crimes-archives-set-to-open-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/05/16/nazi-crimes-archives-set-to-open-2/</guid>
      <description>BBC News: Nazi crimes archives to set open.
 The 47 million files hold Nazi records of forced labourers, concentration camp victims and political prisoners. They have been used to help people trace their relatives, but were kept closed to protect victims&amp;rsquo; privacy. Many people felt the files should be opened to historical researchers to ensure the details of the Holocaust (Nazis genocide) are not forgotten.
 Yes, we must not forget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terri&#39;s autopsy: What does it means?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/15/terri-autopsy-what-does-it-means/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/15/terri-autopsy-what-does-it-means/</guid>
      <description>The results of Terri Schiavo&amp;rsquo;s autopsy were released today. BBC News reported:
 Examiner John Throgmartin said there was no evidence of trauma or strangulation prior to Schiavo&amp;rsquo;s collapse. The autopsy also could not prove that she was suffering from an eating disorder at the time &amp;ndash; her diminished potassium levels at the time could have been affected by emergency treatment. The 41-year-old was found not to have suffered a heart attack or been administered harmful drugs or other substances before her death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembrance</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/09/11/remembrance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/09/11/remembrance/</guid>
      <description>Today, three years ago, a group of animals belonging to the human race decided to take away thousands of innocent lives by destroying the Twin Towers (see World TradeCenter). Let us not to forget how stupid they were, how criminal they were, how non human they were. Let us remember our brothers and sisters who died that day. For me The Towers stand tall. They always will.
September 11th, 2001: We will never forget!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just suppose</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/01/10/just-suppose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/01/10/just-suppose/</guid>
      <description>Suppose you have a friend, a friend like the whole meaning of the word friend &amp;ldquo;somebody who has a close personal relationship of mutual affection and trust with you.&amp;rdquo; It is the person you talk to when happy or when sad, when calm or stressed, when tired or rested. That person is your very good friend.
Now suppose that person wants a job that you think it is not appropriated. It is a job that might require more maturity than what you think your friend has.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>