<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wordpress on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/wordpress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in wordpress on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/wordpress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Joined the rest</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/13/joined-the-rest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/13/joined-the-rest/</guid>
      <description>As you can see, I have joined the rest of the thousands using the drop shadow, centered approach on their websites/weblogs. There are several things I am not sure yet. Different background colour? Should I make the top and bottom with shadow too, with a space at the top and bottom just like it was before? Should I use this opportunity and make the whole interface 800 wide instead of 640 pixels?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress and how I did it</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/06/11/wordpress-and-how-i-did-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/06/11/wordpress-and-how-i-did-it/</guid>
      <description>This might as well be my last entry completely related or dedicated to WP. I am sure I will mention it here and there in the future, but it would have to be something very important for me to talk about it exclusively in one entry.
As the few of you know, I used to run Movable Type (MT) and I was happy with it. The only thing that always bothered me was the rebuild times, which were getting bigger and bigger and the fact the every comment posted would take from 2 to 5 minutes to go through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parsing PHP code</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/27/parsing-php-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/27/parsing-php-code/</guid>
      <description>I am trying to implement a little hack that will allow the use of PHP code within posts. Since I am the only &amp;ldquo;author&amp;rdquo; here, I do not think that will bring much of a security risk. This post is intended to test this hack. I will try the following, &amp;lt; ?php echo(&amp;ldquo;This hack has worked&amp;rdquo;); ?&amp;gt; to see if it does the trick. And here it goes:
This concludes this test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing servers</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/25/changing-servers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/25/changing-servers/</guid>
      <description>As if weren&amp;rsquo;t enough my move to WordPress and my internal debacle on what to do with the site design, now I am getting ready to move all domains and files &amp;ndash;physically&amp;ndash; to another hosting company, on a real colocated server (not VS anymore).
The virtual server I have used until now (and that I still use now, for the time being) served me well, but it is getting old (RH 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living on the bleeding edge</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/20/living-on-the-edge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/20/living-on-the-edge/</guid>
      <description>I have made a habit to upgrade WP every morning and evening to the latest CVS. As I type this I am running WP 1.2 Epsylon RC2, two hours &amp;ndash;more or less&amp;ndash; old. Upgrades are such a breeze that it is actually fun. I find myself looking forward to the next upgrade.
I am not alone on the habit though. Upgrading WP is, certainly, contagious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawing a blank</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/19/drawing-a-blank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/19/drawing-a-blank/</guid>
      <description>I am drawing a blank trying to decided the new layout of this site. I have no problems with the previous one, but as I am running a new engine here I would like the layout to be new as well. I spent a significant amount of time yesterday trying to come up with something and all went to waste.
Perhaps I am procastinating until I see Wordpress 1.2 out, and have all links to be cruft free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt implements inline links</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/19/matt-implements-inline-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/19/matt-implements-inline-links/</guid>
      <description>Matt implements inline links: Just as Charles Gagalac, Mullenweg has implemented a very nice hack. I did the same, but discontinued it after a few posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old permalinks broken</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/15/old-permalinks-broken/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/15/old-permalinks-broken/</guid>
      <description>If you had links to specific entries here you are finding out they broke. Let me start by apologizing, I did not know some people had links pointing to here.
You see, I could&amp;rsquo;ve created permalinks on WordPress that matched the old ones, but I was tired on having such large URI&amp;rsquo;s. That&amp;rsquo;s the reason I have changed them when I switched. The one&amp;rsquo;s in use now will last for a very long time, I have choosen them to be around for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Permalinks</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/15/update-permalinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/15/update-permalinks/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to honor all previously made links to entries around here, so I have tweaked WP accordingly. I did so not only because of the links, but because of the trackbacks as well. Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am not alone</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/14/i-am-not-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/14/i-am-not-alone/</guid>
      <description>Looks like I am not the only one making the move. Judging by the length of the trackback list on &amp;ldquo;Mena&amp;rsquo;s Corner&amp;rdquo;, a whole lot of people is moving away from Movable Type. Since the news has bee Slashdotted, the WP server is overloaded by, not only switchers, but /. visitors. I am sure they will survive. Now ready for the weekend!
Note
Even Mark Pilgrim switched! The world is coming to an end :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the process of moving</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/13/in-the-process-of-moving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/13/in-the-process-of-moving/</guid>
      <description>As you can see, I am in the process of moving from the now defunct Movable Type to the sexy WordPress. Why, you may ask? Well, because I was already planning to and because Six Apart has changed to different venues that do not interest me at all. Also, I was getting tired of the lagginess of MT. Well, it is gone, history. Welcome to a dynamic scenario once again (it all started with i42, remember Stevo and Joey?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>