<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nyt on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/nyt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nyt on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 13:14:44 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/nyt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Unalloyed irony</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/12/08/unalloyed-irony/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 13:14:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/12/08/unalloyed-irony/</guid>
      <description>Soon to be ex-Senator Al Franken announced, on an emotional speech, his resignation yesterday. He is leaving the Senate after been accused of sexual misconduct.
 &amp;ldquo;I, of all people, am aware that there is some irony in the fact that I am leaving while a man who has bragged on tape about his history of sexual assault sits in the Oval Office, and a man who has repeatedly preyed on young girls campaigns for the Senate with the full support of his party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Silence of the Hacks</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/18/the-silence-of-the-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 21:32:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/18/the-silence-of-the-hacks/</guid>
      <description>There is a reason why I subscribed to the digital edition of The New York Times. Its journalists are superb; it is a paper I trust, and have found to be veridical after cross referencing the news they post with other major, equally trusted, news sources.
From yesterday&amp;rsquo;s edition (some emphasis mine):
 The story so far: A foreign dictator intervened on behalf of a U.S. presidential candidate — and that candidate won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incapable of Serving</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/02/14/incapable-of-serving/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 05:49:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/02/14/incapable-of-serving/</guid>
      <description>From the opinion pages of The New York Times yesterday, 13 of February, 2017, also appearing in print today. Some emphasis mine.
 Mr. Trump’s speech and actions demonstrate an inability to tolerate views different from his own, leading to rage reactions. His words and behavior suggest a profound inability to empathize. Individuals with these traits distort reality to suit their psychological state, attacking facts and those who convey them (journalists, scientists).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unpresidential</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2017/01/12/unpresidential/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 20:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2017/01/12/unpresidential/</guid>
      <description>Not presidential at all.
 “President-elect Donald J. Trump’s aides often cite his appearances at professional wrestling matches as an inspiration for his outsize political speaking style, and his buoyantly belligerent news conference in New York on Wednesday proved he has no plans to betray his brawler’s roots in the service of seeming more presidential.”
&amp;mdash; New York Times
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders keeps fighting</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2016/06/09/bernie-sanders-keeps-fighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2016/06/09/bernie-sanders-keeps-fighting/</guid>
      <description>Bernie Sanders has had a good run. Yet numbers are pilled against him, and he should know it. After all he said he was &amp;ldquo;pretty good in arithmetic.&amp;rdquo; Hillary has beaten him, and the right and honorable thing for him to do is to call it quits.
 “If, on November 8th of this year, Hillary Clinton is elected President, we will have only begun to fight,” Sanders told a packed rally in San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Two Child Policy</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/10/29/chinas-two-child-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/10/29/chinas-two-child-policy/</guid>
      <description>This one is worth documenting, as it doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen every day. As a matter of fact, it hasn&amp;rsquo;t happened for over three decades.
 &amp;ldquo;It is the latest twist in the most ambitious and ruthless social-engineering program ever undertaken by a modern state: Beijing announced Thursday that the Chinese Communist Party will officially abandon its one-child policy. Yet it has no plans to relinquish authority over its subjects’ birth patterns; rather, Beijing has simply changed the ration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Francis</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/22/protecting-francis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/22/protecting-francis/</guid>
      <description>The Pope has recently been to Cuba, and today he will be arriving to the United States. Like any other dignitary, the Pope needs protection from both, bad people, and adoring crowds. Yet, doing so is not easy feat.
 “The crowds throw things,” Mr. Clancy, who took over as the head of the Secret Service last October, said in an interview. “They throw flags, dolls and, obviously, babies towards him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Beat a Polygraph Test</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/05/03/how-to-beat-a-polygraph-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/05/03/how-to-beat-a-polygraph-test/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;He used to advise trainees to clench their anus but has since concluded that terrifying mental imagery works better.&amp;rdquo;
 When you get a control question, which is more general, envision the scariest thing you can in order to trigger physiological distress; the polygraph&amp;rsquo;s tubes around your chest measure breathing, the arm cuff monitors heart rate and electrodes attached to you fingertips detect perspiration. What is your greatest fear? Falling? Drowning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ritual of Seduction</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2011/05/27/operation-seduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2011/05/27/operation-seduction/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The ritual &amp;mdash;considered old-fashioned nowadays by just about everyone under the age of 60&amp;mdash; was traditionally a ceremonial, sacred gesture; its history can be traced to ancient Greece and Rome. In the Middle Ages, a vassal paid homage to his lord by kissing his hand. By the 19th century, hand kissing had been reinvented to convey a man&amp;rsquo;s gallantry and politesse toward a woman. Those men who still practice it today know the rules: never kiss a gloved hand or the hand of a young girl; kiss the hand only of a married woman, and do so only indoors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft is a crying baby</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/16/microsoft-is-a-crying-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/16/microsoft-is-a-crying-baby/</guid>
      <description>What does Microsoft do when they don&amp;rsquo;t get it their way? They cry like babies, they snitch and they try to use their mu$cle to get things their way.
 Microsoft Urges Review of Google-DoubleClick Deal &amp;ndash; Microsoft, a veteran defendant of epic antitrust battles in the United States and Europe, is urging regulators to consider scuttling Google&amp;rsquo;s plan to buy DoubleClick, an online advertising company.
Microsoft contends that the $3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>