<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ipad on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/ipad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ipad on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/ipad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Mobile and the iPad</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2013/12/24/tmobile-and-the-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2013/12/24/tmobile-and-the-ipad/</guid>
      <description>I am not sure about the other mobile telephony providers, but this morning I went to T-Mobile with the intention of buying an iPad mini. They had only the dark colour in stock, and on 32GB capacity &amp;ndash; I was wanting a 16GB. The transaction was almost finished, when I was asked for a telephone number. After stating that I just wanted the iPad, no connection, I was told they could only sell it, if it was with a mobile data plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video quality while on 3G</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/05/01/video-quality-while-on-3g/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/05/01/video-quality-while-on-3g/</guid>
      <description>The same day I got the iPad 3G, I noticed a very contrasting video quality while using Wi-Fi and while using 3G. Videos watched on Youtube would have HD quality (Wi-Fi); same videos, while on 3G, would show horribly. Yet, videos on Apple, while on 3G or Wi-Fi, would show perfectly. All that whether using the app or the web browser, tested both.
Is it Youtube serving a very low quality video to 3G users?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPad 3G status</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/29/ipad-3g-status/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/29/ipad-3g-status/</guid>
      <description>It seems that it will be here tomorrow before, or around 3:00PM after all. Just when I was starting to lose my faith&amp;hellip; So happy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend starts</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2010/04/24/weekend-starts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2010/04/24/weekend-starts/</guid>
      <description>The weekend has started. It really started yesterday&amp;rsquo;s afternoon, but who is keeping tabs? The fact is, it is here and thus it brings a dilemma. If I do nothing&amp;mdash;which is impossible if you have a kid&amp;mdash;the weekend will fly by. On the other hand, if I get busy&amp;mdash;and I will&amp;mdash;it will fly by as well.
There are little things in life that keeps you, in a short term, looking forward to a near future.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>