<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/microsoft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/microsoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2015/09/19/microsoft-studio-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2015/09/19/microsoft-studio-code/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft launched its free (non open source), cross-platform, code editor early this year (April, 2015), at its Build Developer Conference.
I have been tempted to try it, as I read its file comparison is very nice, its intelliSense, and it&amp;rsquo;s based on the same platform as Atom, which I happen to love. Today was the day, but as you can see, it is a non-signed OS X application. Microsoft is big enough, and rich enough to afford signing their OS X applications, but they chose not to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft and Global Cybercrime</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2014/07/01/microsoft-and-global-cybercrime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2014/07/01/microsoft-and-global-cybercrime/</guid>
      <description>From The Official Microsoft Blog:
 On June 19, Microsoft filed for an ex parte temporary restraining order (TRO) from the U.S. District Court for Nevada against No-IP. On June 26, the court granted our request and made Microsoft the DNS authority for the company’s 23 free No-IP domains, allowing us to identify and route all known bad traffic to the Microsoft sinkhole and classify the identified threats.
 Microsoft granted rights to take control of another business&amp;rsquo; DNS, to &amp;ldquo;identify and route&amp;rdquo; bad traffic?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft DRM server going offline</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/05/06/ms-drm-server-going-offline/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/05/06/ms-drm-server-going-offline/</guid>
      <description>Rob Bennett, head of MSN Entertainment and Video Services, wrote to customers in an email:
 As of August 31, 2008, we will no longer be able to support the retrieval of license keys for the songs you purchased from MSN Music or the authorization of additional computers. You will need to obtain a license key for each of your songs downloaded from MSN Music on any new computer, and you must do so before August 31, 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Within ten days!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2008/02/07/within-ten-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2008/02/07/within-ten-days/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for submitting your registration to Microsoft Heroes Happen Here: 2008 Launch Events.
You can print this page for your records using the &amp;ldquo;Print&amp;rdquo; button at right. Please expect to receive a confirmation email from [long email] within ten business days.
 The key words here are &amp;ldquo;within ten business days&amp;rdquo;. Ten &amp;ldquo;business&amp;rdquo; days. A confirmation email! Do you find that as crazy as I do? What in the world!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets us make sure</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/28/lets-make-sure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/28/lets-make-sure/</guid>
      <description>Comes v. Microsoft &amp;ndash; Plaintiff&amp;rsquo;s Exhibit 2991 &amp;ndash; (PDF)
  From: Bill Gates Sent: Saturday, December 05, 1998 9:44 AM To: Bob Muglia; Jon DeVaan; Steven Sinofsky Cc: Paul Maritz Subject: Office rendering  One thing we have got to change in our strategy - allowing Office documents to be rendered very well by other peoples browsers is one of the most destructive things we could do to the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want the darn thing?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/18/want-the-darn-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/18/want-the-darn-thing/</guid>
      <description>Beta of XP update made public, A blog by Ina Fried, CNET News.com
 Microsoft issued a release candidate version of XP SP3 in November and expanded its testing earlier this month, promising the public test version would come at some later date.
For anyone who still wants to try the darn thing, Microsoft says, the beta should be up on Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Web site later Tuesday and ready in final form in the first half of next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft is a crying baby</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/16/microsoft-is-a-crying-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/16/microsoft-is-a-crying-baby/</guid>
      <description>What does Microsoft do when they don&amp;rsquo;t get it their way? They cry like babies, they snitch and they try to use their mu$cle to get things their way.
 Microsoft Urges Review of Google-DoubleClick Deal &amp;ndash; Microsoft, a veteran defendant of epic antitrust battles in the United States and Europe, is urging regulators to consider scuttling Google&amp;rsquo;s plan to buy DoubleClick, an online advertising company.
Microsoft contends that the $3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vista, don&#39;t like it? Too bad!</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/04/12/dont-want-vista-too-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/04/12/dont-want-vista-too-bad/</guid>
      <description>It seems that for those individuals who do not build their own machines &amp;ndash;that is, assemble them&amp;ndash; there will be no choice when it comes to pick their OS.
 Windows XP to be phased out by year&amp;rsquo;s end despite customer demand &amp;ndash; Computer makers have been told they&amp;rsquo;ll no longer be able to get Windows XP OEM by the end of this year, despite consumer resistance to Vista and its compatibility problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Microsoft ads on Freshmeat</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/11/30/heavy-microsoft-ads-on-freshmeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/11/30/heavy-microsoft-ads-on-freshmeat/</guid>
      <description>Freshmeat is, in their own words, &amp;ldquo;the first stop for Linux users hunting for the software they need for work or play.&amp;rdquo; and it also &amp;ldquo;offers a variety of original content on technical, political, and social aspects of software and programming, written by both Freshmeat readers and Free Software luminaries.&amp;rdquo;
I have been very surprised to see, more and more, Microsoft ads on Freshmeat. All over the place. Quite often. Freshmeat lists thousands of applications, &amp;ldquo;[&amp;hellip;] preferably released under an open source license [&amp;hellip;]&amp;rdquo; .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Vista is not going in</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/11/30/why-vista-is-not-going-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/11/30/why-vista-is-not-going-in/</guid>
      <description>I was talking &amp;mdash;well, chatting&amp;mdash; the other day with a friend of mine and he was telling me some bad experiences he had had with a Windows Media Center upgrade. That got me talking about Windows Vista, perhaps it is because Windows Vista Ultimate comes with it, I am not sure. Anyways&amp;hellip;
I told my friend I am not installing Vista (although I have Windows Vista Ultimate &amp;mdash;the final version of Vista, no beta, no RC, but final&amp;mdash; as part of my MSDN subscription).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neoseeker: IBM will not use Windows[...]</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2006/03/08/neoseeker-ibm-will-not-use-windows-vista/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2006 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2006/03/08/neoseeker-ibm-will-not-use-windows-vista/</guid>
      <description>IBM will not use Windows Vista - but will move to Linux desktops - Neoseeker News Article: IBM switching to Linux desktops in Germany according to a Linux Forum 2006 presentation by their head of open source and Linux sales in Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Security Bulletins</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/07/13/microsoft-security-bulletins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/07/13/microsoft-security-bulletins/</guid>
      <description>This is the second time that I receive a Microsoft Security Bulletin and, since Microsoft uses PGP to sign their bulletins, I have decided to check their signature validity. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if this has been a flaw in the past as well, since I delete those bulletins without even reading them most of the time, but in the two occassions I have checked them, they had failed to verify, since the signature is bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They advertise with the best</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/06/13/they-advertise-with-the-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/06/13/they-advertise-with-the-best/</guid>
      <description>Imagine my surprise when I saw the following Google Ad showing under one of my posts this morning:
[Was a screenshot of a Microsoft MSN advertisement on Google]
I guess Microsoft knows who is the best, right? I mean, the only way to see that advertising (other than serving adds on your own web space) is by searching the web using Google. I think it is funny&amp;hellip; and interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flipping the switch</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/07/27/flipping-the-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/07/27/flipping-the-switch/</guid>
      <description>Next Monday (August 2nd) we are flipping the switch from the old reliable Linux based email system (Sendmail, Washington University IMAP/POP3) to a relatively newly deployed Microsoft Exchange 2003. Needless is to say that we &amp;ndash;TRC staff&amp;ndash; all have been busy wrapping things up to minimize the impact. But things &amp;ndash;bad things, unexpected things&amp;ndash; are bound to happen. It is just a matter of time.
With Exchange I say good bye to the taken-for-granted reliability, easy maintenance and trouble free email system that we had, to dive into the unknown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do you want to try it?</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2004/05/20/do-you-want-to-try-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2004 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2004/05/20/do-you-want-to-try-it/</guid>
      <description>A demo of Office 2004 for Mac is available for Mac users to try. From Microsoft MacTopia Office 2004 page:
 &amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;There&amp;rsquo;s time for fun and time to focus. When you&amp;rsquo;re ready to get down to business, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Office 2004 for Mac provides the intuitive, intelligent tools you need to transform your ideas and opportunities into action&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
 No, thank you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks to the Slammer, Slammed</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/01/27/thanks-to-the-slammer-slammed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/01/27/thanks-to-the-slammer-slammed/</guid>
      <description>Yes, just like a lot of people around, we got &amp;ldquo;slammed at work.&amp;rdquo; There were several hundred of machines on Campus, I presumed, but the five we got compromised are the one&amp;rsquo;s that bothered me the most.
Out of the five, two were servers, our servers, my servers. A brand new SQL server, just a week old, more or less, was missing the hot fix. Another older one, under the control of somebody else, but still within my College was missing it too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Bill Gates, with love</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2003/01/24/from-bill-gates-with-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2003 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2003/01/24/from-bill-gates-with-love/</guid>
      <description>I received an email today. While it is true that I receive 60 to 70 emails daily, this one was not trivial. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t the expected porno offer, nor a letter from Nigeria or Lagos promising riches. Is wasn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;reputable&amp;rdquo; diplomas or innocent spam passed along by a lack-of-knowledge friend neither. If was an email from Bill Gates itself. Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s right, an email from the billionaire Gates.
I have to admit that my first thought was, &amp;ldquo;It is another spam&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>