<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bookmarklets on David Collantes</title>
    <link>https://collantes.us/tags/bookmarklets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bookmarklets on David Collantes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collantes.us/tags/bookmarklets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bookmarklets I use</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2009/11/07/bookmarklets-i-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2009/11/07/bookmarklets-i-use/</guid>
      <description>These are some of the general bookmarklets I use. I have them synchronized with Chrome and Google Docs, but I am listing them here in case I want to share them with someone else, like you (yes, you there, reading this now). Here there go:  Tweet it! Translate to English Google Dictionary Get Youtube MP4 Record your screen URL to QR Code Selection to QR Code  More will be added as I find the need for something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SuperGenPass update</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2007/12/07/supergenpass-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2007 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2007/12/07/supergenpass-update/</guid>
      <description>SuperGenPass: A Free Bookmarklet Password Generator
Chris Zarate has updated his SuperGenPass bookmarlet, which now has it&amp;rsquo;s own dedicated domain. Version 1.1 comes with (from the website):  Moveable window: The SuperGenPass window can be moved by dragging the title bar. Smarter password capturing: When multiple master passwords are found, the conflict must be resolved by double-clicking the desired field. Smarter autopopulate: Autopopulate is on by default, but only for fields where the master password was found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Single sign on</title>
      <link>https://collantes.us/2005/05/29/single-sign-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2005 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collantes.us/2005/05/29/single-sign-on/</guid>
      <description>Since I am going to start migrating all my web logins to a single sign on approach (using Chris Zarate SuperGenPass), I think the best way to start is by saving the bookmarklet I will have to use over and over. There is a Greasemonkey version available, which has much more features than this bookmarklet version. I will use the latest because it works with all browsers.
The bookmarklet is: Single Sign on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>